Dairy Café Part 1

	You frequently wander the streets together with your slaves and every time you set foot into the city you find something new and interesting that hasn't been here before.
	Just today you discovered a pleasant looking little café which is located near the busy main streets but still a bit away in some minor alley.
	Tables and chairs are positioned outside the little house, which obviously couldn't handle all the customers.
	Nearly every single table was occupied and you hardly find a place to sit down together with (Slave Name).
	You try to look up the name of the shop, but all you find is some can used in dairies to store milk, which is openly positioned in front of the entrance. Nothing else in sight seems to be the sign of the café, so you'll just call it Dairy for now, until you get to know it's exact name.

	After you waited a while you see why this place is so packed - and why they are mostly male customers.
	The waitresses are gorgeous. They all got a nice face, a slim waist, broad hips and long legs. But the thing which is the focus of attention is, that every single one of them has huge breasts, too huge for their frame even.
	And their uniform does well in accentuating their breasts.
	From now it doesn't take that long for a waitress to show up in front of your table and with a friendly smile hands you the menu.
	You're surprised, that everything on it are milk products, quite uncommon for a café, and even for this time of the year, as milk products quickly go bad.

	As you don't know what quality their products are you decide for something small, a glass of milk for you and (Slave Name).
	You hand back the menu to the waitress and give her your order. "Two glasses of milk it is, then," she said and nods.
	You notice her cheeks are a bit flushed as she hurries away to get the things you ordered.

	Fortunately it doesn't take long for her to come back with to glasses on her tray, each of them filled to the brim with dazzling white milk.
	The waitress looks even more flushed than before as she hands out the glasses, avoiding eye contact and finally hurrying away again.
	Wondering you take the glass, even more wondering that it's kind of luke warm.
	A bit cautious you sip the milk, tasting if it's gone bad, but to your surprise it's not bad... it's not bad, it tastes quite good.
	After finishing up to the last drop you want to pay. While you hand the waitress - the same one as before - the coins she asks you how it'd taste, and you assure her it was really good.
	After you said that with a charming smile she quickly hides behind her tray, her cheeks flushing deep crimson and she hurried away faster than before.
	You worry a bit about her behaviour, but let it slide for the moment.
	As it really was good, and despite the many customers also kind of a relaxing break, you decide to come again some time in the future. But still, you keep wondering about the odd behaviour of the waitress.

Dairy Café Part 2

	It's another nice and warm day as you decide to wander around with your slave. The busy streets, buzzing with insects in the shape of humans and beings that closely resemble humans. Near the slave pens you even see a cage with some kind of giant bug safely locked away in a evenly giant cage. As (Slave Name) lets out a small shriek you decide to not walk to the docks, but instead deeper into the city's bowels.
	And you remember a little shop which is there, the Dairy Café you just recently found.
	You decide to head straight there, but as you're not overly familiar with this part of town you get lost, just a little bit - about 2 times.
	But still, in the end you manage to find your way to the café and sit down on an emtpy chair on an empty table - again, it seems it's the only available one as this place seems as buzzing with people as the main streets, except all people here are just sitting down, eating and drinking and obviously oggling the waitresse, who don't seem the slightes bothered by it.
	You even see one waitress giving a little show, hugging herself, clearly accentuating her breasts and bowing down a little, whispering into a customers ear, who suddenly flushes crimson and avoids further eye contact with her, while the waitress only briefly wears a seductive smile on her face.
	As she stands back up, she reverts to her customer friendly smile.
	You want to keep watching a bit, but your view gets obstructed by something, something flesh colored.
	Just as you wondered a bit, you noticed what it was, it were the huge boobs of the waitress from the last time, standing in front of you, seeming slightly displeased.
	Although you don't feel quilty, you still apologize for oggling her college a bit, but it seems, it wasn't the response she waited for, if she even waited for one, because suddenly she got a bit flustered, avoiding eye contact. "Ah, no, it's ok, it..." she stammered a bit with a slightly nervous look in her eyes - still avoiding yours.
	Quickly she changes the topic and hands you the menu, which didn't change in the slightest since your last visit.
	Exactly as the last time, you order a glass of milk, as you remember, that it was quite good. Also you're not here to satisfy your hunger or anything like that, just to relax a little bit and have a nice time in the city sitting here instead of running around and forcing yourself through all these people who are busy doing things you aren't interested in.
	The waitress looks somehow pleased with your order and again you notice a tinge of red on her cheeks as she hurries away trying to bring your order as fast as possible.

	After only a short while she comes back to you, on her tray two glasses of milk, with slightly more flushed cheeks and a bit out of breath. You thank her for bringing your order so fast to which she smiles shyly.
	Trying to be polite and sound concerned, you ask if she has a cold or something the like, as you notice she doesn't necessarily look that healthy.
	The waitress looks slightly shocked but assures you that she's health incarnate.
	You mentally shrug and take a sip of your milk, which tastes exactly as you remember - luke warm but good - and notice out of the corner of your eye, that the waitress is watching you closely as you  swallow, going a bit redder than before.
	Still you can't really explain, why she does that, but at the moment to you it's clear, that she's probably waiting for a tip. Seeing your purse lose another coin kind of makes you sad, but you still manage to act like you completely forgot and give her a tip with a charming smile, to which she goes al flustered again, quickly thanking you and hurrying away.
	As you sit there for a while, you get the feeling, you're being stared at from time to time, but you can't make out who or why is staring.
	But as nothing happens except the waitress coming sometimes to ask if you need anything else you quickly forget the incident.
	After some time, you quietly stand up, pay for your orders and walk away, feeling another stare in your back.

Dairy Café Part 3

	Another day and you're bored, so why don't take a little walk? As you're generous you take (Slave Name) with you to the city to relax a bit and explore.
	But as you're starting to feel uncomfortable within the sea of people flooding the streets you decide to go frequent the less populated alleys and remember, that there was this one shop you visited some time ago, with all these big-breasted waitresses.
	This time you don't even lost this time around and walk nearly straight to the shop, only stopping for short moments to orientate.

	As usual the place is full and as usual it seems you find the last table available and quickly sit down. It doesn't take long for a waitress to appear, although it's not the one who served you the last two times but another one you don't know so far. But she's equally beautiful and also has this huge bosom stuffed in near skin-tight clothes.
	She hands you the menu and awaits your orders, which are the same as ever, just two glasses of milk.
	As strange as it seemed, the waitress seemed kind of happy with that order, don't edging you on to buy more expensive stuff. With a slightly shy smile she leaves your table.
	As you wait you look around a bit and notice some kind of argument at the entrance to the shop.
	You see the new waitress as well as the one you encountered before talking to each other, but you can't really hear what about, as they speak in a very low Volume, but nonetheless it seems, they are arguing.
	After a bit break off and the the new waitress goes into the shop while the other slumps her shoulders.
	It doesn't take that long for your order to arrive after that and you take a sip as usual, tasting the milky flavor.
	It's still kind of luke warm and tastes quite good, but it's somehow different than you can remember and you ask about the difference.
	"Oh, you can tell?" the waitress asks with a beautiful smile. "Each waitress here serves a bit different milk, let's say it's one of our specials." She winks at you, but you don't really get the meaning.
	"If you come the next time, you can ask for a special waitress, if you desire. By the way, my name is Christine."
	Again she smiles at you, but this time kind of seductively. "I-I'm Maria!" tells you a voice from behind.
	You look around just to see the waitress you encountered the first and second time, who seems kind of fidgety.
	"If... if you can, would you please ask for me, the next time, you come here?"
	After saying that she quickly turns around and hurries away. You don't really get, what she's up to, but you just mentally shrug and avert your attention from her back to Christine, who has a knowing grin on her face as she watches Maria hurry away.
	But she quickly turns away from her and wipes the grin of her face as she quietly cleares her throat.
	After you give her her tip and assure her, that you don't need anything else you finish your glass and continue your stroll through the city, this time not only feeling one but two pairs of eyes staring at you.

Dairy Café Part 4

	Again you find yourself walking around with your slave, frequenting several shops, plowing your way through the masses in the streets and again in need of a break.
	Fortunately you now can find the way to the nice café with the nice waitresses without getting lost or having to orientate yourself that much.
	This time however you seem rather lucky, as there doesn't seem to be much customers today.
	Sitting on an empty table you remember the conversation from the last time, where you can even pick your own waitress.
	As an of yet unknown waitress comes to your table to give you the menu you think about what to do:

	a) Call Maria
	b) Call Chrstine
	c) Just get a glass of milk

	Part 4 a)
	You say to the waitress, that she should call Maria, the one you talked with some time ago.
	The unknown waitress seems to be a bit disappointed, but quickly leaves to call her college.
	And it doesn't even take long before Maria comes out of the shop, obviously hurrying to get to your table.
	As she came closer to your table she somehow managed to stumble on something. Just before she falls to the ground you instinctively jump up and capture her in your arms.
	While you're holding Maria, she however seems to be spaced out, looking up to your face, a dreamy look in her eyes.
	It does take her a few seconds to gather her thoughts. Then she flies out of your arms, hurriedly standing up.
	"T-Thank you" she tells you as her cheeks flush bright red.
	It takes a while for the atmosphere to return from akward to normal, but still you managed to order two glasses of Maria's milk which she brought you in the twinkle of an eye.
	You slowly drink the liquid while noticing something strange. Somehow it seems a bit warmer than usual... and you don't know why, but your cheeks seem kind of warm, like you're drunk.
	You ask Maria if she put something into your drink but she assures you that nothing she did nothing suchlike - but still she blushed furiously as you asked.
	After finishing everything you try to set forth but Maria stops you for a bit.
	"If... If you come the next time, I-I want you to come inside the shop."
	Feeling a little drunk you easily agree to that and finally walk away.


	Part 4 b)
	You say to the waitress, that she should call Christine, the one you met the last time.
	The unknown waitress seems to be a bit disappointed, but quickly leaves to call her college.
	And it doesn't take that long for Christine to come out of the shop, a beautiful smile on her face.
	She quickly takes your order - the same as ever - and brings you your glasses of milk handing them out to you and (Slave Name).
	After that she looks around a bit, observing the other customers before she decides, that she won't be needed there, and sits down on an empty chair at your table.
	"Is it tasty?" she asks, as you sip on your glass, to which you give a small nod. "That really makes me happy. But I never thought you'd call for me. Wouldn't you rather call Maria?"
	"Why?" you ask her. "Well, she likes you, you know? And she's cute."
	You tell her, that it's flattering to hear to be liked by someone, but that doesn't necessarily mean you like her the same. And Christine seems as cute - to which she blushed a little.
	Afterwards you change the topic a bit and discuss rather insignificant things with Christine until you finished and decided to leave again.
	"The next time you come," she starts talking, "will you come inside the shop?"
	You ask her if it's special to come inside. You think that it's normally packed in there.
	"Oh, the inside is for invited guests only, so there're many empty seats. And I would like to show you something nice." She smiles at you seductively.
	As you don't have a special reason to deny her, you ensure her, you'll be there the next time you come.



	Part 4 c)
	You have no particula desire to speak to one of the waitresses you know and you just want to relax a bit so you just order the typical glass of milk - it seems you got hooked on it - to which the waitress blushes a little.
	It seems, that ordering milk is something special here but for now you try to ignore it.
	After some time relaxing you finish everything, give the waitress a little tip and finally walk away, into the masses on the buzzing street.

Dairy Café Part 5 a)

	It wasn't that long ago that Maria invited you - and probably (Slave Name) too - to visit the café again, she even asked you to come inside, although you don't see a reason why it should be that special. It's just a café, why would you even need an invitation to enter?
	As you thought that you enter the building, only to bump against something hard. You look up and suddenly feel small.
	The thing you bumped into turned out to be a huge man, towering more than 2 meters. On his head you can make out bull-like horns sticking out. His body is covered in short black fur and his feet end in hoofs while a tail swishes around angrily.
	"What are you doing in here?" he askes with a deep voice dripping with anger. You know, you definitely couldn't win against that monster even if you'd attend to fight it so you quickly think about what to do.
	Either you turn around and flee immediately or you try to talk to the man - it's no wonder you forgot about the invitation for a moment.
	"Get out or do you want me to break your bones, puny one?" The bull-man now speaks with hostility as he cracks his knuckles. In that moment you realize, talk would probably solve nothing and you try to turn around as fast as possible while avoiding doing anything he would see as aggressive.
	Just as you turned around you hear the well-known voice of Maria. "Dad! Stop that! I Invited him*!"
	"Oh?" the muscle man only raised an eyebrow while folding his arms and just being intimidating. "So Maria invited you?"
	"Ah, yes" you nearly stammer while he stares at you. If his stares were physical they would probably rend you to shreds.
	But after you state again that you've been invited the bull-man smiles and steps to the side. "If that's so you're welcome here. Oh, and my name's Minos, little one, what's yours?" You tell him.
	You jerk a bit as one of his big hands lands on you shoulders, even though he doesn't use force. "Come on in!" His voice now sounds friendly and his hand shoves you in the house.
	After you went to the middle of the room he turns his back towards you again guarding the entrance.
	You look around a bit and see something similiar to a living room instead of the interior of a café. "It seems it's the first time you've been here," a female voice calls out to you.
	As you look around you see a woman, who's probably in her late thirties and apparently highly pregnant. The voice belongs to her. And behind her you see Maria, who seems to hide behind the woman and looking at you a bit embarrassed.
	"Then I welcome you in the name of our small family. And now, excuse me, I have to do some milking. Oh my back."
	You see her walk away slowly, seeming a little bit in pain.
	"Ah, t-that's my mother," Maria quickly tells you.
	Being a bit overwhelmed by those new facts you try to just get them into your brain as fast as possible and change the topic. You ask Maria why she would invite you - and (Slave Name) - into their house.
	"I-I want to show you something. It's a bit embarrasing, but I still want you to know. Could you please follow me?"
	After saying that she quickly walks away, deeper into the house. With no other choice left you and your slave follow behind her.
	You enter one small room, only big enough for a bed as well as a small table and a chair. On the table you see an empty glass.
	Maria stands beside the table and shows you to sit down on the chair, which you do.
	"W-Well, you know," she starts fidgeting a bit, "you told me, the milk I serve tastes good, and you even asked for it the other day, and... and I want you to... to drink more of it." She somehow get's embarrassed and starts fidgeting more - and you don't even know why exactly. You ask yourself, just why she took you to this room; at least if she didn't intend on doing something indecent.
	Maria closes her eyes and breathes in and out a few times before she continues. "P-Please, watch me."
	After she says that she takes the glass from the table and guides it to her breasts. She takes of a button of her blouse and her big bosom falls out of her clothes. She then puts the free hand on one of her breasts and puts the glass to her slightly longer nipple, which rapidly gets hard. Kneading the flesh a bit and lastly tugging on her nipple she lets out a pleasured sigh while milk suddenly shoots out of her breast, flowing into the glass until it's filled to the brim.
	After she finished she breathes heavily, her face bright red and the rest of her skin also slightly flushed.
	She looks a bit dreamy at you as she carefully puts the glass back on the table.
	It takes her a few seconds to come back down to earth and as she does she flushes even more than before, quickly buttoning up her blouse again and walks to the door - more like fleeing.
	"Th-That's all for t-today." After stammering that she runs away, hastily closing the door and leaving you alone with (Slave Name) and one glass of milk on the table.
	You wait for a while but Maria doesn't come back, so you reason she won't come back at all.
	As you get bored waiting you decide to talk to (Slave Name) as you notice, she's kind of fidgety herself, often looking at the glass.
	You just thought about the training your slaves doing right now and thought about something good. If you come here again you may get some information regarding her training... and Maria also said "that's all for today", probably meaning there's more to come in the future.
	Wanting to tease your slave a bit you suddenly take the glass and empty it in big gulps, hearing (Slave Name) gasp a little.
	Well, you drinked it three times now, so it doesn't hurt drinking it again, even knowing what it is. Still, you seem to get sligthly drunk from it.
	You hope it doesn't indicate you're getting sick.

	*needs distinction if male or female.

Dairy Café Part 5 b)

	It's another day plagued by accute boredom while training your slave - it's probably not that boring for (Slave Name), but you get easily bored these days as you keep repeating the same things again and again for every slave.
	So you decide to take a little break and remember the little café you went to recently.
	Quickly you find your way there and see that it's packed as usual, this time not even a single table free for you to use. As you try to turn around to walk away you see someone walking up to you, and it turned out to be Christine.
	"Why do you try to leave again? You're always welcome here. Oh and as I said, you can just go inside, I already told that you can enter. Just wait a bit, I'll try to be there as fast as I can."
	After saying that she quickly leaves again to serve the customers. You on the other hand take what you're offered and enter the house, which is unexpectedly dark inside, so you can't really see anything from the outside and the first moments inside you can't see anything at all.
	After a short moment you also notice exactly why you can't see anything except black... a huge bull-man stand in front of you, glaring down at you and it seems he won't budge at all.
	You feel a bit intimidated but still manage to speak to that man-monster. "Excuse me, but I've been invited into, so could you please... make way?"
	Unfortunately he keeps staring you down without saying as much as a word, but unexpectedly he makes way after he had stared enough. "You better wait here for the one who invited you," he finally says to you in a deep bass voice.

	Luckily it doesn't take that long for Christine to arrive. "You didn't do anything to my guest, did you, Dad?" she immediately says to the towering giant. "No dear, I didn't do anything unusual."
	She didn't seem that pleased with the answer but let it slide. "Please follow me" she tells you. Of course you don't have anything against that, as it brings you away from the giant.
	While following Christine you briefly see a highly pregnant woman, probably in her late thirties. "That's Marie, one of dad's wifes, and Marias mother," she introduces her curtly. "Oh, by the way, he got three wives and six daughters, just before you ask, and yes, he's a bull-man... as if it wasn't obvious. And that leads me to something I want to show you."
	As she said that she opens the door to a room which is only big enough to fit a bed, a table and a chair. On the table stands one emtpy glass.
	Christine tells you to sit on the chair while your slave unfortunately has to remain standing.
	Quietly she closes the door, and turning back to you she wears a smile you can't really interpret. It's somehow between shy and seductive. Quietly, slowly and showy she unbuttons her blouse, giving way for her huge breasts.
	"You see," she starts talking, "I kind of like you, so I want to show you something really interesting." She massages her breasts, rubbing the flesh and sometimes tweaking her nipples. Her body flushes slightly red and she lets out quiet moans as she seems to pleasure herself.
	"They feel really good, especially when they're full and you need to release." Your stares fixed on her breast you are getting a bit confused, but that quickly abates as she takes the glass and puts it to her breast. Strongly she tugs at one of her nipple letting out a pleasured moan together with a white stream shooting from her breast - milk.
	She doesn't stop until the glass is filled to the brim, panting heavily at the end.
	"Here's your glass of fresh milk." She hands you the glass with a smile as you sit there dumbstruck. "I have to admit, it feels really good, if you're being watched." After a short pause: "And I would really like to... continue, but unfortunately I don't have that much time today. So... would you please come again when there's not that much patronage outside? Of course you can remain here for a while, but I can't accompany you any more..." The next sentence she whispers directly into your ear with an especially seductive voice: "And that milk is especially made for you."
	After that she quietly leaves the room, her cheeks a bit flushed.
	As you wonder if you should drink or not you notice (Slave Name) being a bit fidgety and you look at her. She has her hands on her breast, slightly massaging them, appearing to be spaced out a bit. As you speak to her she gets all flustered and quickly hides her hand behind her back.
	In this moment you decide to drink the milk in big gulps, observing your slave closely and noticing her cheeks get bright red as she looks at you drinking the white fluid.
	After that you set the empty glass down on the table and head out - while hiding the grin on your face.
	This could prove useful not only for your fun and entertainment but can even bring something new to your training.

Dairy Café Part 6 a)

	You feel strangely restless lately and your thoughts wander from your original goal, the slave training. They seem to wander to one specific location. Not the auction houses to buy slaves but another part of town. A small house, hidden in one of the small streets.
	That is also the location you wander to right now, your slave on your coat-tails.
	You deliberately ignore all the customers sitting on their chairs and leering at the waitresses in their outfits. You enter through the dark doorway as if it was normal - except you rammed head on into a wall, again.
	"What do you want?" the deep voice bellows from above.
	Rubbing your hurting nose you tell the giant bull-man that you've just been here recently and are here right now again to see Maria.
	After looking at you a bit suspiciously he lets you pass. "She's behaving rather odd lately, you should probably be a bit wary." Shrugging your shoulders you pass the giant without another glance.
	Recently you've got this strange longing for Maria, and it gets stronger as you're here in her house.
	You don't know, where you should start searching for her or if she even is here at all. You can't be sure.
	But not knowing where to go, you head to the room you were in the last time you came here.
	Your feet move faster and faster the more you approach the small room at the end of the corridor.
	Slightly short of breath you stand in front of the wooden door and slowly - nearly fearful - open it.
	The next moment you feel something falling against you, giving you a strong hug. Loose hair obstructs your vision for a short while as you feel Marias warmth soaking your body.
	"I was waiting for you", she says while still having her face burried in your chest. Your heart beating faster than before you stroke her head and softly tell her, you wanted to see her, too.
	You gently push Maria in the room and close the door - (Slave Name) just rushed in before she got locked out, as you seem to have completely forgotten about her the moment you saw Maria again.
	Together with Maria you sit down on the simple bed, which makes a low creaking sound.
	"I really..." Maria began, but you put just put your finger on her mouth and she stopped.
	But it didn't stay there, but instead slowly crept down her chin, her throat, onto her collarbone and slid insider her collar, just resting above her huge breasts. You feel her body heat even more than before and it feels warmer than you expected, almost as if to burn you.
	A low moan escaped Marias throat as she felt your - for her - cold fingers on her hot skin.
	With your other hand you slowly unbutton her blouse and after that's done you slowly peel her out of it.
	Her breasts being freed fall out of her clothes while she trembles because of the cold air grazing her skin.
	Finally your hand resolves it's way down her body, feeling up her mound.
	Her breath grows hotter as she tries to feel your hand with her breast, slightly pressing against you.
	Even though they're bigger than most you've seen, they are really firm.
	Avoiding her nipple you slide your hand over the entirety of her breast, even slightly stroking the underside and slightly lifting it to feel its weight in your hand.
	Again you're surprised as her breasts are heavy, much heavier than you expected.
	As if reading your thoughts Maria whispers in your ear "I need to be milked" with a clearly seductive voice and it's not difficult to imagine, what she wants you to do.
	Again you let your cold finger creep across her skin, up to the very top of her mound, which eagerly awaits your touch, standing already fully erect.
	You feel like teasing her a bit and just lightly rub the nipple with your thumb to which you feel Marias body tremble and her throat escapes another moan. With pleading eyes, filled with desire, she looks at you.
	Like that being the starting signal you suddenly tug at her nipple, to which she lets out a small yell and a squirt of milk flies from her breast.
	With that one motion her breath grew even hotter and it seems her normal shyness disappeared. She clearly pleads for more, being milked harder. As you in order to meet her wishes start taging harder she lets out loud moans of pleasure, seemingly close to pure bliss.
	Even you yourself start to feel pleasure milking her, like your hand is being satisfied just by touching her skin.
	It doesn't take long for her to soak both of you in her milk, but both of you just ignore the fact and continue with the milking.
	In fact somewhere along the line - you can't even remember when - you started drinking the milk, directly from the source, hightening her pleasure even more as well as your own.
	You feel your body temperature rising and your desire growing even further. All you can think about is Maria, Maria and Maria, everything else being completely swept out of your brain.
	And everything goes black.
	You have blacked out, but not just you, Maria also suddenly lost consciousness, while (Slave Name) stays awake, feeling oddly aroused, trying to stop herself from rubbing her own breasts.
	A giant black shadow falls on her as she looks at the two lying there, breathing hard with flushed skin.
	"Hmm... somehow it was to be expected."
	The deep voice sounds even more intimidating in this small room.
	"You better keep your friend from coming here again, it seems neither of them can handle it."
	(Slave Name) just looks at him, questioning him with her eyes.
	"Maria is a bit special... ever heard that milk of happy cows tastes better? Well, that's a bit rasistic, but it precisely describes what Maria's milk can do. She can transmit her feeling through her milk... normally it's not bad, it even makes for more customers, but it seems, Maria got some mighty crush on your friend here.
	Didn't he/she* mention Maria a bit more often these days? Well, probably. The more he/she* drinks of her milk, the more he/she* falls in love with her... well, somewhere it should stop along the line, but it seems that her own milk is influencing herself. She has a crush on your friend and that transfers to her milk... and than her milk hightens her own crush. It's a vicious circle of longing.
	If we keep them alone they'll probably do nothing else anymore than ... having each other. If it get's worse, they go at it until they die of exhaustion. Not something I wish for my daughter. Well, she might be happy with it, but I don't think I would be happy with it. Or would you like to lose your friend like that?"
	After that speech he walks to your body and effortless lifts you up. "Rather light" is his only comment while he carries you out of the room, careful not to bump you or himself against anything - which is not that easy considering is height.

Dairy Café Part 7 a)

	You feel kind of sluggish as you wander around town. You can't seem to remember why that's the case, nor can you remember what you even did, the last time you came here; just some time ago you woke up in your bed with one hell of an headache and a small case of amnesia - at least, that's what (Slave Name) told you.
	Your feet seem to head towards one specific location, but as soon as you try to set foot in one of the smaller streets your slave forcefully tears you away from it and drags you toward the mass of people buzzing around like bees in am hive.
	You let out a sigh, some word mixed with it you don't even recognice.
	(Slave Name) on the other hand hears the small "Maria" escaping your mouth and starts remembering what happend... trying to resist the urge to rub her breasts.

Dairy Café Part 6 b)

	You head to the city and take (Slave Name) with you. Of course your goal has something to do with training your slave.
	So you head towards the little café in the middle of the city. Luckily there aren't much customers outside so you are one step closer to your goal. Now you just have to find Christine; but that isn't hard to do, as you clearly see her walking around handling customers together with Maria and some other girl.
	As Maria sees you she shoots you a nervous glance, but you only give her a small nod and walk up to Christine.
	Before she can actually say something to you you bring your face near hers and whisper to her, if she got time today.
	It seems she didn't quite expected such a forward question as you see her blush deeply.
	But still, she nods back without hesitation, giving you her unique smile.
	You say to her, you'll wait for her and after that enter the house, dragging (Slave Name) behind you.
	Learning from your past experience though you don't walk head first into the doorway, as there's standing the usual wall of muscle and fur to deny entry to anything unwelcomed.
	This time you didn't crash against his chest, to which the giant clicks his tongue in unpleasantness, but still obediently steps out of the way.
	You vaguely remember where to go and therefor it doesn't take you long to find the room you've been in the last time.
	The inventory is the same as the last time, except that there's no glass on the desk this time.
	You order (Slave Name) to sit on the chair and face the bed, wheras you sit down on said bed and look alternating to your slave and the door, thinking about the things you'll do.
	It doesn't take that long for Christine to appear. She looks flushed, but not like she rushed here.
	As she steps through the door you order her to sit next to you on the bed, which she does without complaint.
	If it's okay to have a little fun today, you ask her. She gives you a small nod, but then looks a bit worried at (Slave Name). "Shouldn't she wait outside?" she asks you. You ask her if it really matters, especially after she said last time, that she feels better being watched.
	Christines cheeks flush a bit more than before, but she remains silent, not denying it, so you take it she approves of it.
	As there is nothing hindering you from some fun now, you sit behind her and whisper into her ear she should just relax and you'll be having some fun together.
	She seems to be a bit nervous, but does not show any kind of resistance as you unbutton her blouse from behind, presenting her large breasts to the air.
	You put your hands beneatch the mound of flesh and push it up, weighing its heaviness in your hand and feeling her body heat, which went up a little.
	She doesn't seem uncomfortable, just a bit shy, and looks kind of worried towards your slave. But that worry does not last long, as your hands crawl over her breasts, softly kneading the flesh. You trace your finger around her areola and feel her body shake a bit.
	A soft near inaudible moan escapes her lips, but it's filled with a bit of distress, as it arouses her slightly, but thats all.
	But you still continue, to only lightly carress her breasts, making sure to show her breasts to your slave.
	As you kiss Christines neck, you start putting more force in your hands, which is greeted with a audible and pleasure filled moan. As you tuck her nipple a bit, you can feel a slight wetness as her milk slowly wells up from them.
	You tell her, she got some wonderfull tits there as you continue to fondle and knead them. (Slave name) seems to enjoy the show, because you can see her groping her own breats, trying to feel the same pleasure as Christine.
	You take one hand of from her breasts and turn her head sideways.
	It doesn't take her long to realize what your intentions are and she willingly turns her head as you take your hand back to fondle her breast.
	She sticks out her tongue, to taste yours, and you quickly follow, kissing her, sucking on her tongue and playing with her insides all the way while putting more strength in your hand.
	More and more milk gushes forth as her bosom changes form under your caressing. Your partner seems to have forgotten every worry in the world, only seeking pleasure from your tongue and your hands, as she pushes her head towards yours and rubs her breasts against your hand, if they ever stop.
	You can feel her body heat and see her skin glisten erotically with sweat, whereas her breasts get wetter and wetter with her milk. It seems even though you only play with her breasts she nears a heavy orgasm. You could be either mean and stop just there or take it to the finish.
	Even while still considering the option to just stop and tease her immensly you forcefully tug on her nipples.
	A loud moan escapes Christines lips, as her entire body trembles from one enormous orgasm. A strong squirt of milks shoots out of her breasts and lands on your moaning slave. Because of this unexpected event (Slave Name) lets out a small shriek as the milk lands on her face, but that just seems to take her to the edge as she comes lightly.

	Unfortunately Christine just passed out from her orgasm, just when your own body got kind of hot. Maybe her breasts were a bit too sensitive?
	(Slave name) instead is leaning a bit powerless against the wall, panting heavily.
	You think about letting of some steam with her, so you write a quick note and leave it on the table.
	Maybe you'll come again some time to have some more fun, but you have to go now, so you can't look at her sleeping face after passing out.


for a bull part reference look up SortingFile/text/cow/The Interview - The Bull's Story


Milking Ruins
	We have arrived at the ruins, and have spread out to look around. For some reason, I found a strange mural. it depicts women, with
	their breasts exponentially larger. Each picture depicts the woman/women in a hands­and­knees, with the fore­mentioned breasts reaching to the ground.
	Strange ­ it seems like there is a white fluid come from their breasts in this picture. This must be milk, for no other liquid can be secreted from the human breast. There also seems to be people drinking from a river, which seems to originate form the women.
	Note ­ the women in question seem to be very few, and seem to enjoy this predicament.

	Well ­ I'm in a pickle. i was studying some ancient murals, when i noticed a level like obtrusion. Being my curious self, I pulled it.
	Immediately, a hole opened up underneath me, and I felt some 100 feet before landing in a pool of water. Strangely, the only thing that go wet is me, my notebook is as dry as the sun itself.
	When I came out of the water, I found myself in a village like area. In it, women were crawling around. They had huge breasts which spanned the gap between their chest and the group, not stretching at all! Each of them had milk dripping from them.
	When they saw me, one of the crawled up to me, and said she was the leader. She explained that they were down here since the time of the Incas. She said that the air down here contained a drug like mist, which would slowly cause me to become like them. Since I could not return to the real world, I would be trapped here forever. The gas also made them, and later me, immortal, which helped me to understand why they still looked young and beautiful.
	She also explained that they were able to become pregnant due to dildoes which were magical ­ having the ability to spray cum like a real cock. My mind is spinning. They have given me my own hut, and I anxiously await the day when I will not stand out

	It has been a week since I entered this place. I have now taken to going nude, as the changes to my very body have began. My breasts
	have grown 3 cup sized, now sizeable GGG cups, or I cups. My hips are pushing out, and my waist is moving inward.
	My breasts are also very sensitive now, and any touch to them now will make me feel great pleasure. They have no sag at all, and the leader of the colony, whose name is Julia, said that they never will.
	They also tell me that it will be another week or 2 before my milk comes in, and then a week after that, my walking capabilities will have been stolen. I am starting to enjoy life down here.
	Other women are coming to talk to me. They tell me of the time of the Aztecs and why they were made like this. Apparently, their king wanted milk. He wanted so much, that he killed the cows in the area from pure exhaustion. So he sent his scouts out in search of more. They found no more, but instead found a strange cave, where women because milking cows. The king was overjoyed, and moved the entire village to near the cave. Then he chose them as his milk producers, and sent them into the cave. Over time, they became what they are today, and the king had died while they continue making milk.
	That story is kinda cool ­ I mean, a king wanted milk?


	I have great news! My milk has now come it with a vengeance. It takes an hour to fill up my now SSS cup tits. I an now finding it a bit
	hard to walk, and my hips are now a impossible hourglass, my tits curving inward to my waist, and then flaring out to my waist. My pussy hair has also fallen out, and my breasts send impulses of pleasure to me when ever touched ­ to the point of me almost cumming.
	I have to milk my breasts every day 3 times, and I cum every time. I am now deep within the transformation process, and I am loving it. I never want to go back to the real world.

	Well, It's happened. I am now incapable of walking. When I woke up this morning, I was unable to stand. I am now one of the milkers of the
	society. Crawling around is a whole new experience for me. My breasts are constantly brushing the ground, and I love it. It feel like a gentle caress, and it is amazing. I now have my personal milking machine, and I give off 2 litres a day, one from each enormous mound of womanly blessing.
	My breasts are now full of womanly fluid. I am thinking of trying pregnancy, but i dunno. I love life here.
