I ran throu all of the threat and did make a resume of the older ideas. Tell me what you like to see in the game. I the text is already there and all that is missing is to code it, then the chance of me agreeing to do it are much higher.


Changes to story line
[SPOILER=1]On losing the first fight with the milk baron's henchman, the SM is just killed outright. I know the MB is supposed to seem brutal, but that seems a little to dark for this game. The capture endings would fit fine there, so why not use them (capture and rape fit the tone of the game a lot better than cold-blooded murder).


Secondly, the possible massacre at the beach also seems quite dark. Killing off a bunch of innocent people who are unrelated seems way to dark for this kind of game. Even if the MB was that brutal, mass murder like that would probably bring the full force of the militia down on your head. Having a few of his men sneak into Adisa's private section would work better, since the only reason someone else would come there is to meet her.On losing the first fight with the milk baron's henchman, the SM is just killed outright. I know the MB is supposed to seem brutal, but that seems a little to dark for this game. The capture endings would fit fine there, so why not use them (capture and rape fit the tone of the game a lot better than cold-blooded murder).


Secondly, the possible massacre at the beach also seems quite dark. Killing off a bunch of innocent people who are unrelated seems way to dark for this kind of game. Even if the MB was that brutal, mass murder like that would probably bring the full force of the militia down on your head. Having a few of his men sneak into Adisa's private section would work better, since the only reason someone else would come there is to meet her.[/SPOILER]




Additional Content
[SPOILER=2]A couple of minor things that bugged me as well. When searching the milk barons complex during the attack, and when finding something to ass-fuck Adisa, selecting any option other than the correct one has no effect beyond providing some flavour text. I think that for Adisa, it would be fine to have the SM try all the options in sequence before eventually trying the billiardballs (at the least, it would prevent people from reloading after they selected the billiard balls because they wondered what other results the event might have). For the Milk Baron's base, maybe going to the big barn could allow you to sabotage his coaches. That way, if you agree to let him go, you can follow and find the crash site. Adisa's restraints could keep her from being thrown around to much, but the milk baron would be seriously injured, making the fight with him easier.[/SPOILER]
[SPOILER=3]Former Milk Slave (FUta)
Description: While held as a Cow your breasts were also milked of there bounties while never the focus they remain far more sensitive than others.
-More sensitive breasts, more easily effected by lactation drugs. 
(should also have a Slight bonus to Bust 1-3% perhaps)
[/SPOILER]
[SPOILER=4]3
4th February 2012#528
Sciences:
This event fits for other actions as well, e.g.: Theology, Etiquette, Library:
[if she has “Breast Fixation” 40+](slavename) sits at her desk and has difficulties to focus on her work.
She is so aroused she starts to think about sex. She dreams of her breasts being touched and squeezed. She realises they became more sensitive and thus more important to her.


[if she has “Lactation” 10+]Suddenly two tiny wet spots appear on her clothing! [if dressed: The wet fabric getting somewhat transparent]. She tries to cover her tits[if dickgirl:and erect cock]with her arms and rushes to a bathroom.
She locks the door behind her[if dressed and undresses her breasts]. She touches, fondles, squeezes her chest-meat and even tugs and twists her nipples. [if dickgirl: With one hand she plays with her tits and with the other she plays with her hard cock.]
She goes on like this until she can finally cum and coax white milk from her rock-hard nipples.


After a few minutes she returns back to her desk, smiling from her orgasm.


[if she has “Breast Fixation” 60+]
(slavename) sits at her desk and has difficulties to focus on her work.
She is so aroused she starts to think about sex. She dreams of her breasts being touched and squeezed. She realises they become more and more important to her.


[if she has “Lactation” 60+]
She lets out a tiny gasp when she remembers the joy of milking her breasts. It's like she could feel her milk building up pressure inside her. She opens her eyes and realises that her breasts really are swelling a little, and the pressure rises. 
[if dressed: Her loaded mammaries press against her clothes until finally they can't hold her heaving flesh any more.]
[if naked: Her loaded mammaries expand under her unbelieving eyes]
With a muffled sound her breasts thud onto her desk.
She excuses herself and rushes to the next bathroom, trying to cover her tits [if dickgirl:and rock-hard erect cock] with her arms.


After locking the door she finally touches, fondles, squeezes her chest-meat and even tugs and twists her nipples. As the first stream of milk erupts (slavename) is on the verge of orgasm. She milks herself with both hands, making a milky mess around her. 
[if bust-size >150cm : She can even titfuck herself with her huge breasts!]
[if she has done "feed her milk at least 5 times: She raises one of her heavy, overcharged udders to her face, sucking hard and greedily on her nipple. Chugging down her own milk she cums, twice!
Eventually she can feel the sucked tit decrease. Even though she already feels very full (slavename) immediately grabs her other tit and continues to suck and chug.]


After a few minutes she returns back to her desk, with a broad smile from her multiple orgasms.
[if she has done "feed her milk at least 15 times: Her belly is visibly distended, a big firm bulge from drinking nearly all of her own milk. For the next half hour she secretly feels her tummy and breasts again and again.]
Attachment 497066Attachment 497067Attachment 497065


Theology:




Etiquette:


SUSO 1: This event can fire randomly, one time only per slave
Today #slavename came too late to class. Rushing toward the classroom she clashes into a fellow student. #slavename topples her over, both fall to the ground, #Slavename on top of the girl. To her surprise, #slavename lands very softly. As she takes a secound to recouperate, she hears a soft little moan. Raising her head #slavename realises she landed with hands and head on the students truly enormous chest!


These massive mammaries must be quite sensitive, the girl seems to be very aroused just from #slavenames touch and the involuntary kneading she got when #slavename tried to stand up. In a combined effort they finally both stand up again. Just as #slavename has pulled the girl up from the ground, her knees give way and the busty student bumbs into her, causing the girl to moan again. #Slavename is a bit embarrassed but also slightly aroused by the soft, lustful sighs whispered into her ear.


Finally the girl pulls herself together.
"I...I'm sorry, I ...I'm a bit....I...I'm Suso. I...I'm sorry I bumbed into you."
Suso seems to be terribly embarrased by her arrousal and runs away.
[if breast size is more than 110cm: Suso looks back as she runs away, maybe glancing at #slavenames own huge rack [if bust of #supervisor is 120+: and the big tits on #supervisor] .].]


#Slavename and #supervisor rush to her class, both bemused and aroused by the remembrance of the soft pillows she just rested her head on...
Attachment 497070
[Lust + 2]






SUSO 2: This event can fire randomly only ahter SUSO 1 has happend. it is repeatable.
Today #slavename came too late to class again. Rushing toward the classroom she slips and by incredible luck clashes into Suso again. #slavename topples her over, both fall to the ground, #Slavename on top of the girl. #Slavename lands very softly on Suso's gigantic love pillows. 
[if breast-size is >120cm: Her own massive tits are being pressed hardly against Suso's, all four mountains of breast-flesh bulge out between the two.]
[if breast fixation is >30: She can't help but moan from the intense feeling in her chest.]
[if lactation is 60+ or milk build-up is 45+ ONLY if No Nipple-clamps: Two wet spots appair immediately at her nipples are, as her milk is pressed out of her tits.]


Suso's massive mammaries really are quite sensitive, the girl seems to be very aroused just from #slavenames touch and the involuntary kneading she gets when #slavename tries to stand up.
[if breast-size is >120cm: And there certainly is a lot of contact area between the mammaries of them both]
[if breast fixation is >30: #slavename gets more and more aroused as they both try to get up.]
[if breast fixation is >50: #slavename quickly comes dangerously close to orgasm as they both try to get up and their tits keep pushing together.]
[if breast fixation is >50 AND lust is >50: #slavename not only gets quickly aroused by their breast flesh mangling against each other: she prolongs the wrestling on the ground for as long as possible, getting not only herself but Suso as well very close to a tit-orgasm right there on the school-floor.]
[if breast fixation is >60 AND lust is >75: The horny #slavename gets very quickly aroused by Suso's moans and their breast flesh mangling against eatch other: she prolongs the wrestling on the ground for as long as possible, getting not only herself but Suso as well to the very edge of orgasm. Suddenly both girls freeze, holding perfectly still but quenching each other very tightly. A close observer might notice the shivers and Goosebumps as both girls simultaneously have a very quick and very clandestine tit-orgasm right there on the school-floor.]
[if lactation is 60+ or milk build-up is 45+ ONLY if No Nipple-clamps: The longer their wrestling goes on, the more and more the both of them get wet with her and maybe even Suso's milk.]


In a combined effort they finally both stand up again holding each other at arms length. From this close, Suso's tits really seem gigantic.
[if breast-size is >120cm: Still the tips of their breasts touch each other, making Suso shiver again. They take care not to touch.]
[if breast fixation is >50: One or two times Suso inadvertently touches your slaves breasts, making Goosebumps appear on #slavenames skin.]


Different endings:
[ending 1 if none of the below fits: Suso seems to be terribly embarrased by her arousal and the display of clumsiness and runs away.#Slavename and #supervisor finally rush to class, both bemused and aroused by the remembrance of the soft pillows she just rested her head on and the fact it happened again...
[addition to ending 1 if breast size is more than 110cm: Suso looks back as she runs away, maybe glancing at #slavenames own huge rack [if bust of #supervisor is 120+: and the big tits on #supervisor] .]
[Lust + 1, Joy+0,5]


[ending2 if breast fixation is >50 AND lust is >50: The huge titted student is not sure if #slavename caused her arousal on purpose or not. She breathes very heavily excuses herself timidly and rushes of to the bathroom. Although the school-hallway is empty Suso's skin is flushed deeply with embarrassment. #Slavename rushes to her class, very, very aroused, so close to an orgasm she spends most of the lesson just thinking of sex and fondling her mammaries.
[Lust + 15, breast fixation + 0,5, no gain from class]


[ending3 if breast fixation is >60 AND lust is >75: The two girls stand staring at each other for a brief moment. Both are still breathing irregular and their faces show the flush of a recent orgasm. Suso is not sure if #slavename caused her incident on purpose or not. Before #slavename can say anything, she murmurs:
"I...I'm sorry, I ...I'm a bit....I...I've got to go! I...I'm sorry I bumped into you." Although the school-hallway is empty Suso's skin is flushed deeply with embarrassment.
#Slavename rushes to her class, both bemused and quite satisfied by the tit-quickly she just had.
[Lust -10, breast fixation + 0,5]
[addition to endings 2 or 3 if lactation is 60+ or milk build-up is 45+ ONLY if No Nipple-clamps: Both girls rush to different bathrooms, trying to dry themselves. They are soaking wet from #Slavename's milk. Maybe Suso lactates as well?]
[milk build-up -20]
Attachment 497070






SUSO 3: This event can fire randomly only after SUSO 1 has happend. it is repeatable.
#slavename makes an excuse to #supervisor, and darts of to the bathroom. When she is sure the hallways are empty, she hides behind a pillar and waits for the ever late Suso rushing down the hallway. As she hears her approching, #slavename ponders her options:


choice 1: Greet her friendly
choice 2: Greet her with a bear-hug
choice 3: tackle her to the ground again.
choice 4: Feel her up directly.


Choice 1: #Slavename approaches Suso, greeting her from a few meters afar. Both girls continue their way to class and chat along. Suso seems shy but happy to see #slavename again. As they enter class they take two tables next to each other and continue to chat by frequently exchanging tiny letters.
might expand on this later....


Choice2: As Suso is close to her, #slavename jumps from behind the pillar and greet her with an enormous bear hug. 


...
...




Attachment 497070
[Lust + 2]




SUSO 4: This event can fire randomly after SUSO 1 happened, it is repeatable
As #slavename enters the classroom she immediately notices the female student with the enormous breasts she bumped into earlier. Suso greets her shyly.
She takes the empty table next to her and greet her back. She can't help but realise that Suso's tits are so enormous that they rest heavily on Suso's desk, although the girl sits with a straight back.
During the next two hours #slavename notices that Suso often has difficulties to write or get something out of her bag. While the immense size of her chest seem a little hindering, the main problem seems to be her sensitivity: Every time she graces them, Suso bites her lip, sighs lustfully or moans.
[if breast fixation is <30: #Slavename grins to herself, covertly enjoying the show.]
[if breast fixation is >30: #Slavename first grins to herself but than gets aroused herself, covertly watching Susa and cupping herself.
Attachment 497127
[if breast fixation is <30: lust+0.5.]
[if breast fixation is >30: lust+2, breast fixation+0.5]






SUSO 5: This event can fire randomly after SUSA 1 happend:
As #slavename enters the classroom she immediately notices the female student with the enormous breasts she bumped into earlier. Suso greet her shyly.
#slavename takes a desk next to her, greets her and the class begins.


Sometime during the lesson Susa drops one of her pens. Susa and #slavename reach down for it at the same time but thus bumping their head together midway. Maybe only #slavename can hear it but she is fairly certain that Susa moans as her massive tit is pinched between her table and her own weight.
[Susa bits her lip and tries to reach for the pen again but her movement causes one of her tits to slide from the table and swing pendulously under her, grazing #slavenames arm in the motion. Susa bits her lip tighter as she slightly shivers and goosebumbs erupt on her arms. 
#slavename holds still for a secound and the finally gets the dropped pen. She gives it back to Susa who is obviously trying hard to constrain herself but at the same time can't stop holding her enormous tits. The big titted student gives her a thankfull nod, deeply embarassed and flushed red.
#slavename can't help but thinking that Susa sure has sensitive breasts. The ever so quite gasps and moans from her side arouse her as well.






three more events planned involving theese here already edited pictures
Attachment 497128Attachment 497129Attachment 497130
(by the way: suso means breasts in the language of the samar islands 




6th February 2012#545




Meet Suso while running1
Spoiler for Meet Suso while running1: 
my pic: , original: 
If you make her do fitness, while under personal supervision and after Event Suso1:
As #slavename makes her rounds running, she sees the very busty student Suso, she met at etiquette-school. She is clad in a sport dress, with shorts and a shirt , stretched very tight by her massive mammaries. With every step she takes, her tectonical chest-meat swings around with enormous vigor. Most of the time she hold her tits with her arms, but still her pillows bulge and billow. Quite a display, you think for yourself.




Downtown:
Spoiler for Meet an admirer the city1: 

Take a walk, downtown, repeatable: [If Slaver Skill Breast-Expert is 1+, Slaver has finished at least one Cow-Girl, and personal Supervision:You and #slavename stroll down the marketstreets as suddenly a young woman greets you:
"Excuse me, are you #slaver?" Seeing her lovely features and her well endowed rack you greet her back.
"Oh, I just wanted to greet you personally. I admire your work! I mean, I saw one of the slaves you trained the other day and her breasts where so...."
She touches her own ample tits unconciously
"To imagine recieving so much lust just from her....and the form of her...well"
She flushes and excuses herself
"Anyway, it was nice meeting you. Bye!"
[Slaver: Conversation +0,1; Reknown +0,1]




Downtown:
Spoiler for Meet an admirer the city2: 
original, i still want to edit and use for adisa: 
Take a walk, downtown, repeatable: [If Slaver Skill Breast-Expert is 1+, Slaver has finished at least one Cow-Girl, and personal Supervision:You and #slavename stroll down the marketstreets as suddenly a young woman greets you:
"Oh, hello! May I talk to you a minute?" Seeing her slim figure and her bulging rack you stop to talk to her.
"I...well, I met one of your slaves lately, you know: the one you taught to ....." She flushes" ..oh, you know, to enjoy her jubilies way more than normal."
She very slightly swings her own big breasts and cups them subtly. "We talked for some while and...I learned a thing or two, I enjoyed very much!"
She prepares to leave you to your business but adds:
"I, I really admire your skill, I told all my friends of you!"


[Slaver: Conversation +0,1; Reknown +0,1]






Meet hot girl on beach
Spoiler for Meet hot girl on beach: 
original, notice I gave her a brasilian trim down there : Taking a walk on the beach 
[If slaver skill breast expert 2+ and at least 1 finished Cow-Girl and personal supervision, repeatable Event:
As #slavename and you walk down the beach you are approached by a young woman. 
"Excuse me, aren't you #slaver? I have a very pleasurable favor to ask from you!"
You pause and take a closer look at her:
She is very tall and tanned to a very dark tone. Her long, defined legs end in a marvellous firm ass, her flat cute belly and very slim waist are topped by two big, full tataas, barely constrained by her tiny bikini. Her slender arms sport several bracelets and she holds a bottle of some sun-tan-lotion. Overall a stunning appearance!
"#slaver, I have heard quite a lot about your special skills. I have met one of your breast fixated slaves you trained. From what she told me, you must be a real wizzard with your hand. So, here is my offer:
You use your magic fingers and apply my lotion to all of my body, but of course especially my breasts. If your skills hold up to your reputation and you can make me cum just from my twins, I will grand you one sexual wish. I will do what ever you want me to, as long as it involves just the two of us. Look, I even brought a basket with a few sextoys. If you disappoint however, I will tell all my friends at court of how bad your skill as a slavemaker are."
Confident in your advanced skill as a Breast Expert you agree to her terms.


You start to apply the lotion. As you finally reach her breasts you start to massage, knead and even tug on her tit-flesh vith vigor and determination. But somehow the tanned woman doesn't react as strong as you have hoped. While she moans and gasps in lust, by now she should have come at least two times. Suddenly you realise that your fingers are a little number than usual. This is when you realise that this damn women tried to cheat you. Maybe she was send by one of your competitors to destroy your reputation or she just wanted to frame you herself. But who ever tried to fool you, underestimated your skills. With renewed determination you pull all your tricks, every little secret on her. By the look in her eyes, she must have realised that her deception isn't working, her orgasms approaching quickly. Finally you made her cum, her back arcs, her feet and hand clench into the warm sand. Flushed and shiny she lies on the ground, shivering, breathing heavy.
"Damn it! I guess I lost. Your skills truly are impressive. So...I guess, I have to fullfill my end of the bargain now, do I?
What dou you demand of her:


[If male or futa: Oral] With just a little reluctance the tanned woman lowers your pants and starts to fondle your sex. She quickly puts your cock into her mouth and starts to suck hard. As your cock swells she beginns bobbing her head up and down, and, to your surprise, deepthroats your entire length effortless. She must have some training, you think to your self. She must want to make you cum as quickly as possible. After just a few minutes you finally cum, with your cock deeply buried in her throat. After a few minutes more, the tanned women gets up , gathers her belongings and leaves without another word. 
[Slaver Lust -5, fatigue +0,5]


[if female: oral] With just a little reluctance the tanned woman lowers your pants and starts to fondle your sex. She spreads your legs and goes to town with surpring skill. She seems to know exactly when, where and how hard to suckle your clit, or labia. With two of her fingers in you and her hot mouth on your sex, it only takes minutes for you to cum. She must have quite some training doing this. After a few minutes more, the tanned women gets up , gathers her belongings and leaves without another word. 
[Slaver Lust -5, fatigue +0,5]


[If male or futa: fuck her] You quickly undress and tell her to bend over. She sighs, but complies, dropping her bikini-pants. Her vagina is still dripping wet and gaping from her strong orgasm, so you have no difficulty sticking your throbbing cock into her. You are a bit surprised as how hot and wet she is insside. She burns your member to an immediat orgasm. her pelvic muscles are really well developed, her vagina holds your cock in an incredible firm grip, it feels like she just sucks your semen out of you. Within minutes you cum. She realy must be trained well in this. After you came, the tanned women gets up , gathers her belongings and leaves without another word. 
[Slaver Lust -5, fatigue +0,5]


[If male or futa: assfuck] You tell her to bend over, ass you are going to fuck her ass. She sighs, rolls her eyes but complies. Rubbing some of her pussyjuice on your throbbing cock and some on her tight asshole, she finally graps her ass-cheeks and pulls them apart. You enter her burning hot ass with surprisingly litle resistance. She must be well trained in assfucks. Her dark tunnel is very tight, the pressure from her pelvic muscles nearly break you. After only a few minutes you cannot go on anymore and cum, your cock deep in her ass. After a few minutes more, the tanned women gets up , gathers her belongings and leaves without another word. 
[Slaver Lust -5, fatigue +0,5]


[if female: tribalism] Almost eagerly, you and the tanned women get into a tribalism position and quickly start to grind each others hips at one another. Her well lubricated sex feels incredible hot on yours, her legs clamp down around you pulling you closer to her. She must really enjoy this, for after just a few minutes, you and the woman cum, but she keeps going until the both of you are satisfied. After a few minutes more, the tanned women gets up , gathers her belongings and leaves waving you goodby. 
[Slaver Lust -5, fatigue +0,5]


[request nothing] The tanned woman looks truly baffeled. Suprised that you did not take advantage of her. She quickly leaves, with a very thankfull look in her eyes. Maybe she will tell somebody of your generosity.
[Slaver Lust +2, reknown +0,1]




[/SPOILER]
[SPOILER=5]4
1) Maybe consider changing the forest bandits event to have a higher chance of repeating, but give a "downtime" after each event to represent them packing up and moving camp.
I wanted to add more events in the deep forest, the plant-tentacle-event for example. Maybe an X in the southwest-most corner could appear as a marker for the "Deep Forest". Then, Event C would be moved there
4) A bad end if her breasts get too big, maybe the mass forcing her to be immobile.
Thought about adapting texts for very big slaves, maybe a bad end for too big slaves. But that is something for later...
you should add a new copitition cattle show
Good idea, maybe a Cow-Girl-Competition could be added 


[/SPOILER]
[SPOILER=6]5
Spoiler for Plant-Impregnation-BE-Event, reworked, including Love Robins spellcheck and suggestions: 
Forest: (maybe only in the deep forest if it gets added)
this one is a bit more extreme


(slavename) wanders around the border of a small clearing as [if personal supervision: you][if assistant supervision: your assistant] takes a leak behind a tree.
As she reaches the edge of the underbush she notices an exotic aroma; strange and somehow alluring. She follows the smell into the forest, quickly disappearing from view.


She finally arrives at a circle of stone-stelae, looking very old and half buried under vines and bushes. Suddenly (slavename) comes to her senses, as the smell fades. She does not like the look of the stone circle but before she can leave a green tentacle-like vine wraps around her ancle. Just as she looks down at her foot another creeper curls quickly around her arm, then another one, and finally a whole bunch of the green vines have her securely entrapped.


She is carried across the stone-circle towards an altar-like central rockpedal. [If naked: A few thin vines creep under her clothes and start to rip them apart until her pussy[if dickgirl:, cock] and breasts are uncovered][If nippleclams: They snap off her nipple clamps in one quick movement]
The vines bind her to the central rock. Soon she is covered with small thin bundels of vines which crawl and slide all over her body. It looks like they are looking for something. After only a few minutes the vines have discovered her ass and pussy and start to slowly push inside her.


(slavename) gasps in horror and pain as her pussy and ass are each invaded by a green vine, maybe as thick as a finger. As soon as she opens her mouth two thin vines enter her mouth. They probe and feel around until they have found the back of her mouth. The smooth green vines then descend down her throat causing her to cough and gasp.


Meanwhile other tentacles start to circle her breasts, squeezing tightly, as they curl around them. A vine with a strange blossom on top reaches for her nipple. As the blossom opens it unveils a mysterious translucent cup, fitting perfectly on her nipple. A minute later her other nipple is covered by another such cup as well.


(Slavename) moans as other vines retract from the rest of her body and concentrate on her loins and mouth. With little effort 3 new tentacles enter her pussy, probing deep into her. Another tentacle forces its way up her ass as well. While the feeling of their probing is very strange and uncomortable, it does not hurt, as the vines are quite small in diameter.


Looking down on herself she can see her nipples protruding and swelling. The transparent cups are producing a strong underpressure, sucking on her nipples.
[If lactation is >30: Drops of milk emerge from her swollen nipples, disappearing into the vine]
[If lactation is >50: A steady flow of milk emerges from her swollen nipples, disappearing into the vine]
[If lactation is >70: A rich stream of milk emerges from her swollen nipples, disappearing into the vine]
Her mouth is entered by another tentacle, quickly descending into her throat. Although she coughs and fears of not getting enough air, her body is starting to react to the constant touch of the swirling vines.


With some effort 3 more creeper make their way into her pussy. They quickly sink deep into her. Two more of the green vines squeeze up her ass. Their probing gets more synchronised and slowly changes into a more sliding movement. This movement is a bit more comfortable, the bundle of vines is as thick as a normal cock in diameter by now.


[if Lactation is at least 30: Maybe her milkflow was not enough, or her milk not of the right composition] 
(Slavename) lets out a muffled sound as she sees a thin green vine growing within each of the transparent cups. The thin vines press against her [if lactating: lactating] nipples, piercing her swollen mammillae. Her muffeld cry was more in disbelief than pain, her nipples somehow seem to be numb.
[If lactation is >30: She can see no more drops of milk beeing sucked out of her]
[If lactation is >50: Only a few drops of milk flow past the vine]
[If lactation is >70: A very small stream of milk still emerges from her swollen mammillae, passing the vine in her nipple]
Her cry lets in two more vines, joining the others down in her throat. She coughs and still fears of not getting enough air, but she is definitly reacting to the penetration, her loins are wet with girlcum
[if dickgirl: and more and more drops of precuk emerge her raging cock].


Maybe it is something in the moisture covering the tentacles but (slavename) is on the edge of orgasm as her pussy gets stretched by 5 new vines entering her, sliding in between the others. Only very endowed dicks would be as thick as the bunlde of green plantlife sticking in her pussy, slowly moving up and down. 4 vines more are probing around her asshole, forcing their way into her. Her ass is stretched like never before. She moans in wild lust as she is slowly fucked in both holes by what feels like massive dicks


Although she is bit by bit loosing herself to her building climax her eyes widen: Both vines pricking her nipples slowly start to bulge at their base. The bulges, easily tripling the calibre of the vines, slowly ascend towards her breasts. When they finally reach her nipples (slavename) can see new bulges forming at the bases of the vines again. As the first bulge pushes against her nipple she can feel some liquid flowing into her breasts.
[If she had the Count-Be Event3: The feeling is so familiar to the Count's potion she immediately cums to a small orgasm]
[If lactation is <30: The fluid expands her milk-ducts as bulge after bulge unloads its fluids into her breasts]
[If lactation is >30: The fluid flows down her narrow milkducts as bulge after bulge unloads its fluids into her breasts]
[If lactation is >50: The fluid flows down her milkducts, mixing with her milk and pressing it back as bulge after bulge unloads its fluids into her breasts]
[If lactation is >70: The fluid flows down her already milk-filled ducts, pressing her own milk back against the stream of her lactation as bulge after bulge unloads its fluids into her breasts]
The faint, orgasmic pressure building in her drops her jaw in disbelive and lust, which another creeper quickly exploits to plunge down her throat.


The vines in her mouth, ass and pussy are building up their pace, fucking her faster and deeper. The moisture covering them is both lubricating her stretched holes and inciting her raging lust. Her slender flat belly and slim throat are starting to show a bump with each of the deeper and deeper penetrating thrusts. The experience is too much for (slavename): she looses herself in her unearthly lust, riding from one orgasm straight into another. Her breasts look flushed and swollen, the amount of liquid sprayed into them inflating them. She is relieved seeing the vines waiting in front of her mouth to descent towards her hips. She was not sure, if she could breathe if anymore would enter her throat.


Crazy with orgasmic desire she welcomes the 8 new vines shoving inside her pussy, pushing aside the other vines. Combined they are now thick as an arm, stretching her pussy and giving her one high after another. It only takes a little longer until another 8 green intruders have found her way into her ass. (slavename)'s holes are now stuffed with more of them than she could ever imagine to be possible. They pound her with long but deep strokes.


The endless stream of fluid has expanded (slavename)'s tits to nearly twice their original size and...
[If lactation is <30: ...is somehow forcing her mammaries to produce milk! A steady stream...]
[If lactation is >30: ...is somehow forcing her mammaries to produce more and more milk! A thick stream...]
[If lactation is >50: ...is somehow forcing her lactating mammaries into overdrive! A torrent of milk...]
[If lactation is >70: ...is increasing her already conciderable lactation into a massive overdrive. It seems like gallons of milk...]
escapes her pricked nipples and is immediatly sucked up by the cups covering her nipples. With each passing minute more and more milk is produced, pushing against her flesh, expanding her breasts even further.


The pounding of the immense bundles of vines fucking her every, incredibly stretched hole is getting faster and faster. Still some more vines try to squeeze their way past their companions. Some succeed, increasing (slavename)'s already intense orgasms, and some give up. After a particularly fierce minute of high-pace fucking every single vine starts to show a chain of bulges making its way up towards (slavename). All of a sudden the fucking ends with one last stroke, pushing all vines into her body as deep as possible. (slavename) is thourougly fucked, stretched and only half-contious, still she worries about the bulges ascending towards her exhausted body . The first bulges have reached her pussylips, spreading them apart as they enter her fuckhole, a muffled scream escapes her. Every bump passing her asshole stretches it out like the pieces of an anal-bead, she wants to scream again but is betrayed by her body as a new wave of lust araises from her hips. Her jaw is forced open by every bulge entering her throat, she drools even more now.


Finally the bumps have reached the ends of the vines, ejaculating their payload into the helpless body of your slave. It purges deep into her womb, bowels and stomach. All this time her tits are still spraying milk which is greedily sucked away. Maybe it is an aphrodisiac effect of the strange cum or it is the constant stimulation by the endless chain of bulges passing her pussywalls and sphincter, but (slavename)'s body starts to build another orgasm, despite its tiredness. As her lust rises her slim belly starts to bulge itself as more and more cum is pumped into her. The dilation grows constantly with her sexual high until a stream of pussy juice [if dickgirl: and cum] erupt from (slavename) as she looses consciousness, cumming as hard as never before. At that same time her breasts surge a record-amount of milk. The constant ejaculation of the strange plants still continous for several more minutes, inflating her belly to a point she looks...
[if she has no Cow-Girltraining: ...bloated with cum. Finally her body cannot stretch any further and still torrents of slightly green pant-cum escape her holes. 
[If she has Cow-Girltraining at least at level 30: ...six months pregnant. Finally her body cannot stretch any further and stilla stream of slightly green pant-cum escape her holes. ]
[If she has Cow-Girltraining at least at level 50: ...seven months pregnant. But even her trained body cannot stretch any further and so some of the slightly green pant-cum escapes her holes.]
[If she has Cow-Girltraining at least at level 70: ...eight months pregnant. Rising like a dome her trained belly takes all of the plant-cum. It must be gallons worth of the slightly green seed-juice. Even if she was not unconcious, she would be unable to get up now.]


When (slavename) wakes up, she lies on the stone-altar in the middle of the stone-circle. She does not know how much time has passed but there are no vines to be seen around. Looking down at her body she can see milk running freely out of her breasts which are steadily dercreasing in volume, more or less returning to their original,
[if +10% bust-size ample form] 
i[if +25% bust-size full and heavy shape] 
[if +50% bust-size massive size].
Her bloated belly is still flattening as streams of liquid vine-cum flows from her loins with every movement of her loaded body. The altar is covered with a mixture of cum and milk. Dazed, packed-full and with sore holes she gets up and looks around, trying to find her way back.


[if personal supervision: You meet her...]
[if ass. supervision: (assistantsname) meets her...] on a small clearing, after an extended period of shouting and searching. (slavename) is deeply tired and deranged, confused by the horror of the incident and the enormous count of orgasms she had.
Her breasts seem to be different, bigger maybe? And her belly is a bit distended, as if she just ate a whole roast herself. You and your assistand wonder, what happend to her.


Breast Fixation +2, Lactation +5, Nymphomania +3, Lust +2,
Joy -1, refinement -2, intelligence -2, energy -15,


[/SPOILER]
[SPOILER=7]6




Spoiler for Dairy Café Part 1: 
Dairy Café Part 1


You frequently wander the streets together with your slaves and every time you set foot into the city you find something new and interesting that hasn't been here before.
Just today you discovered a pleasant looking little café which is located near the busy main streets but still a bit away in some minor alley.
Tables and chairs are positioned outside the little house, which obviously couldn't handle all the customers.
Nearly every single table was occupied and you hardly find a place to sit down together with (Slave Name).
You try to look up the name of the shop, but all you find is some can used in dairies to store milk, which is openly positioned in front of the entrance. Nothing else in sight seems to be the sign of the café, so you'll just call it Dairy for now, until you get to know it's exact name.


After you waited a while you see why this place is so packed - and why they are mostly male customers.
The waitresses are gorgeous. They all got a nice face, a slim waist, broad hips and long legs. But the thing which is the focus of attention is, that every single one of them has huge breasts, too huge for their frame even.
And their uniform does well in accentuating their breasts.
From now it doesn't take that long for a waitress to show up in front of your table and with a friendly smile hands you the menu.
You're surprised, that everything on it are milk products, quite uncommon for a café, and even for this time of the year, as milk products quickly go bad.


As you don't know what quality their products are you decide for something small, a glass of milk for you and (Slave Name).
You hand back the menu to the waitress and give her your order. "Two glasses of milk it is, then," she said and nods.
You notice her cheeks are a bit flushed as she hurries away to get the things you ordered.


Fortunately it doesn't take long for her to come back with to glasses on her tray, each of them filled to the brim with dazzling white milk.
The waitress looks even more flushed than before as she hands out the glasses, avoiding eye contact and finally hurrying away again.
Wondering you take the glass, even more wondering that it's kind of luke warm.
A bit cautious you sip the milk, tasting if it's gone bad, but to your surprise it's not bad... it's not bad, it tastes quite good.
After finishing up to the last drop you want to pay. While you hand the waitress - the same one as before - the coins she asks you how it'd taste, and you assure her it was really good.
After you said that with a charming smile she quickly hides behind her tray, her cheeks flushing deep crimson and she hurried away faster than before.
You worry a bit about her behavior, but let it slide for the moment.
As it really was good, and despite the many customers also kind of a relaxing break, you decide to come again some time in the future. But still, you keep wondering about the odd behavior of the waitress.
Spoiler for Dairy Café Part 2: 
Dairy Café Part 2


It's another nice and warm day as you decide to wander around with your slave. The busy streets, buzzing with insects in the shape of humans and beings that closely resemble humans. Near the slave pens you even see a cage with some kind of giant bug safely locked away in a evenly giant cage. As (Slave Name) lets out a small shriek you decide to not walk to the docks, but instead deeper into the city's bowels.
And you remember a little shop which is there, the Dairy Café you just recently found.
You decide to head straight there, but as you're not overly familiar with this part of town you get lost, just a little bit - about 2 times.
But still, in the end you manage to find your way to the café and sit down on an emtpy chair on an empty table - again, it seems it's the only available one as this place seems as buzzing with people as the main streets, except all people here are just sitting down, eating and drinking and obviously oggling the waitresse, who don't seem the slightes bothered by it.
You even see one waitress giving a little show, hugging herself, clearly accentuating her breasts and bowing down a little, whispering into a customers ear, who suddenly flushes crimson and avoids further eye contact with her, while the waitress only briefly wears a seductive smile on her face.
As she stands back up, she reverts to her customer friendly smile.
You want to keep watching a bit, but your view gets obstructed by something, something flesh colored.
Just as you wondered a bit, you noticed what it was, it were the huge boobs of the waitress from the last time, standing in front of you, seeming slightly displeased.
Although you don't feel quilty, you still apologize for oggling her college a bit, but it seems, it wasn't the response she waited for, if she even waited for one, because suddenly she got a bit flustered, avoiding eye contact. "Ah, no, it's ok, it..." she stammered a bit with a slightly nervous look in her eyes - still avoiding yours.
Quickly she changes the topic and hands you the menu, which didn't change in the slightest since your last visit.
Exactly as the last time, you order a glass of milk, as you remember, that it was quite good. Also you're not here to satisfy your hunger or anything like that, just to relax a little bit and have a nice time in the city sitting here instead of running around and forcing yourself through all these people who are busy doing things you aren't interested in.
The waitress looks somehow pleased with your order and again you notice a tinge of red on her cheeks as she hurries away trying to bring your order as fast as possible.


After only a short while she comes back to you, on her tray two glasses of milk, with slightly more flushed cheeks and a bit out of breath. You thank her for bringing your order so fast to which she smiles shyly.
Trying to be polite and sound concerned, you ask if she has a cold or something the like, as you notice she doesn't necessarily look that healthy.
The waitress looks slightly shocked but assures you that she's health incarnate.
You mentally shrug and take a sip of your milk, which tastes exactly as you remember - luke warm but good - and notice out of the corner of your eye, that the waitress is watching you closely as you swallow, going a bit redder than before.
Still you can't really explain, why she does that, but at the moment to you it's clear, that she's probably waiting for a tip. Seeing your purse lose another coin kind of makes you sad, but you still manage to act like you completely forgot and give her a tip with a charming smile, to which she goes al flustered again, quickly thanking you and hurrying away.
As you sit there for a while, you get the feeling, you're being stared at from time to time, but you can't make out who or why is staring.
But as nothing happens except the waitress coming sometimes to ask if you need anything else you quickly forget the incident.
After some time, you quietly stand up, pay for your orders and walk away, feeling another stare in your back.
Spoiler for Dairy Café Part 3: 
Dairy Café Part 3


Another day and you're bored, so why don't take a little walk? As you're generous you take (Slave Name) with you to the city to relax a bit and explore.
But as you're starting to feel uncomfortable within the sea of people flooding the streets you decide to go frequent the less populated alleys and remember, that there was this one shop you visited some time ago, with all these big-breasted waitresses.
This time you don't even lost this time around and walk nearly straight to the shop, only stopping for short moments to orientate.


As usual the place is full and as usual it seems you find the last table available and quickly sit down. It doesn't take long for a waitress to appear, although it's not the one who served you the last two times but another one you don't know so far. But she's equally beautiful and also has this huge bosom stuffed in near skin-tight clothes.
She hands you the menu and awaits your orders, which are the same as ever, just two glasses of milk.
As strange as it seemed, the waitress seemed kind of happy with that order, don't edging you on to buy more expensive stuff. With a slightly shy smile she leaves your table.
As you wait you look around a bit and notice some kind of argument at the entrance to the shop.
You see the new waitress as well as the one you encountered before talking to each other, but you can't really hear what about, as they speak in a very low Volume, but nonetheless it seems, they are arguing.
After a bit break off and the the new waitress goes into the shop while the other slumps her shoulders.
It doesn't take that long for your order to arrive after that and you take a sip as usual, tasting the milky flavor.
It's still kind of luke warm and tastes quite good, but it's somehow different than you can remember and you ask about the difference.
"Oh, you can tell?" the waitress asks with a beautiful smile. "Each waitress here serves a bit different milk, let's say it's one of our specials." She winks at you, but you don't really get the meaning.
"If you come the next time, you can ask for a special waitress, if you desire. By the way, my name is Christine."
Again she smiles at you, but this time kind of seductively. "I-I'm Maria!" tells you a voice from behind.
You look around just to see the waitress you encountered the first and second time, who seems kind of fidgety.
"If... if you can, would you please ask for me, the next time, you come here?"
After saying that she quickly turns around and hurries away. You don't really get, what she's up to, but you just mentally shrug and avert your attention from her back to Christine, who has a knowing grin on her face as she watches Maria hurry away.
But she quickly turns away from her and wipes the grin of her face as she quietly cleares her throat.
After you give her her tip and assure her, that you don't need anything else you finish your glass and continue your stroll through the city, this time not only feeling one but two pairs of eyes staring at you.
Spoiler for Dairy Café Part 4: 
Dairy Café Part 4


Again you find yourself walking around with your slave, frequenting several shops, plowing your way through the masses in the streets and again in need of a break.
Fortunately you now can find the way to the nice café with the nice waitresses without getting lost or having to orientate yourself that much.
This time however you seem rather lucky, as there doesn't seem to be much customers today.
Sitting on an empty table you remember the conversation from the last time, where you can even pick your own waitress.
As an of yet unknown waitress comes to your table to give you the menu you think about what to do:


a) Call Maria
b) Call Chrstine
c) Just get a glass of milk


Part 4 a)
You say to the waitress, that she should call Maria, the one you talked with some time ago.
The unknown waitress seems to be a bit disappointed, but quickly leaves to call her college.
And it doesn't even take long before Maria comes out of the shop, obviously hurrying to get to your table.
As she came closer to your table she somehow managed to stumble on something. Just before she falls to the ground you instinctively jump up and capture her in your arms.
While you're holding Maria, she however seems to be spaced out, looking up to your face, a dreamy look in her eyes.
It does take her a few seconds to gather her thoughts. Then she flies out of your arms, hurriedly standing up.
"T-Thank you" she tells you as her cheeks flush bright red.
It takes a while for the atmosphere to return from akward to normal, but still you managed to order two glasses of Maria's milk which she brought you in the twinkle of an eye.
You slowly drink the liquid while noticing something strange. Somehow it seems a bit warmer than usual... and you don't know why, but your cheeks seem kind of warm, like you're drunk.
You ask Maria if she put something into your drink but she assures you that nothing she did nothing suchlike - but still she blushed furiously as you asked.
After finishing everything you try to set forth but Maria stops you for a bit.
"If... If you come the next time, I-I want you to come inside the shop."
Feeling a little drunk you easily agree to that and finally walk away.




Part 4 b)
You say to the waitress, that she should call Christine, the one you met the last time.
The unknown waitress seems to be a bit disappointed, but quickly leaves to call her college.
And it doesn't take that long for Christine to come out of the shop, a beautiful smile on her face.
She quickly takes your order - the same as ever - and brings you your glasses of milk handing them out to you and (Slave Name).
After that she looks around a bit, observing the other customers before she decides, that she won't be needed there, and sits down on an empty chair at your table.
"Is it tasty?" she asks, as you sip on your glass, to which you give a small nod. "That really makes me happy. But I never thought you'd call for me. Wouldn't you rather call Maria?"
"Why?" you ask her. "Well, she likes you, you know? And she's cute."
You tell her, that it's flattering to hear to be liked by someone, but that doesn't necessarily mean you like her the same. And Christine seems as cute - to which she blushed a little.
Afterwards you change the topic a bit and discuss rather insignificant things with Christine until you finished and decided to leave again.
"The next time you come," she starts talking, "will you come inside the shop?"
You ask her if it's special to come inside. You think that it's normally packed in there.
"Oh, the inside is for invited guests only, so there're many empty seats. And I would like to show you something nice." She smiles at you seductively.
As you don't have a special reason to deny her, you ensure her, you'll be there the next time you come.




Part 4 c)
You have no particula desire to speak to one of the waitresses you know and you just want to relax a bit so you just order the typical glass of milk - it seems you got hooked on it - to which the waitress blushes a little.
It seems, that ordering milk is something special here but for now you try to ignore it.
After some time relaxing you finish everything, give the waitress a little tip and finally walk away, into the masses on the buzzing street.
(4c loops back to 4, so that you get the choices again)
Spoiler for Dairy Café Part 5 a): 
Dairy Café Part 5 a)


It wasn't that long ago that Maria invited you - and probably (Slave Name) too - to visit the café again, she even asked you to come inside, although you don't see a reason why it should be that special. It's just a café, why would you even need an invitation to enter?
As you thought that you enter the building, only to bump against something hard. You look up and suddenly feel small.
The thing you bumped into turned out to be a huge man, towering more than 2 meters. On his head you can make out bull-like horns sticking out. His body is covered in short black fur and his feet end in hoofs while a tail swishes around angrily.
"What are you doing in here?" he askes with a deep voice dripping with anger. You know, you definitely couldn't win against that monster even if you'd attend to fight it so you quickly think about what to do.
Either you turn around and flee immediately or you try to talk to the man - it's no wonder you forgot about the invitation for a moment.
"Get out or do you want me to break your bones, puny one?" The bull-man now speaks with hostility as you cracks his knuckles. In that moment you realize, talk would probably solve nothing and you try to turn around as fast as possible while avoiding doing anything he would see as aggressive.
Just as you turned around you hear the well-known voice of Maria. "Dad! Stop that! I Invited him*!"
"Oh?" the muscle man only raised an eyebrow while folding his arms and just being intimidating. "So Maria invited you?"
"Ah, yes" you nearly stammer while he stares at you. If his stares were physical they would probably rend you to shreds.
But after you state again that you've been invited the bull-man smiles and steps to the side. "If that's so you're welcome here. Oh, and my name's Minos, little one, what's yours?" You tell him.
You jerk a bit as one of his big hands lands on you shoulders, even though he doesn't use force. "Come on in!" His voice no sounds friendly and his hand shoves you in the house.
After you went to the middle of the room he turns his back towards you again guarding the entrance.
You look around a bit and see something similiar to a living room instead of the interior of a café. "It seems it's the first time you've been here," a female voice calls out to you.
As you look around you see a woman, who's probably in her late thirties and apparently highly pregnant. The voice belongs to her. And behind her you see Maria, who seems to hide behind the woman and looking at you a bit embarrassed.
"Then I welcome you in the name of our small family. And now, excuse me, I have to do some milking. Oh my back."
You see her walk away slowly, seeming a little bit in pain.
"Ah, t-that's my mother," Maria quickly tells you.
Being a bit overwhelmed by those new facts you try to just get them into your brain as fast as possible and change the topic. You ask Maria why she would invite you - and (Slave Name) - into their house.
"I-I want to show you something. It's a bit embarrasing, but I still want you to know. Could you please follow me?"
After saying that she quickly walks away, deeper into the house. With no other choice left you and your slave follow behind her.
You enter one small room, only big enough for a bed as well as a small table and a chair. On the table you see an empty glass.
Maria stands beside the table and shows you to sit down on the chair, which you do.
"W-Well, you know," she starts fidgeting a bit, "you told me, the milk I serve tastes good, and you even asked for it the other day, and... and I want to... to drink more of it." She somehow get's embarrassed and starts fidgeting more - and you don't even know why exactly. You ask yourself, just why she took you to this room; at least if she didn't intend on doing something indecent.
Maria closes her eyes and breathes in and out a few times before she continues. "P-Please, watch me."
After she says that she takes the glass from the table and guides it to her breasts. She takes of a button of her blouse and her big bosom falls out of her clothes. She then puts the free hand on one of her breasts and puts the glass to her slightly longer nipple, which rapidly gets hard. Kneading the flesh a bit and lastly tugging on her nipple she lets out a pleasured sigh while milk suddenly shoots out of her breast, flowing into the glass until it's filled to the brim.
After she finished she breathes heavily, her face bright red and the rest of her skin also slightly flushed.
She looks a bit dreamy at you as she carefully puts the glass back on the table.
It takes her a few seconds to come back down to earth and as she does she flushes even more than before, quickly buttoning up her blouse again and walks to the door - more like fleeing.
"Th-That's all for t-today." After stammering that she runs away, hastily closing the door and leaving you alone with (Slave Name) and one glass of milk on the table.
You wait for a while but Maria doesn't come back, so you reason she won't come back at all.
As you get bored waiting you decide to talk to (Slave Name) as you notice, she's kind of fidgety herself, often looking at the glass.
You just thought about the training your slaves doing right now and thought about something good. If you come here again you may get some information regarding her training... and Maria also said "that's all for today", probably meaning there's more to come in the future.
Wanting to tease your slave a bit you suddenly take the glass and empty it in big gulps, hearing (Slave Name) gasp a little.
Well, you drinked it three times now, so it doesn't hurt drinking it again, even knowing what it is. Still, you seem to get sligthly drunk from it.
You hope it doesn't indicate you're getting sick.


*needs distinction if male or female.
Spoiler for Dairy Café Part 5 b): 
Dairy Café Part 5 b)


It's another day plagued by accute boredom while training your slave - it's probably not that boring for (Slave Name), but you get easily bored these days as you keep repeating the same things again and again for every slave.
So you decide to take a little break and remember the little café you went to recently.
Quickly you find your way there and see that it's packed as usual, this time not even a single table free for you to use. As you try to turn around to walk away you see someone walking up to you, and it turned out to be Christine.
"Why do you try to leave again? You're alway welcome here. Oh and as I said, you can just go inside, I already told that you can enter. Just wait a bit, I'll try to be there as fast as I can."
After saying that she quickly leaves again to serve the customers. You on the other hand take what you're offered and enter the house, which is unexpectedly dark inside, so you can't really see anything from the outside and the first moments inside you can't see anything at all.
After a short moment you also notice exactly why you can't see anything except black... a huge bull-man stand in front of you, glaring down at you and it seems he won't budge at all.
You feel a bit intimidated but still manage to speak to that man-monster. "Excuse me, but I've been invited into, so could you please... make way?"
Unfortunately he keeps staring you down without saying as much as a word, but unexpectedly he makes way after he had stared enough. "You better wait here for the one who invited you," he finally says to you in a deep bass voice.


Luckily it doesn't take that long for Christine to arrive. "You didn't do anything to my guest, did you, Dad?" she immediately says to the towering giant. "No dear, I didn't do anything unusual."
She didn't seem that pleased with the answer but let it slide. "Please follow me" she tells you. Of course you don't have anything against that, as it brings you away from the giant.
While following Christine you briefly see a highly pregnant woman, probably in her late thirties. "That's Marie, one of dad's wifes, and Marias mother," she introduces her curtly. "Oh, by the way, he got three wives and six daughters, just before you ask, and yes, he's a bull-man... as if it wasn't obvious. And that leads me to something I want to show you."
As she said that she opens the door to a room which is only big enough to fit a bed, a table and a chair. On the table stands one emtpy glass.
Christine tells you to sit on the chair while your slave unfortunately has to remain standing.
Quietly she closes the door, and turning back to you she wears a smile you can't really interpret. It's somehow between shy and seductive. Quietly, slowly and showy she unbuttons her blouse, giving way for her huge breasts.
"You see," she starts talking, "I kind of like you, so I want to show you something really interesting." She massages her breasts, rubbing the flesh and sometimes tweaking her nipples. Her body flushes slightly red and she lets out quiet moans as she seems to pleasure herself.
"They feel really good, especially when they're full and you need to release." Your stares fixed on her breast you are getting a bit confused, but that quickly abates as she takes the glass and puts it to her breast. Strongly she tugs at one of her nipple letting out a pleasured moan together with a white stream shooting from her breast - milk.
She doesn't stop until the glass is filled to the brim, panting heavily at the end.
"Here's your glass of fresh milk." She hands you the glass with a smile as you sit there dumbstruck. "I have to admit, it feels really good, if you're being watched." After a short pause: "And I would really like to... continue, but unfortunately I don't have that much time today. So... would you please come again when there's not that much patronage outside? Of course you can remain here for a while, but I can't accompany you any more..." The next sentence she whispers directly into your ear with an especially seductive voice: "And that milk is especially made for you."
After that she quietly leaves the room, her cheeks a bit flushed.
As you wonder if you should drink or not you notice (Slave Name) being a bit fidgety and you look at her. She has her hands on her breast, slightly massaging them, appearing to be spaced out a bit. As you speak to her she gets all flustered and quickly hides her hand behind her back.
In this moment you decide to drink the milk in big gulps, observing your slave closely and noticing her cheeks get bright red as she looks at you drinking the white fluid.
After that you set the empty glass down on the table and head out - while hiding the grin on your face.
This could prove useful not only for your fun and entertainment but can even bring something new to your training.
Spoiler for Dairy Café Part 6 a): 
Dairy Café Part 6 a)


You feel strangely restless lately and your thoughts wander from your original goal, the slave training. They seem to wander to one specific location. Not the auction houses to buy slaves but another part of town. A small house, hidden in one of the small streets.
That is also the location you wander to right now, your slave on your coat-tails.
You deliberately ignore all the customers sitting on their chairs and leering at the waitresses in their outfits. You enter through the dark doorway as if it was normal - except you rammed head on into a wall, again.
"What do you want?" the deep voice bellows from above.
Rubbing your hurting nose you tell the giant bull-man that you've just been here recently and are here right now again to see Maria.
After looking at you a bit suspiciously he lets you pass. "She's behaving rather odd lately, you should probably be a bit wary." Shrugging your shoulders you pass the giant without another glance.
Recently you've got this strange longing for Maria, and it gets stronger as you're here in her house.
You don't know, where you should start searching for her or if she even is here at all. You can't be sure.
But not knowing where to go, you head to the room you were in the last time you came here.
Your feet move faster and faster the more you approach the small room at the end of the corridor.
Slightly short of breath you stand in front of the wooden door and slowly - nearly fearful - open it.
The next moment you feel something falling against you, giving you a strong hug. Loose hair obstructs your vision for a short while as you feel Marias warmth soaking your body.
"I was waiting for you", she says while still having her face burried in your chest. Your heart beating faster than before you stroke her head and softly tell her, you wanted to see her, too.
You gently push Maria in the room and close the door - (Slave Name) just rushed in before she got locked out, as you seem to have completely forgotten about her the moment you saw Maria again.
Together with Maria you sit down on the simple bed, which makes a low creaking sound.
"I really..." Maria began, but you put just put your finger on her mouth and she stopped.
But it didn't stay there, but instead slowly crept down her chin, her throat, onto her collarbone and slid insider her collar, just resting above her huge breasts. You feel her body heat even more than before and it feels warmer than you expected, almost as if to burn you.
A low moan escaped Marias throat as she felt your - for her - cold fingers on her hot skin.
With your other hand you slowly unbutton her blouse and after that's done you slowly peel her out of it.
Her breasts being freed fall out of her clothes while she trembles because of the cold air grazing her skin.
Finally your hand resolves it's way down her body, feeling up her mound.
Her breath grows hotter as she tries to feel your hand with her breast, slightly pressing against you.
Even though they're bigger than most you've seen, they are really firm.
Avoiding her nipple you slide your hand over the entirety of her breast, even slightly stroking the underside and slightly lifting it to feel its weight in your hand.
Again you're surprised as her breasts are heavy, much heavier than you expected.
As if reading your thoughts Maria whispers in your ear "I need to be milked" with a clearly seductive voice and it's not difficult to imagine, what she wants you to do.
Again you let your cold finger creep across her skin, up to the very top of her mound, which eagerly awaits your touch, standing already fully erect.
You feel like teasing her a bit and just lightly rub the nipple with your thumb to which you feel Marias body tremble and her throat escapes another moan. With pleading eyes, filled with desire, she looks at you.
Like that being the starting signal you suddenly tug at her nipple, to which she lets out a small yell and a squirt of milk flies from her breast.
With that one motion her breath grew even hotter and it seems her normal shyness disappeared. She clearly pleads for more, being milked harder. As you in order to meet her wishes start taging harder she lets out loud moans of pleasure, seemingly close to pure bliss.
Even you yourself start to feel pleasure milking her, like your hand is being satisfied just by touching her skin.
It doesn't take long for her to soak both of you in her milk, but both of you just ignore the fact and continue with the milking.
In fact somewhere along the line - you can't even remember when - you started drinking the milk, directly from the source, hightening her pleasure even more as well as your own.
You feel your body temperature rising and your desire growing even further. All you can think about is Maria, Maria and Maria, everything else being completely swept out of your brain.
And everything goes black.
You have blacked out, but not just you, Maria also suddenly lost consciousness, while (Slave Name) stays awake, feeling oddly aroused, trying to stop herself from rubbing her own breasts.
A giant black shadow falls on her as she looks at the two lying there, breathing hard with flushed skin.
"Hmm... somehow it was to be expected."
The deep voice sounds even more intimidating in this small room.
"You better keep your friend from coming here again, it seems neither of them can handle it."
(Slave Name) just looks at him, questioning him with her eyes.
"Maria is a bit special... ever heard that milk of happy cows tastes better? Well, that's a bit rasistic, but it precisely describes what Maria's milk can do. She can transmit her feeling through her milk... normally it's not bad, it even makes for more customers, but it seems, Maria got some mighty crush on your friend here.
Didn't he/she* mention Maria a bit more often these days? Well, probably. The more he/she* drinks of her milk, the more he/she* falls in love with her... well, somewhere it should stop along the line, but it seems that her own milk is influencing herself. She has a crush on your friend and that transfers to her milk... and than her milk hightens her own crush. It's a vicious circle of longing.
If we keep them alone they'll probably do nothing else anymore than ... having each other. If it get's worse, they go at it until they die of exhaustion. Not something I wish for my daughter. Well, she might be happy with it, but I don't think I would be happy with it. Or would you like to lose your friend like that?"
After that speech he walks to your body and effortless lifts you up. "Rather light" is his only comment while he carries you out of the room, careful not to bump you or himself against anything - which is not that easy considering is height.


Dairy Café Part 6 b)


You head to the city and take (Slave Name) with you. Of course your goal has something to do with training your slave.
So you head towards the little café in the middle of the city. Luckily there aren't much customers outside so you are one step closer to your goal. Now you just have to find Christine; but that isn't hard to do, as you clearly see her walking around handling customers together with Maria and some other girl.
As Maria sees you she shoots you a nervous glance, but you only give her a small nod and walk up to Christine.
Before she can actually say something to you you bring your face near hers and whisper to her, if she got time today.
It seems she didn't quite expected such a forward question as you see her blush deeply.
But still, she nods back without hesitation, giving you her unique smile.
You say to her, you'll wait for her and after that enter the house, dragging (Slave Name) behind you.
Learning from your past experience though you don't walk head first into the doorway, as there's standing the usual wall of muscle and fur to deny entry to anything unwelcomed.
This time you didn't crash against his chest, to which the giant clicks his tongue in unpleasantness, but still obediently steps out of the way.
You vaguely remember where to go and therefor it doesn't take you long to find the room you've been in the last time.
The inventory is the same as the last time, except that there's no glass on the desk this time.
You order (Slave Name) to sit on the chair and face the bed, wheras you sit down on said bed and look alternating to your slave and the door, thinking about the things you'll do.
It doesn't take that long for Christine to appear. She looks flushed, but not like she rushed here.
As she steps through the door you order her to sit next to you on the bed, which she does without complaint.
If it's okay to have a little fun today, you ask her. She gives you a small nod, but then looks a bit worried at (Slave Name). "Shouldn't she wait outside?" she asks you. You ask her if it really matters, especially after she said last time, that she feels better being watched.
Christines cheeks flush a bit more than before, but she remains silent, not denying it, so you take it she approves of it.
As there is nothing hindering you from some fun now, you sit behind her and whisper into her ear she should just relax and you'll be having some fun together.
She seems to be a bit nervous, but does not show any kind of resistance as you unbutton her blouse from behind, presenting her large breasts to the air.
You put your hands beneatch the mound of flesh and push it up, weighing its heaviness in your hand and feeling her body heat, which went up a little.
She doesn't seem uncomfortable, just a bit shy, and looks kind of worried towards your slave. But that worry does not last long, as your hands crawl over her breasts, softly kneading the flesh. You trace your finger around her areola and feel her body shake a bit.
A soft near inaudible moan escapes her lips, but it's filled with a bit of distress, as it arouses her slightly, but thats all.
But you still continue, to only lightly carress her breasts, making sure to show her breasts to your slave.
As you kiss Christines neck, you start putting more force in your hands, which is greeted with a audible and pleasure filled moan. As you tuck her nipple a bit, you can feel a slight wetness as her milk slowly wells up from them.
You tell her, she got some wonderfull tits there as you continue to fondle and knead them. (Slave name) seems to enjoy the show, because you can see her groping her own breats, trying to feel the same pleasure as Christine.
You take one hand of from her breasts and turn her head sideways.
It doesn't take her long to realize what your intentions are and she willingly turns her head as you take your hand back to fondle her breast.
She sticks out her tongue, to taste yours, and you quickly follow, kissing her, sucking on her tongue and playing with her insides all the way while putting more strength in your hand.
More and more milk gushes forth as her bosom changes form under your caressing. Your partner seems to have forgotten every worry in the world, only seeking pleasure from your tongue and your hands, as she pushes her head towards yours and rubs her breasts against your hand, if they ever stop.
You can feel her body heat and see her skin glisten erotically with sweat, whereas her breasts get wetter and wetter with her milk. It seems even though you only play with her breasts she nears a heavy orgasm. You could be either mean and stop just there or take it to the finish.
Even while still considering the option to just stop and tease her immensly you forcefully tug on her nipples.
A loud moan escapes Christines lips, as her entire body trembles from one enormous orgasm. A strong squirt of milks shoots out of her breasts and lands on your moaning slave. Because of this unexpected event (Slave Name) lets out a small shriek as the milk lands on her face, but that just seems to take her to the edge as she comes lightly.


Unfortunately Christine just passed out from her orgasm, just when your own body got kind of hot. Maybe her breasts were a bit too sensitive?
(Slave name) instead is leaning a bit powerless against the wall, panting heavily.
You think about letting of some steam with her, so you write a quick note and leave it on the table.
Maybe you'll come again some time to have some more fun, but you have to go now, so you can't look at her sleeping face after passing out.


Spoiler for Dairy Café Part 7 a): 
Dairy Café Part 7 a)


You feel kind of sluggish as you wander around town. You can't seem to remember why that's the case, nor can you remember what you even did, the last time you came here; just some time ago you woke up in your bed with one hell of an headache and a small case of amnesia - at least, that's what (Slave Name) told you.
Your feet seem to head towards one specific location, but as soon as you try to set foot in one of the smaller streets your slave forcefully tears you away from it and drags you toward the mass of people buzzing around like bees in am hive.
You let out a sigh, some word mixed with it you don't even recognice.
(Slave Name) on the other hand hears the small "Maria" escaping your mouth and starts remembering what happend... trying to resist the urge to rub her breasts.




My cowgirl approach would be a café run by cowgirls who are more or less proud of their body, showing of, but still trying to keep their origin secret... as it's maybe kind of shameful to admit.
Gradually showing the advantages of their training and feeling content, privately even proud of it.
At least, that's the idea. Unfortunately (or luckily?) mostly focusing on Cowgirl - Slavemaker interaction, while your slave watches.


Part 1 is more or less just the introduction. Hope I can dish the rest out fast 
And I hope, it's acceptable for the universe Slave Maker is set into.


Edit: Also going with a love approach as one of the waitresses is interested in the Slaver (regardless of gender).


Edit: Storyline keeps growing as I type it... still don't know how many parts I will end up with 


Edit: After long time i finished Part 6 b) with an open end. The entire text file as an attachment is... well... attached to this post.


Spoiler for How the story goes on ... probably (for those who're interested): 
Maria:
Here I go with something like "Happy milk from happy cows", where Maria has the special ability to transfer feelings through milk... as she's in love - or more like being obsessed - with the main character, it doesn't bode so well, as the main gets more obsessed with her the more he drinks her milk... in the end it has to be broken apart kind of forcefully.
Well, it's probably not what everyone likes, and I didn't plan for it, it's just the way the story grew.


Christine:
More a rational approach than the over emotional path of Maria. Here it would be more like an interactive lesson n cowgirls or something like that... did not yet flesh it out. (well, she wasn't even planned in the beginning...)
Also... I definitely need someone to look ower the texts to find spelling errors, bad grammar or words that sound weird / don't make that much sense... I'm not a native speaker, so it could be messed up somwhere, even so I try to prevent that.


Edit: Part 6 a) is up now! That was some heavy work, rewriting that event 2 times... Well, only one repeatable part for Marias story... and something for Christines story... well, there's enough time, no need to rush.






1. Originally Posted by Lsar 
5) About the count-event: is it only once per slavemaker? If so: the option to do business with him could include an option to betray him to the lord so you can take over with fairer treatment. It could also generate a small income from that time? Maybe the Lord can give you a penalty for having done business with the count in the first place? (to counter the advantages).
I completely support anything that allows me to screw things up for that jerk.


Scythless, I like your ideas. It would be great if there were some way to counteract the addictiveness of Maria's milk and hire her as a servant in your house. -1 slave fatigue per day due to an abundant supply of refreshing milk? 
[/SPOILER]
[SPOILER=8]7
Incidentally, I wrote this from what my perspective of "being a cowgirl" means. In my mind, the attraction to it is a certain degree of mindlessness...you are there to be milked, plain and simple. Your only real pleasure is to be milked. Sex is nice and all, but the main pleasure a cowgirl gets is to be able to lose herself, and become a vacant, happy cow. If that's not your vision, I apologize for being derivative, and would be more than willing to rewrite this to suit your idea.
Spoiler for Low Class Party, Cowgirl Event: 


Serve as a Maid, Outside
(This scene replaces Catgirl scene, as Cowgirls cannot be catgirls. Maybe.)


(SlaveName) sees a couple of maids quietly leaving the party, and heading outside. Curious, she follows them to a large shed in the backyard. Some gentleman are lingering outside casually, so (SlaveName) assumes this to be a quieter, less publicized area of the party. The gentlemen look her over speculatively as she enters the shed.


Inside, (SlaveName) is surprised to see a beautiful young woman with enormous breasts being roughly fucked on the floor of the shed. A small group of noblemen watch on with obvious interest…probably waiting their turn…while attractive maids tend to their cocks dutifully. When (SlaveName) takes a closer look, she realizes with some surprise that the woman who is the center of all this attention is a cowgirl! The man on top of her is fucking her with long, rough strokes, his erect cock pistoning in the girl’s well-used hole with wet slaps. The cowgirl’s massive udders flop uncontrollably as the treatment intensifies, small streams of milk leaking from her erect teats. She is letting out low moans that sound more like moos than anything else.






(Cowgirl levels low)
One unattended nobleman notices (SlaveName) and gestures her over, unceremoniously dropping his trousers and telling her to start sucking his cock. (SlaveName) does so, with some skill, but the nobleman orders her to go more slowly, and not to make him cum. The reason why is soon apparent, as the man fucking the cowgirl lets out a low grunt, pushes deep into her pussy, and begins squirting his seed deep inside her with thick squelches. The cowgirl moans and moos throughout it all, making no actually human noises, tears running down her face. Once the nobleman is finished, he pulls out, wiping his cum-stained cock on the cowgirl’s flesh and stepping back, only to be replaced by another nobleman soon after. Then the fucking begins again, as it has been all night.


(SlaveName) attends many men that evening, but all of them insist on cumming only in the cowgirl’s flooded cunt. They seem to enjoy her general distress and discomfort, eyeing her bloated breasts with great pleasure. Once or twice one of them fucks her ass instead, but usually pulls out long enough to spray his load over her pussy.


(SlaveName) can see that the cowgirl enjoys the physical sensations greatly, and even orgasms several times, but seems distinctly unhappy for some reason. By the end of the night, she is covered in semen and her own breastmilk, a sad look on her face. (SlaveName) hesitates, wanting to comfort the girl, but doesn’t know what to say.






(Cowgirl Apotheosis/Acceptance)
One unattended nobleman notices (SlaveName) and gestures her over, unceremoniously dropping his trousers and telling her to start sucking his cock. (SlaveName) does so, with some skill, but the nobleman orders her to go more slowly, and not to make him cum. The reason why is soon apparent, as the man fucking the cowgirl lets out a low grunt, pushes deep into her pussy, and begins squirting his seed deep inside her with thick squelches. The cowgirl moans and moos throughout it all, making no actually human noises, tears running down her face. Once the nobleman is finished, he pulls out, wiping his cum-stained cock on the cowgirl’s flesh and stepping back, only to be replaced by another nobleman soon after. Then the fucking begins again, as it has been all night.


(SlaveName) spends the night sucking nobleman cock, urging their erections and lust until they cannot stand it any longer, but she her real attention is always on the cowgirl. Tears run down the cowgirl’s face as she is fucked again and again, despite the fact that she orgasms many times from the sensations. As (SlaveName) stares at the cowgirl’s swollen mammaries, she suddenly realizes the problem. None of the nobleman, entranced though they may be by the sight of the cowgirl’s breasts, are actually milking her!


(SlaveName) feels a moment of outrage that surprises her. It is cruel give the poor cowgirl so much pleasure, but deny her the greastest satisfaction of being milked! Afterall, a cowgirl’s only true happiness is in being milked, in having her breasts suckled, in feeling that wonderful release of milk…(SlaveName) looks down at her own breasts, proudly, and realizes that she now and forever considers herself a true Cowgirl!


Afterwards, as the noblemen begin to finish and dwindle slightly, (SlaveName) approaches the abused cowgirl, who is mooing unhappily on the ground, cunt leaking a steady stream of cum. (SlaveName) moos quietly, soothingly to her fellow cowgirl, and takes one engorged nipple into her mouth, suckling gently. The cowgirl looks up at her, relief and affection in her eyes. (SlaveName) nurses happily, savoring the taste of milk and happily dreaming of her life as a cow.






(High Levels of Cowgirl)
Offended by the treatment of this poor cowgirl, (SlaveName) goes over and mercifully starts suckling at the cowgirl’s engorged breast. Instantly, she is rewarded with a surprised and happy moo, as well as a thick stream of sweet milk. Her own arrousal flaring at the wonderful taste, (SlaveName) begins fondling her own breasts with her free hand, and raises her ass high in the air towards the crowd of noblemen. Excited by this new development, it is not long before a large cock is thrust into (SlaveName)’s moist pussy, and she moos in a low moan to show her pleasure. Some kind hands unbutton her blouse, and it is not long after that (SlaveName) is tugging eagerly at her own engorged teats, spraying streams of milk onto the floor. Some of the noblemen start to catch on, and one begins suckling at (SlaveName)’s nipple, drinking down her milk with vigor.


(SlaveName) is in heaven, her world reduced to little more than a steady stream of cocks and milking. She drinks heavenly milk from the other cowgirl until her stomach feels like it will burst, only pausing long enough to suck some excited nobleman’s spunk down before returning to sweet milk. Her pussy and ass are fucked, over and over, filling her to the brim with warm cum, until it runs down her legs in little rivers. And, best of all, the wondrous pressure of her breasts being relieved into hungry mouths, her milk drunk down like ambrosia. Her mind blanks, her eyes become vacant, and all she can think about is how happy she is to be a cowgirl as she cums again, and again, and again…


Eventually the noblemen tire, and the crowd begins to thin. (SlaveName) hardly notices, content to simply enjoy the wonderful fullness and the mindless joy of being a cow. Sometime later, Miss N comes to collect her and take her home, asking if she had fun this evening. In answer, (SlaveName) simply moos happily, rubbing her breasts and stomach with obvious pleasure.


[/SPOILER]
[SPOILER=9]8
- Cats like milk. I suppose that actually, for technical reasons, Cowgirl and Catgirl trainings are not compatible, but I thought about some specials events for a cowgirl involving catgirls
Spoiler for Some ideas: 


- Step 1: catgirl meetings may result in a yes/no choice where catgirls want to drink some milk during "take a walk" action
- Step 2: catgirl visit as an end of day event where catgirls want to buy some milk
- Step 3: as the milk is kind of potent and addictive a massive attack of catgirls kidnapping your cow
- Step 4: cowgirl rescue in the forest (with the help of the forest guardians and/ or the "good doogy" pet?) Option A: A truce: agree to send them milk (lower the money earned) or war
- Step 5: the Count try to prevent milk delivery with the hope of total war (false catgirl attack on the way, if you don't investigate it will trigger war because with no delivery you break your pledge, same thing if you think that it's a true catgirl attack. Possible clues: footprints in the forest leading to the farm, rumors at the Court, farm spying, tailor visit (made catgirls suits for the count), seduciing a count slave




An idea for gaining the skill
Spoiler for Skill: 


- At the court or during a Count lending you hear a rumor about a Cont cowgirl which is on the loose
- You can found her in the slums she needs some cure
- Astrid told you what kind of ingredients you need (forest for herbs, drug dealer for some ingredients etc), this task is eaier if your slaver has Alchemy
- Now you can visit her and gain the skill
- What can go wrong with the visit: You and/or your slave have to taste the milk. You can forget that you have come here (no skill gain) and have a big breast milk explosion during the night . For a rapid teaching, keep your Lust low (there's drugs for this even for slavemakers)


[/SPOILER]
[SPOILER=10]9


I have some suggestions regarding BE & the milkiing.


After each BE event there's a chance that the slaves clothes bursts in the seams dependent on how much bigger the boobs got in the event. This effectively destroys the clothes the slave are wearing and you need to buy new ones. Maybe add a morning event first where the slavemaker/assistant notices that the slaves clothes looks awfully tight as a hint.
To stop this from happening you have to visit the tailor and get the old clothes re-sewn to her new size, the cost ~15-20% of original price.


If the her clothes tear while she is out walking there should be a loss of renown for the slavemaker, the slave gets a boost in reputation but a decrease in refinement. Maybe the chance for the clothes to tear could be based on what activities the slave is doing.


Another thing I have been thinking about: pierced nipples and a milking machine?! Does that really work well? How about as long as the slave has piercings in her nipples the milking gives a low yield and you get an option to remove them to increase the yield.


A third thing was that if the slave is pumped full of drugs to get her breasts to increase in size, what does that do the milk?
Spoiler for Events affecting the SM: 
There is an event from one of the other slaves you can milk where you sample the product and if you are a male you become a woman/herm if you sample to many times.


What if the milk contains traces of the drug and the slavemaker serves it to the rest of the household? I would guess general mayhem since the drug can have some interesting sideeffects:
Spoiler for Drugged milk event: 


1. Since the start of the first milking event only your slaves milk are served at breakfast.
2. This milk makes everyone very horny, and nipples that are stiff and all crinkled up are especially sensitive when rubbing against cloth.
3. They cant stop massaging their breasts because of how good it feels
4. Their breasts increase one cup-size and starts dribbling milk
5. They help each other out of their milk soaked clothes
6. Much licking, sucking and milkdrinking ensues for a while.
7. IF unhibitory drugs have been used the night before: mixed drugs in the milk makes everyone who drinks it to increase in cup-size again and produce milk that are extremely addictive before the drug dissolves. People only need to smell it to feel a craving for it. This leads to everyone in the household is fucking, sucking, milking, licking and cumming for the rest of the day.
8. When the event finishes all breasts return to their previous size.


You can even expand on the event so that the whole town is affected and you loose renown because of it.




Spoiler for Event 1: 


- a general note, ideally text should vary if the slave is naked
eg "This is a very beautiful dress, my dear!"
would be removed if she is naked for the day.


- If slave is Kasumi: She already dislikes her busty figure.
Also please consider variations for Tifa
Also Yurika is very susceptible to drugs, so some unusual reaction for her


First of all I want to play with her new breast for the rest of the day,
- It is currently awkward in the game to reschedule and make the 2 hour visit last for the rest of the day. It is possible, but the text does not seem to indicate a long encounter. Either something to indicate much longer time passing or limit it back to the two hours and remove the reference


- You refer to the potion as 'mythical' I think legendary is a better term.


She lowers herself on her knees and starts to skill-fully lick the contents of your pants.
- This would sound a little awkward for a female slave makers


- Did you have any suggested graphics, particularly for the large breasted slaves. I can easily create a combined image, depending on art style. Otherwise the Counts image can be in the small person window and the slaves in the large?


- You put in a next button. The game allows unlimited lenght text so it is unnecessary, unless you want a different image shown.


- What are the stat & breast effects for the Yes path (you give them for no)


Spoiler for Event 2: 


- If you refuse event 1 nothing special?


Spoiler for Event 3: 


He used only one quart of a vial for both of us together.
quart? quarter I assume


Gulps of cum run down her cock.
Gulps sounds wrong, Globs maybe


Stat effects
Charisma +10; Lust -10; Nymphomania +10; Fucking +2; Obedience +5; Temperament -5 


Ok, but obedience should not really rise, or less, is she more obedient to you now? Increase her constitution a bit to reflect the physical exercise and effort involved.


[/SPOILER]
[SPOILER=11]10
the only thing I though about is "Got Milk ?"
(and the silly idea of disappearing persons portraits on the good milk company milk bricks... poor Count )


maybe the science course should take into account the Snow Club... future milk-addicted cows ???
it can be intertwined with BE chain of events(should be), or it can be as default slave->BE at least all of counts events-> new npc that we meet somewhere and takes interest i our slave bust size


also if we start our own Milk Co. it can be made that considering our (SM) outlook we aply different means for ex. as followers of the old gods are uninhibitted but hate restrains they would be followin the natural flow of things and won't be using milking machinesand prefer handywork(quantity of milk will be less, but quality better and slaves would enjoy it more) we would get less money at first couse it would require skilled "milkers" new gods followers would be more practical and progressive in the matter (creatig a comfortable milking device) and those of no gods will have to choose


[/SPOILER]
[SPOILER=12]11
4. If you want,cmac, i can write an event where you can meet the vigilantes again. this way, the pictures could alternate. Or i can just write two versions of the same first vigilante-ambush
If there is a band of bandits in the forest it it reasonable there can be more meetings. Some possibilities
- if you cannot pay then they require sexual favours
- if you run it could lead to the Deep Forest, a very wild and unvisited place
a) in Rei's training it is there the Spider/Fish Men can take you
b) the elven and dark elven kingdoms will have outposts
- negotiate with them for favours
a) have them chase off the fairy hunter
b) help to explore the ruins
c) attack a pirate ship to rescue some slaves taken in a raid
and lots more potentially




[/SPOILER]
[SPOILER=13]12
2. Also, i want to add a few lines to the regular "lend her to the count"-event, due to the fact that he "invested" an expensive potion in her. But I am a bit low on ideas on this one
I suggest
a) if you do nott lend her for say 2 weeks a messenger appears requesting a loan
b) when loaned
- he has a servant closely measure her breast size
- he also measures by feel
- he makes suggestions to your slave maker that you should give her to him, then suggest selling her, but at a low price initially
- price rising each loan, but never a fair price, a bit low, showing that he has little interest in her other talents and training
- have a servant girl speak to you or your slave when the Count steps out. Imploring that you do not sell your slave
and more possible events.




[/SPOILER]








Event line Content
[SPOILER=14]1
Have you considered the idea of a "dark path"? Having Adisa refuse to train you could result in an encounter with one of the milk farmers from the north west farm who wants who offers to teach you in exchange for helping him capture Adisa.






[/SPOILER]
[SPOILER=15]2
Well, the main result/or goal I wanted to achieve with the Be-Eventline and the Cowgirltraining is the following:
An Eventline which offeres a one-time-possibility to gain access to your own
• a)means to expand your slaves bustline (and maybe even turning a male slave into a female one, though I know there is not even one male slave out there, mhm maybe minor slaves.....ah the mind boggles at the possibilities)


• b)aquire the skills to change the center of lust of your slave so that she can cum just from her breasts


• c)aquire the skills to make her lactating


• d)additional text-bits that reflect the breasts of your slave


• e)a way to sell/ or profit from her milk




I realise that there a a number of different "ideals" for Cowgirls. In order to satisfy most people (and following a suggestion from cmac) i want to offer to "ways of the cowgirls"
Way A): The Cow-SLAVE is used simply to harvest her product, her needs are secondary. She is considered a Cow because she is held/used like cattle. She is drugged into a dull, sex-crazed state of mind in order to keep her in her milking-stall as long as possible. The allready existing Farm-Milking is a good example. The Cow-SLAVE offers her milk to cum, to be fucked.
Following this way you may earn more money, work with the count and his consorts. It is a huge but shady and illegal business and most of the girls are abducted.


Way B): The Cow-GIRL loves her breasts, she offers her milk because she likes the recipiant, to give and the feeling of it. She is of normal mind, mimicing the cows because it is cute, like catgirls. She wants to be milked or milk herself because she likes it, not because of drugs. At the beginning of the game there are a few women out there who like to lactate, but there is no real milking-business. I would like the player to be able to found his own business, from a new addition to his house and thus offer an alternative "green" , girl-friendly way of Milk.


As for the amount of Expansion: Well, personally i think a hentai-bust of 140 is plenty BUT there a at least a few people out there (and sometimes even myself) who want more, so I do not want to add an upper limit. I am currently thinking if I want to include a third Way C): After the bust reaches 200+ she is mostly immobile and can only be used for nightactions and milking. But this would require a lot of writing for ALL daytime events and nightactions.


Summary and Quick Walkthrough:
1. Go through Events 1-3
2. Go through Event 4 and solve the little BE-riddle, now you have a lactating slave for the first time.
3. This way you gained access to two new nightactions, one to increase her breast-fixation and one to increase her lactation.
3a) Breast Fixation is from here on accessiable for all new slaves.
4. If the riddle was solved you can plant a few strange fruits in the new house addition "The greenhouse". The first fruits will only be ripe to harvest after starting a new slave.
5. By feeding strange fruits to a new slave you can make her lactating, thus gaining access to the "milk-her" night-action.


This way you can get your first and all following slaves to be breast fixated and lactating, IF you solved the puzzle and build the required house addition.


X. With any lactationg slave: Depending on your choices during a two or three Events/Visits you may work for EITHER the Count or start your own business. This should be a one-time-only choice per slave to be made, considering its fundamental different philosophies. Once you founded your own business you can let any new lactating slave work there, it would be really cool if minor and past slaves could work there too.


XXX. Depending on her stats and the "milk-Career"-Choice she can get 2 different endings
XXXX. If she is only lactating but did not work at any Dairy-farm at all, she gets just a few additional lines at her completion.


[/SPOILER]
[SPOILER=16]3
Spoiler for Cowgirl Clamps Encounter: 




Cowgirl Encounter (Clamps)


Take a Walk, Town Center, first encounter


Taking a break from her walk, (SlaveName) comes across a small café where she is delighted to see that a cowgirl works as a waitress! (SlaveName) is disappointed to see that there are no seats available, but she stays close by, watching with interest. Unsurprisingly, the cowgirl seems to be a popular waitress, with customers constantly calling her over to their table. She looks a little flustered by the attention, but does the best she can to make sure everyone is served.


At most of the tables she stops at, the cowgirl hesitates for a long moment while serving the customer, seemingly fiddling with her own shirt. (SlaveName) cranes her neck to get a better look, but the cowgirl’s back is turned towards her. In time, however, she makes her way to serve a man near (SlaveName), and asks shyly what the customer would like. He immediately orders the house special, a smile on his face.


Flushing slightly, the cowgirl returns briefly with a cup of coffee, which she places on the table. Then, discreetly, she unbuttons her shirt, and removes one large breast, aiming it at the coffee cup. The cowgirl squeezes gently on her own breast, wincing slightly and biting her lower lip. Soon after, a steady stream of milk emerges, pouring straight into the coffee! (SlaveName) watches, entranced, as the cowgirl slowly milks herself into the man’s coffee, stopping every so often to ask if he has had enough. The man smiles and nods to the cowgirl.


The cowgirl, still blushing, takes a deep breath, and the milk slows, then stops. The man tips the cowgirl, then sits back to enjoy his coffee.. He seems to take immense pleasure in the drink, and admires the cowgirl’s swaying hips as she walks away.


(Assistant Present)
(SlaveName) wants to linger a bit longer, but is pulled away by (Assistant).


(SM Present)
(SlaveName) wants to linger a bit longer, but you tell her it is time to go.






Take a Walk, Town Center, second encounter


(SlaveName) makes her way back to the café with the cowgirl waitress, intent on meeting her this time. Fortunately, she manages to find a seat this time, and settles in to wait for service. The cowgirl seems even busier today than she did last time, but (SlaveName) watches the cowgirl with no small amount of interest, marveling each time she delivers a house special with her own personal cream.


(Extra: Slave is Lactating)
(SlaveName) watches in relative awe at the cowgirl’s self control. Each time she milks herself for a customer, it is with little stimulation and stops almost on command. (SlaveName) is a little turned on by the show, and feels her own nipples begin to slowly dew with milk, leaking and staining the front of her shirt.


In time, the cowgirl makes her way over to (SlaveName)’s table, a shy, embarrased look on her face. She seems to know that (SlaveName) has been watching her the whole time, and seems a little self-conscious about her breasts.


(SlaveName) spends some time getting to know the cowgirl, who introduces herself as Aria. Aria seems shy, but also very friendly, and willingly tell’s SlaveName all about what it means to be a cowgirl.


Aria:
“I work here because a cowgirl needs to be a provider. If they don’t give their milk to someone who needs it, then it’s being wasted…and no real cowgirl wastes milk. It’s a little embarrasing to milk myself in front of all these people, but I can be happy giving them what I can.”


(SlaveName) can’t stop herself from asking how the cowgirl provides milk for all of her customers, and always so readily. The cowgirl blushes deeper, and says that her master has made sure to train her to only give milk when she needs to. When (SlaveName) asks about the training, the cowgirl looks uncomfortably around, and removes a pair of clamps from her apron pocket.


Aria:
“I trained with these nippleclamps. It hurt at first, and my milk got so full after a while…but eventually, I learned to control it. Now, I only milk when I want to.”


(Extra: Slave is not lactating)
She looks down at the clamps, a little fondly, but then presses them into (SlaveName)’s hands with a shy smile.


Aria:
“Here…I don’t need them anymore. Why don’t you take them? Maybe you can learn to be a cowgirl too!”
(Extra: Slave is lactating)
She glances down at (SlaveName)’s chest, noticing the milk stains. She smiles shyly, and then quickly presses the clamps into (SlaveName)’s hands.


Aria:
“Here…it looks like you need these more than me. Remember not to keep them on too long, or you might get too full.”


(End Extras)
Aria smiles at (SlaveName) happily, hoping that (SlaveName) will visit again sometime soon. Thoughtfully, (SlaveName) pockets the clamps and leaves the café. She looks back once, but Aria is already serving another customer, face red and milk flowing.






Take a Walk, third encounter
(SlaveName) comes across Aria the cowgirl once more, still working in the café. Aria smiles happily to see her again, and the two sit down and talk for a while about cowgirls and milk. Aria makes sure to get (SlaveName) a house special, turning bright red as she hesitatingly provides the cream.


[/SPOILER]
[SPOILER=17]4
Hi there!


I've got just a couple of questions:
Spoiler for Question 1: 
Concerning the way to your own/ the Counts farm: Should i write two sets of events, one for experiencing them the first time with a slave, the other for doing it all again with another slave?
Should a new slave (after choosing being a cow-girl) be able to work at your/the counts farm from the start?


Spoiler for question 2: 
I thought of the following:
alternative 1: You gain the new SM-skill "Cow-trainer(Really need a better name for that)" with any slave either in a series of visits at the count after the event3 OR visiting the new NPC
Now you can use a new night action "do something with her breasts(obviously a working-title ".
If you have trained her breasts enough you can do the following: Visit the count again and be offered the chance to join him and his farm: your slave can work on the farm now.
or you visit the new NPC and you will talk about your own farm: thus your slave could work freelance in your own barn
You will have to choose.


alternative 2: You gain the new SM-skill "Cow-trainer(Really need a better name for that)" with any slave in a series of visits at the count after the event3.
Now you can use a new night action "do something with her breasts(obviously a working-title ".
If you have trained her breasts enough you can do the following: Visit the count again and be offered the chance to join him and his farm: your slave can work on the farm now.
BUT before you can work you get one day to think about. the next action you do now will let you met a new NPC. You will talk about your own farm: thus your slave could work freelance in your own barn
You will have to choose.


alternative 3: You encountered several cow-girls and a new NPC before. After your slave returns from Event 5 (the fruits and such): You get an early morning event showing your slave lactating enough. You get 3 choices: 1.) Ask the count if he wants to milk her: You can work at the farm
2.) You don't want to exploid her breasts at all. (no more lactation texts/jobs for those who don't want that)
3.) You don't like the way the count and his farm work so you set out to look for an alternative (meeting npc, finding pieces of device etc.)


alternative 4: You meet the new npc at a walk at the farm. You can meet her randomly again 2 more times. She then offers you to visit her.
She teaches you how to train Cow-girls but warns you of the counts evil farm.
When your slave finally starts lactating you have to choose between count or your farm.


Alternative 4: well the stuff i wrote in the post 24


note that the rescue of tifa and such can be included either way.
I'm just looking for a way into the farm-business which lets your SM learn a new skill and works for newly started slaves as well.


i cannot really decide in which way to start the farm-event line
i personally favor alternative 3 but that means doing the same events again.
Please i need a little input! 


[/SPOILER]
[SPOILER=18]5
Otherwise for the milking farm, for one thing I would prefer to not refer to them as a Company, let us still refer to it as a farm or something similar. Company just sounds a little anachronistic. Also let us not refer to the term machine specifically, again a little anachronistic. So 
milking aparatus
milk extracting device
or some such.


Corrupt path - sounds reasonable, but a few thoughts
a) we should consider the situation if you lose a slave to the cow girl ending. It could be a path
- you do the various count events
- you realise what really happened to your old slave and do not care, she was owned by another after all
- you negotiate with the count for a piece of the action, for blackmail and for compensation
b) remember I plan to make it that Tifa is rescued from the farm. So one way could be you learn from her of this endevour


Good path
- I like the NPC path, introducing a new person. The Busty Cat Slave can be owned by her (or him, I prefer her) or be a friend
- ditto I like the rescue and similar story ideas


Ideas for character
- Yoko from Gurren Laagen
- Lei Fang from Street Fighter
- Boa Hancock
- Kurumu the Succubus
All quite well endowed.


The new job sounds well thought out, I have nothing to add there at the moment. Same for the ends as well, all sound good.
I'll have to add the new hidden stat some time.
[/SPOILER]
[SPOILER=19]6
so I will do on the following:
If your slave experienced Event No.3: BE at the Count:
4a) a set of of 3 different additional texts if you meet the count somewhere. DONE
4b) two different messenger....well...messages delivered from the count. DONE
4c) a set of 5 -10 different texts if you visit the count again.
4d) 2 different texts for lending her to the count again.
4e) A set of 3 different additional text-lines in which npc's, you already visited, comments on her being bigger, chest-wise. DONE, 5 actually
4f) A set of three different additional text-lines in which npc's, if you never encountered them before, comment on her big tits. DONE, 5 as well
4g) Some text in which somebody mentions the alternative Girl-milking business.
4h) Some small additional lines, regarding the influence her bigger breasts have on the other daytime/night action 






If your slave experienced the Event No.3: BE at the Count and the Event No.5: BE in the forest:
6a) a set of 3 different additional texts if you meet the count somewhere 
6b) two alternatives for the messengers again. The count reeeeeeally wanna see her new bust.
6c) 3 different texts for lending her to the count again. The first one offers a choice and can lead to a bad-end. The second one applies if you have bad-end off or declined. And the third text applies if you have bad-ends off and visit the count any succeeding time.
6e) A set of 3 different additional text-lines in which npc's, you already visited, comments on her being really huge, chest-wise.
6f) A set of three different additional text-lines in which npc's, if you never encountered them before, comments on her huge tits.
6g) Some text with the person from the alternate Girl-milking-business comments on her even bigger rack.
6h) Some small additional lines, regarding the influence her huge breasts have on the other daytime/night action 
Spoiler for As for the last potion: 
I will go with the over-dose theory. If you lend her again after Event3 he will have her breasts examined, measured and thoroughly touched and kneaded. 
If you lend her again after Event3 and the BE in Event5: he will tell you, that in order for the result to be permanent, the potion must be applied one more time. If you have bad-ends on, he will inject the stuff again directly, she will grow to a massive size. The count will buy her for almost nothing, considering the original owner does not like her any more (just like with the uninhibitory-potion but with different text). If you have bad-ends off: The count will let her drink the potion, as it is intended, to consolidate the BE.




almost forgot:


One end if you sold her to the count (gonna be called: counts pet)
An aditional end in which her new breasts and her love for being milked is mentioned (cowgirl ending)




I think this should sufficiently round up the BE-Event-line. 
When I am done with this, hopefully soon, I will start to flesh out some vigilante-events. Still no rape though, but what about a duel with their ...foxy leader? If you loose she will get a round with your slave and/or you.
The deep forest....just saying that gives me ideas! well, first things first! 
Sorry to those who suggested Slavemaker-BE, abandoned for now! (in regards off the current SM-stat panel)






oviously the steps 4c) 4g) and 6g) require some more info on your planned cow-Girl-part.
so, cmac: What do you think of these thoughts?




[/SPOILER]
[SPOILER=20]7
Spoiler for The corrupt Milk-Company: 


The corrupt Milk-Company: if you like the idea I will include the following texts:
The first time you visit the count after Event 3 he will offer you an uncomfortable milking-machine. He asks you to apply it to your slave nightly in order to stimulate your slaves breasts to be more productive and maybe even gain a little size. You can accept or decline this. If you accept: Just like visiting mistress eponema, each visit will increase your slavemaker skill of Cow-Girl-Trainer by 0.2
If you visit him again, after Event 3 and Event 5 had happened, he will tell you about his …. business and offers you to join.
In this way you get access to two new actions, see below.




If you start a new slave and already have Cow-Girl-training: at her first visit the count (your new business-associate) will give her a/the pill/potion and allow her to work at his company. He also offers the cow-accessories (this would mean a storyline continuing from one slave to another, alternative would be to do all events again)




Spoiler for The friendly Milk-Company: 
The friendly Milk-Company: As for the person to work with: I think astrid is a rather corrupt influence herself, considering her cock-milking-business. For the busty- cat slave at the beach: it would be somehow sad to only make cat-girls to cow-girls. Also, what if you hadn't trained Urd before, could you still found your own rivalling Milk-Company? 
maybe Maid Sumi?




But I would suggest a new NPC. You could notice her at first, maybe on different slave-maker actions. The next time you take a walk with your slave she notices your slave being more big-breasted. Maybe she even notices the marks left by the (uhuuu, beware ) eeeevil-milking-machine the count used on your slave (during event3) . She then admits of being milked herself, but having escaped the farm she is not a cowgirl any more.
You and this NPC realise that there will always be a demand for this special dairy-product, and so women will always be kidnapped to satisfy the market. you both agree to the following: you will provide the markets, but in a humane way without any kidnapping or brainwashing. If you can crush the evil Company along the way, even better. 
You can now visit her, each time you edge out more and more the construct of your company. Also you both develop a more comfortable milking-device. Just like before, each visit will increase your slavemaker skill of Cow-Girl-Trainer by 0.1. (Lower than the bonus the count-visit offers, because you have to figure it out on your own.)
Maybe a new upgrade/addition to your house could be necessary for your company to work 
Another step could be to visit the busty cat slave at the beach with personal supervision. Talking to her will tell you the way to obtain her milky potion.
Another step: visit the merchant(or somebody else) to get hold of a part for your machine.
Another step: rescue your new partner from thugs, trying to destroy your business.
Another step: own at least one minor-slave (or a specific one) which maintains your equipment.




If you want a new started slave to become a cow-girl as well, you can visit the new NPC again. She will offer your new slave the first potion and/or the suiting accessories: A tail, hoof-shoes, ears and horns and maybe even a special dress.
Alternatively you have to meet cowgirls at the farm to obtain these items.
Spoiler for Pic-Suggestion for new NPC: 
mhm everytime i try to add pictures, i get a freeze and have to refresh the page 






Spoiler for The Work for the Company: 


regardless which company you decide on, a new job is available now: Work for Company. This action will provide money and raise her Cow-Girl-stat. Depending on your affiliations her other stats change differently.
During night-training you can now choose: Milk her. This is a rather sexual milking. This training will stimulate her breasts more and will slowly raise her Cow-Girl-stat and raise her (secret-stat) milk-produktion. It could be a 5-step-training like the others, adding 5-10 cm to her bust for each step. This could reflect her breasts getting more productive.
Milk-produktion: she produces (secret stat) / 20 bottles of milk plus (Milk her-skill level) x (bust-size/100) 
A starting cowgirls-slave with the secret stat of 2, a bust of 80, and a “milk-her”skill of 0 would produce 0.1 liters(or simply bottles, its unit-less). 
a slave with the secret stat of 50, a bust of 125, and a “milk-her”skill 4of5 would produce 7,5 
a pro-cow-girl with the secret stat of 90, a bust of 150, and a “milk-her”skill 5of5 would produce 12
Each bottle will gain her 15gold if working for the count and 10 if working for you. (alternative: she produces less working for you)






To reflect the new business he founded/joined a slavemaker could now also work at a new job himself, called “Work at Farm”.








As for the Cow-Girl-Trainer-stat (what a word): 
Level 1: You can make some slaves wear the accessories and convince her to drink the potion/pill
Cow-slave ending
Level 2: All slaves can reach 100 0f 100 and become a Cow-Girl. You now know how to raise her milk-production faster.






If you work for/with the count: end 1: She is dull and only a little more than a cow. She is valued on her production, which depends on your skill.
If you work on your own: end 2(additional): (If Cow-slave)She will function normally, her owner will comment on her giving milk. (if CowGirl: she will function normally, her owner congratulating you on her fine milk he often uses himself)




[/SPOILER]




Game Mechanics
[SPOILER=21]1
Have you considered changing the text for the tit-fuck night action based on breast fixation and lactation? High breast fixation could cause your slave to orgasm from the sensation alone, and high lactation could mean they use their milk as lubricant.
[/SPOILER]
[SPOILER=22]2
<MilkHerself>Milk Herself</MilkHerself>
<MilkHerselfOn>On - May relieve the pressure of her lactation herself</MilkHerselfOn>
<MilkHerselfOff>Off - May not milk herself, the pressure in her breasts keeps rising</MilkHerselfOff>
c) if Milk Herself rule is on there there should be ocaisonal events (morning/evening etc) where she milks herself, maybe even walk events, or visit etc. A whole range of things. But these are optional really. 
[/SPOILER]
[SPOILER=23]3
<BreastExpert>Breast Expert</BreastExpert>
<BreastExpertDescription>You are an expert in making a girl feel good by touching her breasts and nipples. With the help of strange fruits and devices you can train cowgirls</BreastExpertDescription>
<BreastExpertLevel1>You can convince most slaves to agree to Breast-Play and being milked. Your slave can reach a “Cowgirl” level of 60 and thus get the additional ending "Cow-Girls" or “Milk-Maid”.</BreastExpertLevel1>
<BreastExpertLevel2>You can convince any slave to agree to “Breast Play”. Your slave can reach a “Cowgirl” level of 100 and thus getting the ending “Joyfull Cowgirl”..</BreastExpertLevel2>


[/SPOILER]
[SPOILER=24]4
Milk-Buildup: This is secret stat with a value from 0-100.
A lactating breast constantly produces milk. Depending on the Lactation-rate and breastsize it can take a while until the slave will start to leak, or (if she has nipple-clams) gets uncomfortable with the pressure in her chest. This stat can trigger additional lines to standard-events, or a new event.


• There are 2 Conditions for Milk-Buildup
• Condition 0: She does not lactate(lactation <30)
• Condition 1: Lactation at least 30
• If condition 1 is met, the following happens: each day without a milking action the value of milk-build-up rises by lactation/5.
• This means, everyday her breasts gets fuller
• if she is allowed to milk herself: the value sinks by -15 per Day
• if she in not allowed: the value still sinks by -5 per day (as she leaks if the pressure is to high)
• If she wears nipple clamps: The value does not sink
• If she wears vibrating nippletoys: The value increases by additional lactation/10 per day
The nightaction Milk her lowers the milk-buildup value
>Milk her by hand lowers it by -10 per action
>Milk her by mouth lowers it by -5 per action
>Milk her with a device lowers it by -20 per action
>Feed her own milk lowers it by -5 per action


[If Value is lower than 30]: No pressure, no changes


[If Value is higher than 30]: The milk stored makes her bust increase by 5% until she is milked. Additional text-line may appear to all day- and nightactions: Her breasts look rounder than usual.


[If Value is higher than 45]: The milk stored makes her bust increase by 10% until she is milked. Additional text-line may appear to all day- and nightactions: Her breasts look round and ripe.


[If value is higher than 60]: The milk stored makes her bust increase by 15% until she is milked. Additional text-line may appear to all day- and nightactions: Her breasts look very round and full. She asks you to milk her, as her breasts are getting quite heavy.


[If Value is higher than 75]: The milk stored makes her bust increase by 5% until she is milked. She feels the pressure, all stat-increases are halfed. 
Additional text-line may appear to all day- and nightactions:
>[If she wears no nippleclams and is dressed]:Her breasts look tight and swollen She feels uncomfortable with the pressure. With every breath she takes the wet stain on her clothes gets bigger and bigger as she constantly leaks drop after drop of milk. She begs you to milk her.
>[If she wears no nippleclams and is naked]:Her breasts look tight and swollen She feels uncomfortable with the pressure. A single, thin stream of milk sprays constantly from her nipples, but it is not enough to relieve the stinging amount of milk in her breasts. She begs you to milk her, or at least allow her to do it herself.
>[If she wears nippleclams]: Her breasts look tight and swollen with huge amounts of milk. She feels uncomfortable with the pressure and moans in pain [if she has bondage level >4: and a little lust]. She begs you to remove her clams and milk her, or at least allow her to do it herself.


[If Value reaches 100 over night you will get an early morning event]:
(Assistantname) wakes you up and calls you quickly over to (slavenames) Room. You dress in a hurry wondering what is wrong.
[If she wears no nippleclams]: (Slavename) lies on her bed, naked. Her breasts are flushed and stand up filled to the brim with milk. Your slave seems to be in pain, supporting her tits as they erupt milk in a steady flow squirting in the air. You quickly rush over to her
[If she wears nippleclams]: (Slavename) lies on her bed, naked. Her breasts are red an you can see the veins far more clearly than usual. Her tits stand up filled to the brim with milk. Your slave seems to be in pain, supporting her tits as their own weight hurts her. You quickly rush over to her and remove the nippleclams. 


You take her swollen mammaries in your hands and feel her tight flesh. Just touching them causes a gush of milk to erupt from her nipples. With skilled hands you start to milk your slave. With every burst of milk (Slavename) moans in a mixture of lust and painrelieve. You order your assistant to come over. Each of you take one of her breasts with both hands and press more and more milk out. As her milkflow decreases, the both of you start to suck direktly on her nipples, chugging down her milk. By now (slavename) is in a constant orgasmic rush, cumming just by the sensations in her breasts and nipples.


Finally (slavename)s breasts are looking normal again, she does not leak anymore. You guess she is empty ... for now....
Just like a visit of the wandering vendor you can start your day now at 10.am
Lust +2, Breast Fixation +2; Lactation +2, Refinement -2, Intelligence -2


For the additional text lines for other events see post #3
[/SPOILER]
[SPOILER=25]5
Cow-Girl Training":
This stat has a range from 30 to 100. A perfect Cow-Girl loves her breasts, can orgasm from them and yields a high milk-production. So this training stat is the sum of "breast-fixation"+"Lactation" divided by 2. Depending on this stat you will get different (additional) endings.


If your slave agrees to the night-action "Milk her" the first time you can ask her to become a cow-girl. Some girls will only agree to this if your slaverskill is high enough:
Early Morning Event to start the Cow-Girl-Training:
(Slavename) agreed to be milked. Although she is still not totaly comfortable with all of the sensation she experiances, your skilled eye realises her potential to gain significantly more pleasure from her breasts. You ask herself if she would agree to be trained as a Cow-Girl. Do you want (Slavename) to become a Cow-Girl?


[If you choose no: The event ends]: You decide agains this, as not everybody likes Cow-Girls. So it could lower her value for some owners.


[If you say yes but your skill is too low]: You like the idea, but (Slavename) strongly refuses: "No, I'm not some Cow!"
[If you say yes and your skill is high enough]: You suggest her to become a Cow Girl. She hesitates a little but finally she nods. You will need to focus on the sensitivity of her breasts and nipples, it requires constant training. You should also start and increase her lactation. And maybe you can find someone who can sell you a nice Cow-Bell.....
[Lust +7; refinement -2; sensibility +2; Joy +2, Breast Fixation +1]
[/SPOILER]
[SPOILER=26]6
This additional text could be added to any existing event with BE-elements


[If bustline is expanded by 5% and the slave is naked:] Looking down on her new bustline, (slavename) is sure that she won't fit into her clothes anymore. She asks you to take her to the tailor as soon as possible.
[If bustline is expanded by 5% and the slave is naked, AND has the skill Naked 5:]Looking down on her new bustline, (slavename) is sure that she won't fit into her old clothes anymore. She doesn't seem to mind, though.


[If bustline is expanded by 5% and the slave is wearing clothes:] When you are ready to leave (slavename) comes to you:
"I really need to go to the tailor, my clothes are killing me, they pinch me constantly [If breastfixation is >50: and not in a good way]"


If her Bustline was expanded by 5% and you have not been to the tailor yet you will get this additional line at every morning:
"Please take (Slavename) to the Tailor, slaver, her clothes could tear any minute and she seems to be unhappy"
Joy -1.


If her Bustline was expanded by 5% and you go to the tailor:
"Oh my, what happend to you, your bust seems to fight the fabric really hard. Did you wash your clothes to hot? But don't worry I can alter your wardrobe,no problem"
Do you want the tailor to alter (slavenames) entire wardrobe? It will cost you (Number of dresses x 50gp)
[if yes: money is deducted, events end]
[if no: you will get the early morning message every day with joy-1 everyday until you alter the wardrobe]








[If bustline is expanded by 10% and the slave is naked:] Looking down on her new bustline, (slavename) is sure that she won't fit into any of her old clothes anymore. She asks you to take her to the tailor as soon as possible or she would have to walk around naked.
[If bustline is expanded by 10% and the slave is naked, AND has the skill Naked 5:] Looking down on her new bustline, (slavename) is sure that she won't fit into into any of her old clothes anymore. She doesn't seem to mind running around completly naked, though.


[If bustline is expanded by 10% and the slave is wearing clothes:] When you are ready to leave (slavename) comes to you:
"I really can't fit my breasts into my clothes, they just won't fit! Please, please take me to the tailor!"


If her Bustline was expanded by 10% and you have not been to the tailor yet you will get this additional line at every morning:
"Please take (Slavename) to the Tailor, slaver, she cannot fit her fat tits in any of her clothes. I'm afraid she has to walk around naked today"
The slave is automaticaly naked with all the aplying stat-changes.


If her Bustline was expanded by 10% and you go to the tailor:
"Oh my, you are naked! Didn't I sell you some clothes a while ago? I'm sure of it. Well anyway, let me see what I can find or alter to fit your...uhmm...brea..I mean build.
The player has to buy the clothes again!
[/SPOILER]
[SPOILER=27]7
Milk-Buildup: This is secret stat with a value from 0-100.
A lactating breast constantly produces milk. Depending on the Lactation-rate and breastsize it can take a while until the slave will start to leak, or (if she has nipple-clams) gets uncomfortable with the pressure in her chest. This stat can trigger additional lines to standard-events, or a new event.


• There are 2 Conditions for Milk-Buildup
• Condition 0: She does not lactate(lactation <30)
• Condition 1: Lactation at least 30
• If condition 1 is met, the following happens: each day without a milking action the value of milk-build-up rises by lactation/5.
• This means, everyday her breasts gets fuller
• if she is allowed to milk herself: the value sinks by -15 per Day
• if she in not allowed: the value still sinks by -5 per day (as she leaks if the pressure is to high)
• If she wears nipple clamps: The value does not sink
• If she wears vibrating nippletoys: The value increases by additional lactation/10 per day
The nightaction Milk her lowers the milk-buildup value
>Milk her by hand lowers it by -10 per action
>Milk her by mouth lowers it by -5 per action
>Milk her with a device lowers it by -20 per action
>Feed her own milk lowers it by -5 per action


[If Value is lower than 30]: No pressure, no changes


[If Value is higher than 30]: The milk stored makes her bust increase by 5% until she is milked. Additional text-line may appear to all day- and nightactions: Her breasts look rounder than usual.


[If Value is higher than 45]: The milk stored makes her bust increase by 10% until she is milked. Additional text-line may appear to all day- and nightactions: Her breasts look round and ripe.


[If value is higher than 60]: The milk stored makes her bust increase by 15% until she is milked. Additional text-line may appear to all day- and nightactions: Her breasts look very round and full. She asks you to milk her, as her breasts are getting quite heavy.


[If Value is higher than 75]: The milk stored makes her bust increase by 5% until she is milked. She feels the pressure, all stat-increases are halfed. 
Additional text-line may appear to all day- and nightactions:
>[If she wears no nippleclams and is dressed]:Her breasts look tight and swollen She feels uncomfortable with the pressure. With every breath she takes the wet stain on her clothes gets bigger and bigger as she constantly leaks drop after drop of milk. She begs you to milk her.
>[If she wears no nippleclams and is naked]:Her breasts look tight and swollen She feels uncomfortable with the pressure. A single, thin stream of milk sprays constantly from her nipples, but it is not enough to relieve the stinging amount of milk in her breasts. She begs you to milk her, or at least allow her to do it herself.
>[If she wears nippleclams]: Her breasts look tight and swollen with huge amounts of milk. She feels uncomfortable with the pressure and moans in pain [if she has bondage level >4: and a little lust]. She begs you to remove her clams and milk her, or at least allow her to do it herself.


[If Value reaches 100 over night you will get an early morning event]:
(Assistantname) wakes you up and calls you quickly over to (slavenames) Room. You dress in a hurry wondering what is wrong.
[If she wears no nippleclams]: (Slavename) lies on her bed, naked. Her breasts are flushed and stand up filled to the brim with milk. Your slave seems to be in pain, supporting her tits as they erupt milk in a steady flow squirting in the air. You quickly rush over to her
[If she wears nippleclams]: (Slavename) lies on her bed, naked. Her breasts are red an you can see the veins far more clearly than usual. Her tits stand up filled to the brim with milk. Your slave seems to be in pain, supporting her tits as their own weight hurts her. You quickly rush over to her and remove the nippleclams. 


You take her swollen mammaries in your hands and feel her tight flesh. Just touching them causes a gush of milk to erupt from her nipples. With skilled hands you start to milk your slave. With every burst of milk (Slavename) moans in a mixture of lust and painrelieve. You order your assistant to come over. Each of you take one of her breasts with both hands and press more and more milk out. As her milkflow decreases, the both of you start to suck direktly on her nipples, chugging down her milk. By now (slavename) is in a constant orgasmic rush, cumming just by the sensations in her breasts and nipples.


Finally (slavename)s breasts are looking normal again, she does not leak anymore. You guess she is empty ... for now....
Just like a visit of the wandering vendor you can start your day now at 10.am
Lust +2, Breast Fixation +2; Lactation +2, Refinement -2, Intelligence -2
[/SPOILER]
[SPOILER=28]8
Stuff i collected (unshopped) images for:
piercings: nipple-rings, nipple-clams, vibrating-clams, maybe nipple-weights or a cage of some sorts or nipple-clams with a rod for insertion for 3 more bdsm-options


Attire: horns, ears, tail and maybe a bell


Various items for the items list, not equipable: a milking device, a superior milking device(less production more joy), a strong milking device (viceversa), "a box of various nippletoys" for the nightaction sub-choice "use nipple-toys" (this box is a little deus ex machina-device, allowing to use different images, with different toys or different girls)
[/SPOILER]
[SPOILER=29]9
Spoiler for milk her: 
Milk her- requirements TBD- must have milking machine obviously, same with lactating
I kept similar descriptors to be cohesive with the other descriptions
You bring (Slavename) into the milking room where the machine stands ready for her
[if +10% bust-size: huge breasts.]
[if +25% bust-size: giant breasts.]
[if +50% bust-size: enormous breasts.]


NOTE: assuming an implementation of breast fixation is part of the planned cowgirl training, the next parts could also be based on her "level" of milk her, similar to the levels of sexual trainings
[if milk her level <3: She looks timidly at the machine, unsure whether to feel excited or afraid but]
[if milk her level <4: She feels a hot flush and makes a cute gasp as]
[if milk her level <5:She looks at the machine and feels her cunt moisten with arousal and ]
[if milk her level =5: She almost orgasms just from the sight and]


[if lactation <30: drops of milk form at her nipples in response.]
[if lactation >30 & <50: her clearly erect nipples start to leak milk.]
[if lactation>70: she emits a steady stream of milk, quickly forming a puddle on the floor which you order her to lick.]
The machine rises before you, consisting of a padded bench which (slavename) must straddle, [if 10 or more bondage trainings; restraints for her arms and legs so she cannot pleasure herself] and the cups for her breasts. Tubing runs from each cup to a central collecting tank with has many attachments for your use.
[depending on her Dildo training: a small vibrator rises from the cushion which (slavename) mounts daintily before /a large vibrator rises from the cushion, which (slavename) carefully lowers herself onto before /a huge vibrator rises from the cushion which (slavename) easily slips inside her cunt before /an enormous vibrator rises from the cushion which (slavename) practically jumps on before]
[depending on anal plug training: pushing the small plug into her ass with a grimace/ sliding the plug into her ass after several deep breaths/ slipping the plug into her ass with a sigh/ easily shoving the anal plug inside herself and nearly cumming from the sensation ]
As you have learned, milk production increases if the slave is being stimulated.
Once (Slavename) is positioned properly you start the suction, slowly allowing her to get used to the sensation before engaging the vibrator and anal plug as well. (Slavename) lets out a gasp and bucks her hips against the rods filling her as they both begin to piston in and out. You watch for a while, alternating the vibration and speed of the thrusting in order to maximize her yield. As (Slavename) is about to cum you slow the machine down, holding her at the edge until [if bondage done <5x: she reaches down and brings herself off, cumming wildly and releasing another gush of milk] [else: she strains against her bonds, begging you to allow her to cum. You smile evilly and continue her torture for many long minutes, enjoying the way her body writhes with need; all the while her udders continue to spurt milk. Finally you turn everything on maximum and (Slavename) lets loose a [if cowgirl training <50: scream] [else: long loud MOOOOOOOoooooo!!!] as her breasts explode with one last gush of milk before she collapses completely. You let her rest for a few minutes before removing her from the machine.


[/SPOILER]
[SPOILER=30]10
Fruit-frenzy
Only happens if breast fixation >70; and both "feed her a fruit" and "gardening" has been done at least once
OR
if breast fixation is <70 BUT "feed her a fruit" has been done at least 5 times


(Assistantname) hurries into your room, waking you up roughly.
"(Slavemakername), come quickly, (Slavename) has broken into the greenhouse! She is wreaking havoc among your strange fruit culture!"
Alarmed you rise from your bed and rush towards your greenhouse with its precious plants and flowers. Upon entering you can her (slavename)s lustfull moans and slurping. You see her surrounded by the remains of what seems like all of your strange fruits. She lies naked on a sunbed, her skin is glistening with sticky juice and the sweat of her lust. She must be in here for nearly all of the night, ever since you send her to bed. During this time she ate so many fruits that her belly is bulging massivly and must have had countless orgasms, her sex and the sunbed are covered with a thick layer of her own juices.
But all of this is not really noticed by you as you cannot stop staring at her ...
[if +10% bust-size: huge breasts, barely hold together by her slender arms]
[if +25% bust-size: giant breasts, flowing forth from under her slender arms]
[if +50% bust-size: enormous breasts, flowing over her chest and the sides of the sunbed.]
[if lactation is at least 30]: a constant thick stream of milk runs down her busty curves, each movement of her breasts results in a little spray and a noticable increase of the flow coming out of her nipples.
[if lactation is at least 50]: gallons of milk run down her busty curves, each movement of her breasts results in a wild spray from her nipples and whole rivers of white paint her figure in a milky shade.
[if lactation is at least 70]: gallons of milk spray from her milkplants, spraying around vividly. Each movement of her breasts increases the torrents even further, pressing out her oversaturatet tits.
[if you own a milking device] She even brought your milking device with her! The suction cups are lying on the ground, they must have fallen off, as her breasts expandet and the countless orgasms shoke her body.


When (slavename) finally notices you, she gan only weakly smile, but as she looks you directly in the eyes, she raises her one hand and bites into another fruit, quickly devouring it. With both hands empty now she immediatly starts to masturbates her tits, cumming almost instantly. Ignoring her expanding flesh for now you quickly step forward, trying not to slip on the wet floor. You take the last few fruits from her and order (assistantname) to get your bondagegear. After hiding the sad remains of your culture you set your mind on punishing the disobedient (slavename) 




You tie her into a very tight bondage, ignoring her lustfull moans as you cannot avoid touching her breasts sometimes and thus sending new lustwaves down her spine. 


Quite some time later, when (/slavename) finally comes back to her senses, she is hanging tightly bound from the ceiling, her [if +10% bust-size huge breasts]i[if +25% bust-size giant breasts][if +50% bust-size enormous breasts] hanging pendulously under her. One look at your angry face tells her that she is in trouble now. 


You start her punishment by just letting her hang there, building the suspense. 
[if bondage has beed done at least 20x: As you start to notice her arousal you know you would really have to exert yourself this time.]
[If you do not own a whip: With your bare hands you start to slap her tits, causing them to swing widly.]
[If you own a whip: With quick and aimed strikes of your whip you slap her tits continously, causing them to swing widly.]
[additional If you are a cruel master: You slowly start to pace your strokes faster and faster, with increasing force]


Each of your slaps causes a spray of milk being pressedd out of her tits. Soon they are shining red, and tears flow down (slavenames) face. But still, under the influence of the fruits, her lust keeps building her one orgasm after another!


You realise that you cannot really punish her by touching her breasts, so you change your plans: 
You order your assistant to stand on the other side of (slavename) and together you each grab one of her nipples. At first you start to milk her, instantly driving her mad with lust. Just on the edge before she cums once again you seize your milking and forcefully press her nipples shut.
Irritated (Slavename) begs you to continue, rocking her chest and hips in a helpless attempt to reach her orgasm. But you stay firm and keep on closing her nipples by strongly pinching them.


Soon you can feel her breasts to increase in volume and you have to increase your grip. 
[if you own the silky ropes: Her growing chestmeat starts to press against the silky ropes]
After a little longer the veins under the skin of her tits are becoming visible, distenting from her otherwise flawless skin. (Slavename) starts to feel the pressure inside her, steadily changing from pleasend to painfull. 
She begs you again to continue her milking. Still, you refuse.
By now her breasts became even more inflated and you have to struggle a bit to sustain your firm grip. (Slavename) starts to sweat heavily, moaning and whailing under the discomfort of her overloaded, distended tits.
Once or twice you have to renew your grip as your fingers start to hurt from the sheer efford of pressing her nipples shut. Whenever you release your grip for a second, immediately a thick stream of milk explodes from her nipples. Each time (slavename) thinks her milking will finally continue and her hopes are each time crushed as you continue your grip with vigor. Her whole world concentrates just on her breasts, constantly straining, distending and inflating. The need to be milked, to release the pressure dominates her mind.


Finally you cannot hold on to her billowed milkplants any longer. As she seems fascinated by the lactation inducing effect of the strange fruits you decide to give her more than she asks for: 
[if you do not own a milking device: You grap a gardenhose and lubricate one end with the thick juices still wetting her sex. You press the other end firmly agains one of her nipples.]
[If you do own a milking device: You take a gardenhouse and attach it to the outlet of your milking device. Then you lubricate the other end with the thick juices still wetting her sex.]
With a mischievous grin you then plug the hose into her ass.
[depending on her anal-plug and anal fuck training: It is quite difficult to insert the hose, she fights you for every inch/ With a little efford you manage to push the hose into her ass/ Her trained ass takes the hose with ease]
Tantalizing you push the hose further and further into her, until it rests many many inches deep in her bowels. (slavename)s orgasms has been denied for so long now, that she starts to rock her hips agains the hose, moaning and begging all the way.


[If you do not own a milking device: You take another garden hose and order your assistant to press it agains her other nipple while you stuff the other end into her ass, stretching her with the two hoses.] 
[If you own a milking device: You then attach the suction cups to her teats]
You decide it is now time to allow (slavename) to release some of the pressure build inside her. By now her tits are flushed red, blue veins are visible all over; they look so huge, round and bloated you are afraid anymore milk inside her could harm her.
As you release the your grip from her nipples and areolas (slavename)s berries instantly send forth heavy, finger-thick streams of milk, busting out of her overly stretched breasts. A deep, animalistic "oouhhh gooooooooooooooooooooooooood..........." breaks from her lips as (slavename) finally releases the pressure, cuming immediately and mind-breakingly strong. After the first burst her flow recedes to a continous, rich river of white, running down the hoses.
[If you do not own a milking device: Now you can finally apply enough force to direct all of her flow down the garden hose.]
[If you own a milking device: Your milking device struggles hard to suck up all of her flow, it may not be build to handle the shher amounts of milk]


(slavename)s orgasmic face suddenly changes its expression as the second part of your little mischievious plan comes into action: Finally her milk has reached the end of the hose and starts to pour into her bowls. But at the moment the orgiastic sensation of the milk flowing from her breasts rides her into another orgasms. You watch closely as slowly but surely her flat, slender belly starts to rise. 


By the time she is inflated by her own breastmilk that she looks like a mid-term pregnant woman the discomfort of her stretched belly penetrades her lust, she starts to moan in discomfort. But her breasts keep on lactating endless amounts of milk, gushing from her nipples and so her lust rises again. For a long time she alternates between discomfort and orgasm.


As her belly has reached the form of a full time pregnancy, hanging heavily under her, the discomfort overrides the pleasure and she begs you to release her, promising never to misbehave again. You wait until her belly is massivly distendend, looking as bloated as her tits just a few moments ago.


You wait a few more minutes, until you are sure she gets the message. Finally you remove the milkinput from her ass, 
[If you own a butt-plug: placing the biggest butt-plug you own inside her.] As her breasts are still in full production you hesitate shortly but then place a clean hose at her mouth, thus making her fill her stomach with milk as well. Finally you untie her and after she promised you to never misbehave again you allow her to leave.


With a belly as full as never before and slaped, still milk spraying tits the hastly takes of to the bathroom.
When she returns, you think you tie her up again, maybe redo the whole procedure again....
[if you a re a cruel master: ...and again and again.....]


[/SPOILER]
[SPOILER=31]11
9: The Greenhouse-Addition:
This is a bit difficult, because i don't know how house-additions will work.
Thus i will only provide a picture of a greenhouse and what i want it to be


Since it is not yet clear how house-extensions will work I just start with basics:
I assume you will go somewhere and order the house extension
I assume further that there will be a timeintervall between order and completion of the extension.


Textdescription for the greenhouse if you select it to be build:


First a longer description: This lovely mardukane-style greenhouse is a sturdy build made of forged steel and crystal-clear window-glass. It is not only a place where you can grow even the rarest of plants and flowers; with its spacy dimensions and sunny warm temperature it is also a winter garden, offering you a green salon you will want to use all year long.
[If Playerhome is Abandoned Keep] It will be placed in the sunniest part of the central courtyard, backing against one of the castle walls and covering nearly half of the courtyard.
[If Playerhome is Brothel] It will be added in the backyard, away from your customers.
[If Playerhome is City Apartement] Parts of the roof will be changed and replaced to fit a roof garden.
[If Playerhome is eerie house] Placed next to your house it will also offer a marvelous view over the beach and sea. We can only deliver it in a black finish, I'm afraid.
[If Playerhome is Farm House] Connected to your kitchen the new greenhouse will be placed in your backgarden.
[If Playerhome is Forest home] After cutting out a clearing to allow enough light to flow through the windows, it will be placed close to your house.
[If Playerhome is Mansion] The rooftop of your mansion is the perfect place for a spacious, secluded greenhouse.
[If Playerhome is Onsen] It will be placed close to your springs, using their heat to keep the plants warm, even in the strongest winters. A neatly trimmed hedge will allow for some privacy.
[If Playerhome is Temple] A part of the secluded temple garden will be covered with steel and glass of the greenhouse, creating a beautifull greenhouse.


If the above is all too long: This greenhouse will allow you to plant seeds and plants you may find. It is designed to be partially a winter garden.


At the completion of the greenhouse you get the following text: After the completion of your mardukane Greenhouse you take your whole household to a tour of your new rooms. The lofty structure of the slim stelltrusses and huge windows place a smile on your face.


Possibility A: You gained the strange fruit and the buy the greenhouse: [If BE-Event 4 (the strange Island) has allready occured, the player gets the following text: Suddenly you remember the strange fruits your slave brought back from the wildernis a while ago. You place them in different planters and different potting soils, unsure how to grow them best. At any rate it while take quite a while until you can think of a harvest.
Possibility B: You gained the strange fruit and allready have the greenhouse: [If BE-Event 4 (the strange Island) has just occured, the player gets the following text: You take the strange fruits from from (slavename) and take them to your greenhouse as soon as you have a minute to your self. You place them in different planters and different potting soils, unsure how to grow them best. At any rate it while take quite a while until you can think of a harvest.


The first time you can feed a fruit to a slave will be after you started a new slave!
This will be possible by selecting "feed her a fruit" in the submenue of the new night-action "Breast Play" ......which is yet to be implemented


If cmac allowes it, there could be a new daytime-action "gardening":
(Slavename) does a little of gardening, replanting flowers, cropping branches and withered blossoms. She enjoys the work, humming to herself.
joy+1; sensibility +1; constitution +1; conversation -1
[if breast fixation is >30: She shows a special interest in the strange fruits whenever she feels unsupervised.]
[if breast fixation is >50: She concentrates on caring for the strange fruits.
additional lust+1]
[if breast fixation is >70: Regarding her the lustfull glances at the strange fruits it may be best to not let her enter the greenhouse unsupervised.
Additional lust +1,5]


Note: the above daytime-action could be divided into 2 different subchoices:
A: Gardening, with focus on dirty work
B: Create a flower bouquet, with a more refined, sensible focus.


[/SPOILER]
[SPOILER=32]12
5) I will not be putting nipple insertion events into the game (well inserting a milking device maybe). I find the nipple fucking etc too grotesque and just unreal. Other developers can add them for their slaves or assistants, but I will not add it for core events


[/SPOILER]
[SPOILER=33]13
you should consider smth like wearing nipple rings would prevent or make it difficult for girl to milk herself and so for example she would need SM to permit her taking off the rings,
also theres a matter of the breast size influnce on daily activities , it would be quite logical that the bigger she gets the more difficlt and tiresome some tasks are at least for some time till she ets accustomed to her new havy flesh,it could be related to her constitution and fitness 


and theres also an influence on sexual training you should consider applying stroking,hand milking and breast feeding during intercourse and while doing "lick her" as well as "touch her"


[/SPOILER]
[SPOILER=34]14
For graphics and breast size changes, I have standardly included two versions of the dress images for most slaves
standard size
breasts 10% bigger
This is generally as it is easier to edit the images with a moderate size increase. I could add a third stage, a larger size 20 or even 50% but they may not look as good.


I have changed the game so the selection of these images is based on her bust size. In previous versions it was purely based on if she was taking the milk drug.




[/SPOILER]