<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!--
	To add before 3.5
	images
	rape in forest event
	sensorial depravation event
-->
<Language>


	<Events>
	<!--   _____________________________________________________ CUSTOM LOCATION DECLARING START _________________________________________________ -->
		<CustomHouse-x_Mareks_Camp name="x_Mareks_Camp" hint="A little forest clearing. Currently home to Mar'ek the goblin." xpos="240" ypos="450" show="true">
			<Choices>
				<Choice chance="60%">
					<DoEvent now="true">ConversationAnna</DoEvent>
				</Choice>
				<Choice chance="60%">
					<DoEvent now="true">ConversationMarekMain</DoEvent>
				</Choice>
				<Default>
					<DoEvent now="true">GeneralEventsCamp</DoEvent>
				</Default>
			</Choices>
		</CustomHouse-x_Mareks_Camp>
	<!--   _____________________________________________________ CUSTOM LOCATION DECLARING END _________________________________________________ -->
		<StartGame>  <!--  called when a slave starts training, so immediately at the start, before the first day of training -->
		  <SMBrandGoblins>
		  </SMBrandGoblins>
		</StartGame>


		<UpdateDateAndItems>
			<if flagSMBrandGoblins-5="true">
				<ShowCustomHouse>x_Mareks_Camp</ShowCustomHouse>
			</if>
		</UpdateDateAndItems>


		<Daily>
		</Daily>


		<EarlyMorning> 
			<GoblinTrigger chance="5%" flagSMBrandGoblins-0="false">  <!-- Rumor about goblins, do you want them?  -->
				<HideImages/>
				<ShowImage image='Images/Events/SMBrandGoblins/intro.jpg' align='2'/>
				<AddText>\rIt is said that the wanton forest men from the far south east carry steal away young women and girls. Mioya hasn't had anything to do with them or their kingdom for years; not since the Firee embargo. However I hear tell that some of these "goblin" girls are on show as exotic slaves right here in Mioya. We could go to see them if you like?"</AddText>
				<SetFlags flagSMBrandGoblins-0="true"/>
				<AskQuestions>
					<Question event='GoblinsYes'>Goblins ehh? Interesting...</Question>
					<Question event='GoblinsNo'>Meh, pass.</Question>
				</AskQuestions>
			</GoblinTrigger>
		</EarlyMorning>

		
		<Walk>


			<DocksSlavePens>
				<GoblinSlaveEncounterMain chance="50%" flagSMBrandGoblins-1="true" supervise="slavemaker" day="false" flagSMBrandGoblins-2="false">
					<HideImages/>
					<ShowImage image='Images/Events/SMBrandGoblins/Takerslave 1.jpg' align='2'/>
					<AddText>There are three exotic young slave women in a cage. They are being watched over by a burly slave hunter named Taker. Their nude bodies are athletic and lithe and they have pert young breasts. All three of them have the same strange sigil branded into their upper left thighs. The of the two most striking things about them the first is that they are neither afraid nor upset; they are observing the camber with obvious curiosity. The second is their appearance; vivid green skin, slim little tusks, yellow eyes and pointed ears. The sign at the base of the cage reads "BEHOLD YE GOBLYNS". You aproch Taker and inquire at his bounty.</AddText>
					<PersonSpeak person="Taker">Court your eye did they? I got these cunts on my last trip; some kind of wild elf I be reckon. Don't speak a word of propper 'Duk; just some heathen jibberjabber. 'Corse lot o me clientele prefure it that way "silent slits bare no tales" as they say.</PersonSpeak>
					<PersonSpeak person="#slavemakername">Do they fuck well; how is their pussies?</PersonSpeak>
					<PersonSpeak person="Taker">Now I aint no nob but I reckon I've had most every kind of pussy. I've had hummies, furries, faeries and moemon. Ive fucked centaurs, kitsunes, catgirls and girls who act catish. Ive porked elven skanks of all colours. I've fucked over I don't rightly know how many slave girls and soon to be slave girls when I've done with them if'n you take my meaning. Pussies a pussy; aint no real tell. Now they fuck well enough; none of that hollerin and bawlin you get when you break in some of the fresh takes.</PersonSpeak>
					<PersonSpeak person="#slavemakername">Where did you find these three if you don't mind?</PersonSpeak>
					<AskQuestions caption='Taker holds out his palm and rubs his thumb.'>
						<Question event='GoblinSlaveEncounter1'>Just look at his hand in askance.</Question>
						<if flagSMBrandGoblins-3="false" Money="25+">
							<Question event='GoblinSlaveEncounter2'>25 gold</Question>
						</if>
						<if Money="100+">
							<Question event='GoblinSlaveEncounter3'>100 gold</Question>
						</if>
						<if flagSMBrandGoblins-4="false" Money="250+">
							<Question event='GoblinSlaveEncounter4'>250 gold</Question>
						</if>
					</AskQuestions>
				</GoblinSlaveEncounterMain>
			</DocksSlavePens>


			<Forest>
				<IntroducingMarek chance="10%" flagSMBrandGoblins-2="true">
					<SetFlags flagSMBrandGoblins-5="true"/>
					<HideImages/>
					<ShowImage image='Images/Events/SMBrandGoblins/FirstForestEncounter.jpg' align='2'/>
					<NoRepeatEvent>IntroducingMarek</NoRepeatEvent>
					<AddText>As you wander deeper and deeper into the forest you spy the smoke of a camp fire. You emerge from the woods into a small glade. Two figures sit by a fire, the smell of roasting meat wafts on the wind.</AddText>
					<PersonSpeak person="Ne'alla">Shark'ren ZEEK! Sol'Vah hadu Ki!</PersonSpeak>
					<AddText>A third person you didn't see is sitting up a tree calls down. She sounds quite young and brash; she has a javelin trained on you.</AddText>
					<PersonSpeak person="Ma'rek">Hail friend, come and sit by the fire; you have nothing you need to fear from us. I am Shak'ren Mar'ek; you may call me Mar'ek. And you are?</PersonSpeak>
					<AddText>The man has a strange accent, guttural vowels yet almost purring on some of the consonants. He is a slim middle aged dark haired green man. He is wearing fur trousers and a brown cloak. You can see the faded tracery of scars on his taught chest.</AddText>
					<PersonSpeak person="#slavemakername">I am #slavemakername and this is my slave #slave; please to meet you Mar'ek</PersonSpeak>
					<PersonSpeak person="Ma'rek">Well met. This is vision of loveliness is my personal slave Rho'shan an'ha and that is my daughter Gho'goa Ne'alla up there.</PersonSpeak>
					<AddText>The nude woman reclining by the fire is obviously a slave; she has a curvaceous figure, ample breasts and a pleasant face figure. Now that your closer you can tell she is a natural blond, she is wearing only collar and is leashed to a stake. She smiles at you like she has something she wants to say only can't. The daughter emergase warily from the shadows, the javelin no longer raised but still at hand. She has slim lithe figure conceled under a thighlength fur wrap; her pert left breast exposed for all to see. Now that you get a better look at her you can see that Ne'alla looks a lot like the slave woman, once you get past the obvious youth, green skin and pointed ears.</AddText>
					<PersonSpeak person="#slavemakername">May I ask what brings you to our land?</PersonSpeak>
					<PersonSpeak person="Ma'rek">I am up from the south; the dark elven lands. I am in the business of trade, scouting for trade more exactly. I am looking for new markets for our wears, new sources of things we need; materials, crafts and slave girls</PersonSpeak>
					<PersonSpeak person="#slavemakername">I think you've come to the right place my friend, Mioya always has plenty of pussy for sale</PersonSpeak>
					<ShowCustomHouse>x_Mareks_Camp</ShowCustomHouse>
				</IntroducingMarek>
			</Forest>
		</Walk>


		<GoblinsYes>
			<SetFlags flagSMBrandGoblins-1="true"/>
			<PersonSpeak person="#slavemakername">We can always do with more variety. I think I should like to see some more of these here "goblins" around these parts.</PersonSpeak>
			<DoEvent>9999</DoEvent>
		</GoblinsYes>
		<GoblinsNo>
			<PersonSpeak person="#slavemakername">Urggh; again? As if I don't have enough to deal with. I've no interest in silly fairy tales. Don't bother me with this nonsense again.</PersonSpeak>
			<DoEvent now="true">9999</DoEvent>
		</GoblinsNo>
		
	<!--   ________________________________________________   GOBLIN ENCOUNTERS START   ______________________________________________________    -->
		<!--Answers for GoblinSlaveEncounterMain - Start-->
		<GoblinSlaveEncounter1>
			<PersonSpeak person="Taker">No; trade secret see. If I blathers all my knowings then I wont have any trade left.</PersonSpeak>
			<DoEvent>9999</DoEvent>
		</GoblinSlaveEncounter1>
		<GoblinSlaveEncounter2>
			<SetFlags flagSMBrandGoblins-3="true"/>
			<PersonSpeak person="Taker">My last trip. I was huntin runaways when I found em</PersonSpeak>
			<Money>-25</Money>
			<DoEvent>9999</DoEvent>
		</GoblinSlaveEncounter2>
		<GoblinSlaveEncounter3>
			<SetFlags flagSMBrandGoblins-2="true"/>
			<SetFlags flagSMBrandGoblins-3="false"/>
			<SetFlags flagSMBrandGoblins-4="false"/>
			<ShowImage image='Images/Events/SMBrandGoblins/000.jpg' align='2'/>
			<PersonSpeak person="Taker">I met this er goobo trader up the woods. I was out huntin for runaways an anything interesting I could bag when I found im. Sold em to I right cheep to. He ad this other skank but e wouldner sell er to I. I er tell o poison shanks with them so I wasn't reckoning to quarrel bout it</PersonSpeak>
			<Money>-100</Money>
			<DoEvent>9999</DoEvent>
		</GoblinSlaveEncounter3>
		<GoblinSlaveEncounter4>
			<SetFlags flagSMBrandGoblins-4="true"/>
			<HideImages/>
			<ShowImage image='Images/Events/SMBrandGoblins/takerstalltale.jpg' align='2'/>
			<PersonSpeak person="Taker">We were down south to those mountains. The lads an me where untin the wild moemon; out to take rare and valuable pussy for the tables of the lord. Any way saw this hot spring. We tried to stalk close -moemon an furries like to frolic in hot springs see so it makes right sense to check em- when we catch sight of this goblin slit a bathin. No sooner do we step out to lay hands on er then twenty of these futa warriors jump us with spear. The five o us were court and trust up. A whole tribe o these things up there; man eating amazons ruled by a bitch queen. One by one they took the lads an I never saw em again; et no doubt. When my turn came up I was put in a ring. I ad to fight their champion; this great rank pig furry. Thought I was dun for then; gods know ow I did it but I kills it. The queen as them let I go an I takes er daughters as trophy. And that's how I nabbed these three cunts.</PersonSpeak>
			<Money>-250</Money>
			<DoEvent>9999</DoEvent>
		</GoblinSlaveEncounter4>
	<!--   ________________________________________________   GOBLIN ENCOUNTERS END   ______________________________________________________    -->
		
	<!--   ________________________________________________   ANNA TALK START   ______________________________________________________    -->
		<ConversationAnna>
			<HideImages/>
			<ShowImage image='Images/Events/SMBrandGoblins/Anna' frame="random5"/>
			<if supervisor="slavemaker">
				<SetText>You and #slave pick your way down the familiar track ways to the camp of the goblin trader. You pick out the faint wisps of smoke leading you to the clearing; you can hear a soft feminine voice singing in the strange goblin tongue. As you emerge from the trees you can see the naked figure of Anna busying herself about the camp but no sign of her master. As soon as she spots you she kneels in silent supplication before you; the slave clearly displaying her ample breasts and soft pussy to you as she waits for you to acknowledge her. </SetText>
				<else>if</else>
					<SetText>#assistant and #slave picks #slavehisher way down the familiar track ways to the camp of the goblin trader. #slaveheshe #slavesee the faint wisps of smoke leading #slavehimher to the clearing;  the naked figure of Anna is busying herself about the camp but there is no sign of her master. Anna warmly greets #slave as soon as she sees #slavehimher. </SetText>
			</if>
			
			<Alternatives>
				<Alternative>
					<AddText>Anna is covered in whip marks. It looks like she has been a very naughty girl lately.\r\r</AddText>
				</Alternative>
				<Alternative>
					<AddText>Anna appears to be shifting around a little. On close inspection she has a bunny tale with a plug.\r\r</AddText>
				</Alternative>
				<Alternative>
					<AddText>Anna has semen on her face and body. Probably just missed her master then.\r\r</AddText>
				</Alternative>
				<Alternative>
					<AddText>Anna appears to have rope marks on her arms and legs as well as across her crotch and breasts. Obviously someone had fun last night.\r\r</AddText>
				</Alternative>
				<Alternative>
					<AddText>Anna is wearing a blindfold. She makes no attempt to remove it.\r\r</AddText>
				</Alternative>
				<Alternative>
					<AddText>Annas hands and feet are bound together\r\r</AddText>
				</Alternative>
				<Alternative>
					<AddText>Annas legs have been bound into a frogtie position.\r\r</AddText>
				</Alternative>
			</Alternatives>

			<if supervisor="slavemaker">
				<PersonSpeak person="#slavemakername">Hello Anna. I've come to visit.</PersonSpeak>
				<PersonSpeak person="Anna">Thank you #slavemakername your visits are always a pleasure. What do you want to talk about today?</PersonSpeak>
				<AskQuestions caption="What do want to know about?">
					<Question event='AnnaTalkAboutGoblins'>Tell me about goblins.</Question>
					<Question event='AnnaTalkAboutHerself'>Tell me about you.</Question>
					<if flagSMBrandGoblins-18="true">
						<Question event='AnnaGoblinLexicon'>Teach me some more words.</Question>
					</if>
					<if flagSMBrandGoblins-6="true">
						<Question event='AnnaGivesHead'>Rhoshan An'ha</Question>
					</if>
					<Question event='AnnaLeave'>Leave her be</Question>
				</AskQuestions>
				<EndEvent/>
			<else>if</else>
				<PersonSpeak person="#assistant">Hello Anna. I've come to visit.</PersonSpeak>
				<PersonSpeak person="Anna">Thank you #assistant your visits are always a pleasure. What do you want to talk about today?</PersonSpeak>
				<AskQuestions>
					<Question event='AnnaSlaveTalk'>Tell me about goblins.</Question>
					<Question event='AnnaBlowTalk'>I'd like to learn</Question>
					<if flagSMBrandGoblins-18="true">
						<Question event='AnnaGoblinLexicon'>Teach me some more words.</Question>
					</if>
					<Question event='AnnaDoesStuff'>Can we do something together</Question>
					<Question event='AnnaLeave'>Leave her be</Question>
				</AskQuestions>
				<EndEvent/>
			</if>
		</ConversationAnna>

		<AnnaLeave>
			<HideImages/>
			<ShowImage image='Images/Events/SMBrandGoblins/LeaveAnna.jpg' align='2'/>
			<SetText>On seeing that Mar'ek is not here you decide to leave. You turn and walk away without acknowledging Anna. She never moves or utters a sound as you go; not even so much as raising her eyes to look at you. Now that is a well disciplined slave.</SetText>
			<Points>
				<Joy>-1</Joy>
				<Temperament>-0.5</Temperament>
				<Obedience>0.5</Obedience>
			</Points>
			<SMPoints>
				<Lust>2</Lust>
			</SMPoints>
			<DoEvent>9999</DoEvent>
		</AnnaLeave>
			
		<AnnaSlaveTalk>
			<Alternatives>
				<Alternate>
					<PersonSpeak person="Anna">There are rules about using another man's slave. I am His. His to use. His to punish. If any other free man wants to have me they need Masters Permission. Of course if a man has rights over the master then he has rights over all that is his; slaves, wives and daughters.</PersonSpeak>
				</Alternate>	
				<Alternate>
					<PersonSpeak person="Anna">All slaves of the same master are sisters. It doesn’t matter what blood connection they may or may not have. A mother and daughter are first, foremost, always and ever sisters in slavery.</PersonSpeak>
				</Alternate>	
				<Alternate>
					<PersonSpeak person="Anna">The word for slave is feminine. It does not matter what equipment “she” may have. All slaves are female and should always think of themselves that way; no matter the evidence otherwise</PersonSpeak>
				</Alternate>	
				<Alternate>
					<PersonSpeak person="Anna">The traditional expression between slaves is “Sal’tis Cor’’da” or pressing lips. It is our kiss of friendship. It’s used to; greet, part, well-wish, apologize, make up, forgive or agree. It can be done with these lips or with or to our “other” pair of lips.</PersonSpeak>
				</Alternate>	
				<Alternate>
					<PersonSpeak person="Anna">Goblins love to see their women “at play”. Slaves can be permitted or given leave to enjoy each other regardless of who owns them or their partners. At celebrations and festivals it is traditional for all slaves and women to be given their leave.</PersonSpeak>
				</Alternate>	
				<Alternate>
					<PersonSpeak person="Anna">Goblins have a far greater variety of shapes than human cocks. Men with human mothers tend to have much more human like cocks however most goblin men have goblin mothers and more goblin like cocks. \r\r When it comes to goblin cocks they can deviate from the standard human norm quite drastically. Some of the most extreme I ever has include prehensile members. Ive had very large nobly cocks that look far too big to fit but will squish down to fit any pussy. Knotted almost canine lick cocks; thats quite common in some tribes. Then you have these ones that are tiny, little finger sized and mostly just skin but when get erect they can grow enormous. \r\r Even some of the more standard shaped cocks can be quite unusual by human standards. Things like warty ridged and even furry shafts, an extra bollix, that kind of thing. Whilst the human shaped knob is the most common it is by no means the majority and their are variations on that as well. Ball shaped, bell shaped and scolloped. Double cocks are by no means rare and I have known more than a few men with two. \r\r I can pretty much tell all the grown men of the tribe from their cocks alone. The Mar'eks uncle had a forskin made of stinging tendrils; that was a really wild ride. The chiefs son has a normal shaped cock but its got taste buds... actual taste buds so not only do you get a tongue like texture inside you but he can taste you pussy whilst he's fucking you. </PersonSpeak>
				</Alternate>	
				<Alternate>
					<PersonSpeak person="Anna">Masters cum is just magic to me. No only did it seed my woomb with Ne'alla and all the other children I have born Him but it has helped make me the slave I am today. Just the smell of His essence makes me gidy and wet for Him. When He showers me with His hot jiz it drives me crazy. When I massage it into my skin its like I am carrying him with me all day. \r\r I love how His salty cream tastes, the way it feels on my tongue, how it goes down as smooth as buttered silk. And when I drink Him its like everything is right with the world, all of the little niggles and doubts just don't seem to matter anymore. If I am ever down I go down and by the time i come up for air I always feel better. \r\r His seed fills me with an inner warmth, a sense of wellness and knowledge that makes His sex all the sweeter for it. If he is gone for more than a few days start to feel anxious, then frantic. Some of the others will share and it helps but I need Him. I don't how I would cope without it, without him. I don't want to.</PersonSpeak>
				</Alternate>	
				<Alternate>
					<PersonSpeak person="Anna">Goblins like to share. They like to pass the pussy around and they love to dogpile on one woman and fuck the living shit out of her. Its a traditional game to them; a way to reinforce the bonds of friendship and brotherhood between them. Its a way to show a woman as sexually belonging to the men of the tribe; literally scent marking her as theirs. A man benefits from sharing his woman in this way as it enhances his status as well as advertises her sale value. Its also a way to prove once and for all who has the biggest cock and knows best how to use it. \r\r For us its kind of a way of showing off. Look at me. Look at my stamina. Look how many men are hard for me, look how many men I can satisfy at once or one after another. For once we get to be the center of attention. I have been in that pile myself more than once and let me tell you it is great fun... exhausting but fun. You have to relax, let them have their way with you, take every cock that's offered you, keep swallowing and just try to breath as best you can. Afterwards the men send their women to massage the worst of the stiffness away and lick clean the sweat and juice. \r\r I remember Ne'allas first time. She wanted to prove herself so badly; to take them all inside her and leave them in the dust. I remember she writhed so beautifully as they took her, how she screamed as they brought her over and over and over again. I knew then that Masters daughter was a woman grown. After when we where "bathing" I could see in her eyes that they had mastered her body and she had loved it, that she was born to be a slave. I was so happy for her.</PersonSpeak>
				</Alternate>	
				<Alternate>
					<PersonSpeak person="Anna">Goblins have tusks or fangs. Some are bigger than others but they are all pretty toothy by human comparison. They keep growing and most goblins have to keep them short by grinding them down. I don't rightly know what they are supposed to be used for but I know a few tricks He puts them to believe me. \r\r Whilst the thought of puting any part of you body between tem might seem a little scary they aren't that big an issue to tell you the truth. The trick is to trust them; they know what they are doing with them and most of the time they are no where near as inconvenient as they seem. When you are up close and oral with one they really don't want to hurt you. Even in the moment of orgasm they arn't going to gore you or take a bite out of you; the angle is all wrong for that. If that was their first instinct? since you cant impregnate a dead woman they would be extinct already.</PersonSpeak>
				</Alternate>	
				<Alternate>
					<PersonSpeak person="Anna">I love Masters hard blunt masculine claws. He uses them so manfully. I am helpless when He holds me down they dig into me fiercely. When He caresses me His hard points graze my most tender parts and take my breath away and I always love to lick pussy juice off His tips. When He fucks me they make me a bitch in heat; I am nothing but a fucking animal under those claws and I love it.</PersonSpeak>
				</Alternate>	
			</Alternatives>
			<DoEvent>9999</DoEvent>
		</AnnaSlaveTalk>
			
		<AnnaDoesStuff> <!-- good luck finding images -->
			<Alternatives>
				<Alternate>
					<AddText>Anna shows #slave how to give #assistant a traditional massage</AddText>
					<Points>
						<Sensitivity>2</Sensitivity>
					</Points>
				</Alternate>
				<Alternate>
					<AddText>Ana shows #slave some practical techniques for cooking on an open fire.</AddText>
					<Points>
						<Cooking>2</Cooking>
					</Points>
				</Alternate>
				<Alternate>
						<AddText>Anna gives #slave a traditional massage</AddText>
						<PersonSpeak person="Anna">This is good for stiff joints; especially after "exertion" whilst bound</PersonSpeak>
						<Points>
							<Tiredness>5-</Tiredness>
						</Points>
				</Alternate>
				<Alternate>
					<AddText>Anna shows #slave some traditional stretching posses.</AddText>
					<PersonSpeak person="Anna"> Masters prize flexible slaves. It is in his interests if his slaves try to become as limber as they possibly can. These positions also help to display our bodies and our abilities for his appreciation and for the admiration of his peers.</PersonSpeak>
					<Points>
						<Tiredness>2</Tiredness>
						<Charisma>1</Charisma>
						<Constitution>2</Constitution>
					</Points>
				</Alternate>
			</Alternatives>
			<DoEvent>9999</DoEvent>
		</AnnaDoesStuff>

		<AnnaBlowTalk>
			<Alternatives>
				<Alternate>
					<PersonSpeak person="Anna">For me giving a blowjob is more than just the mechanical act of sucking a mans cock, much much more. When I kneel before Him He takes my head and places control of His pleasure in my mouth. As a slave it is both a great privilege and a great responsibility. To me fellatio is a willing devotion to his pleasure; a chance to express and submit my creativity to His cock; a chance I relish almost as much as His semen.</PersonSpeak>
				</Alternate>
				<Alternate>
					<PersonSpeak person="Anna">Giving head is one of the most essential skills a slave can have. It is sex but it is different from fucking. When Master fucks you He is taking what he is due. When you blow Him you offer Him what you owe. And that is the difference; you are solely responsible for His pleasure. \r\r Their are a great many techniques that can be employed. You can do things for your Master with your mouth that is simply impossible for most women's pussies; though I have kissed a few that can kiss back. Your mouth can kiss, nip, suckle, nibble, lick, bite and swallow. Like any techniques they can be learned and refined through study and practice.</PersonSpeak>
				</Alternate>
				<Alternate>
					<PersonSpeak person="Anna">Men love blowjobs. For many men good head is simply better than sex. For as long as men own slaves slave will perform oral sex on them. I have blown most every cock in the tribe; many besides and his most of all. Fellatio is one of His favorite kinds of sex and one of mine. \r\r I have served Master for my entire adult life. I believe I was born to be His slave; my purpose in life is His service. The mouth of a slave exists to give pleasure; My mouth exists for Masters pleasure. Your mouth is an extension of your pussy, its purpose is to receive His cock and His cum. It is a great gift; use it wisely.</PersonSpeak>
				</Alternate>
				<Alternate>
					<PersonSpeak person="Anna">Any idiot can suck a cock but a good blow job requires more. Oral sex is sex; He may be having sex with your mouth but in the end the whole of you is serving Him. Unless prevented you should use your body, your hands, your eyes, your voice, your very breath itself and most of all your mind to enhance his experience. A good blowjob is a performance art; enjoyed as much with the eyes and the ears as it is with the cock.</PersonSpeak>
				</Alternate>
				<Alternate>
					<PersonSpeak person="Anna">It requires at skill and a good attitude to give a good blowjob. Skills can be taught. A good attitude must be instilled in a slave either with good advice and an effort of will or at the end of a whip; your choice. \r\r The right attitude is the right thinking. You need to learn to enjoy it..to show that you enjoy it, to show that you are grateful for His cock. That can be a problem for some slaves. Some women and many men simply don't enjoy it. They don't like the taste, they find the very idea degrading and repugnant. As a slave that is not an option. You don't have a choice. You must serve and serve well or face punishment. \r\r And this is where willpower comes into play. The mind is malleable and can be made to bend under pressure. If you find you have a problem with sucking cocks then I say to you lie to yourself. Tell yourself you like giving head, that you want this. Tell yourself you enjoying, pleasure yourself as you think of it, as you do it . Associate the act in your mind with things you do find pleasurable, associate the taste of him with something you love. Tell yourself these things often enough and hard enough and eventually you will come to believe them; eventually they will become the truth. You will become a better slave for it.</PersonSpeak>
				</Alternate>
				<Alternate>
					<PersonSpeak person="Anna">There is a real difference between performing a blowjob as a free woman and as a slave. Fellatio places a free woman in charge. She is the one in control; he is passive and pleasured whilst she is actively orally pleasing him because she wants to. As a slave its not the same. Your master is still your master regardless. His needs are absolute; its not about what you want. \r\r If your master wants you to eagerly and enthusiastically serve serve him then have at it. If he wants you to meekly submit to his every command then do so. If he wants to humiliate you then allow yourself to feel pride degraded. If he wants to violate you then call upon your disgust and revulsion. </PersonSpeak>
				</Alternate>
				<Alternate>
					<PersonSpeak person="Anna">The human mouth is a wonderful pleasure giving organ but it has its limitations. The most sensitive part of the penis is the head and the most effective way you have to pleasure it is with the front of your mouth; however he will want to feel like he is fucking you so will be inclined to thrust his cock to its full length.To combat this I recommend first going all the way down as you can and then backing off and wrapping your hand firmly around and masturbating the shaft. Doing this on and off will allow you to limit and control the depth of penetration at the same time as allowing your mouth to better simulate your pussy. \r\r A sustained blowjob can take over an hour but you need to breathe, after a while your jaw will ache and your performance drop. I can tell you the most effective way of dealing with this is to give your mouth a break. Remove his cock and apply it to the outside; working on his balls, kissing his shaft and licking and nibbling the perineum, head and foreskin are all excellent techniques.</PersonSpeak>
				</Alternate>
				<Alternate>
					<PersonSpeak person="Anna">Orally pleasuring more than one cock at the same time is not easy but by no means impossible. If possible you should go from one penis to the other and use both hands to keep up the momentum. If more than one cock is in your mouth at once then your options are really limited. You don't have room to work your lips or your tongue properly, you don't have a seal for good suction and they can't get the angle to thrust.</PersonSpeak>
				</Alternate>
				<Alternate>
					<PersonSpeak person="Anna">The actual act of sucking a futanari cock is basically the same however their are differences of. Whilst performing oral sex on a futa it is wise to remember her pussy. You can alternate between cock sucking and cunt licking however some futa will get offended by that. One thing to remember is that the join between the pussy and the folds inside the cock are highly sensitive; if she has a true clit then it'll be in there.</PersonSpeak>
				</Alternate>
				<Alternate>
					<PersonSpeak person="Anna">When performing a blowjob there is no need to rush to the finish. Orgasm may be the destination but you have absolutely no need to rush. Take your time, savor the sensation...the sweat kiss of your lips on His cock. You will please Him greatly and as a slave that should be your highest goal. However unless he decides to fuck you that destination will be reached. \r\r He will cum and a a slave you won't always be able decide where. It depends on the man and his feelings but he could cum all over your face and/or breasts, he could cum in your mouth, he could plunge Himself home and cum straight down your throat or he might flip you over and cum in or over your pussy or ass; all are valid. Master often likes me to lean back; he cums across my face and into my open mouth. I show him what I have managed to catch, how delicious it is and then...hmmn yes and then I get to swallow it all down.</PersonSpeak>
				</Alternate>
				<Alternate>
					<PersonSpeak person="Anna">One of the best things about giving a blowjob is that Master does not need to be hard. He could be tired, or busy or even still asleep. His cock might be spent and dripping fresh juice and seed from a pussy and I can still suck it. When he is soft I love how he feels in my mouth. And I like how I can take him all and close my lips round his balls; you can't do that when he is hard.</PersonSpeak>
				</Alternate>
				<Alternate>
					<PersonSpeak person="Anna">Men like having two slaves pleasure their cock at once. They don't physically get that much more pleasure from two mouths as one however its the visuals of having two women mouthing their dick, the sense of power it gives them that does the trick. Sharing cock is a joy. Some of my fondest memories are of helping Ne'alla as well as my eldest daughter to learn and practice it; whenever I see her we always pleasure her master together. \r\r The technique is to have one take the head in her mouth and the other to work her mouth on the shaft and balls. Since you have no real room for your hands you use them to play with yourself and your partner. This also works if he is fucking one of you with a pussy taking the place of one of the mouths. You can also kiss each other and have his cock in the middle going back and forth. After he cums then its time to share. You lick the semen from each others faces and suckle it from her breasts or pussy. When you have cum in your mouth you kiss and share it; making sure you both show the Master before you swallow together. </PersonSpeak>
				</Alternate>
			</Alternatives>
			<Points>
				<Blowjob>3</Blowjob>
			</Points>
			<DoEvent>9999</DoEvent>
		</AnnaBlowTalk>
		
		<AnnaTalkAboutGoblins>
			<AskQuestions caption='What would you like to hear'>
				<Question event='AnnaTalkAboutGoblinsRandom'>I want to hear something new</Question>
				<if flagSMBrandGoblins-19="true">
					<Question event='LanguageBarrier'>1</Question>
				</if>
				<if flagSMBrandGoblins-20="true">
					<Question event='AnnaOnMaids'>2</Question>
				</if>
				<if flagSMBrandGoblins-21="true">
					<Question event='AnnaOnPublicSex'>3</Question>
				</if>
				<if flagSMBrandGoblins-22="true">
					<Question event='AnnaOnAnimism'>4</Question>
				</if>
				<if flagSMBrandGoblins-23="true">
					<Question event='AnnaOnCannibalism'>5</Question>
				</if>
				<if flagSMBrandGoblins-24="true">
					<Question event='AnnaOnFurries'>6</Question>
				</if>
				<if flagSMBrandGoblins-27="true">
					<Question event='AnnaOnNudity'>7</Question>
				</if>
				<Question event='9999'>On second thoughts lets not</Question>
			</AskQuestions>		
		</AnnaTalkAboutGoblins>		
		<AnnaTalkAboutGoblinsRandom>
			<if flagSMBrandGoblins-19="true" flagSMBrandGoblins-20="true" flagSMBrandGoblins-21="true" flagSMBrandGoblins-22="true" flagSMBrandGoblins-23="true" flagSMBrandGoblins-24="true" flagSMBrandGoblins-27="true">
				<SetText></SetText>
				<PersonSpeak person="Anna">I'm sorry, but I have nothing new to tell about goblins.</PersonSpeak>
				<DoEvent>AnnaTalkAboutGoblins</DoEvent>
				<EndEvent/>
			</if>
			<Alternatives>
				<Alternative flagSMBrandGoblins-19="false">
					<DoEvent now="true">LanguageBarrier</DoEvent>
				</Alternative>
				<Alternative flagSMBrandGoblins-20="false">
					<DoEvent now="true">AnnaOnMaids</DoEvent>
				</Alternative>
				<Alternative flagSMBrandGoblins-21="false">
					<DoEvent now="true">AnnaOnPublicSex</DoEvent>
				</Alternative>
				<Alternative flagSMBrandGoblins-22="false">
					<DoEvent now="true">AnnaOnAnimism</DoEvent>
				</Alternative>
				<Alternative flagSMBrandGoblins-23="false">
					<DoEvent now="true">AnnaOnCannibalism</DoEvent>
				</Alternative>
				<Alternative flagSMBrandGoblins-24="false">
					<DoEvent now="true">AnnaOnFurries</DoEvent>
				</Alternative>
				<Alternative flagSMBrandGoblins-27="false">
					<DoEvent now="true">AnnaOnNudity</DoEvent>
				</Alternative>
			</Alternatives>		
		</AnnaTalkAboutGoblinsRandom>

		<AnnaTalkAboutHerself>
			<AskQuestions caption='What would you like to hear'>
				<Question event='AnnaTalkAboutHerselfRandom'>I want to hear something new</Question>
				<if flagSMBrandGoblins-7="true">
					<Question event='AnnaFullName'>1</Question>
				</if>
				<if flagSMBrandGoblins-10="true">
					<Question event='HowIBecameHis'>2</Question>
				</if>
				<if flagSMBrandGoblins-17="true">
					<Question event='HowIBecameAnna'>3</Question>
				</if>
				<if flagSMBrandGoblins-13="true">
					<Question event='TheTasteOfHome'>4</Question>
				</if>
				<if flagSMBrandGoblins-8="true">
					<Question event='AnnaOnSlavePsychologyAndPresenceOfMind'>5</Question>
				</if>
				<if flagSMBrandGoblins-9="true">
					<Question event='RhoshanAhna'>6</Question>
				</if>
				<if flagSMBrandGoblins-11="true">
					<Question event='HisBrand'>7</Question>
				</if>
				<if flagSMBrandGoblins-12="true">
					<Question event='OnHerRelationshipWithNealla'>7</Question>
				</if>
				<if flagSMBrandGoblins-14="true">
					<Question event='AnnaOnPregnancy'>7</Question>
				</if>
				<if flagSMBrandGoblins-15="true">
					<Question event='AnnaOnGoingHome'>7</Question>
				</if>
				<if flagSMBrandGoblins-16="true">
					<Question event='MastersPrize'>7</Question>
				</if>
				<if flagSMBrandGoblins-28="true">
					<Question event='BreakingThePrize'>7</Question>
				</if>
				<Question event='9999'>On second thoughts lets not</Question>
			</AskQuestions>		
		</AnnaTalkAboutHerself>
		<AnnaTalkAboutHerselfRandom>
			<if flagSMBrandGoblins-7="true" flagSMBrandGoblins-10="true" flagSMBrandGoblins-17="true" flagSMBrandGoblins-13="true" flagSMBrandGoblins-8="true" flagSMBrandGoblins-9="true" flagSMBrandGoblins-11="true" flagSMBrandGoblins-12="true" flagSMBrandGoblins-14="true" flagSMBrandGoblins-15="true" flagSMBrandGoblins-16="true" flagSMBrandGoblins-28="true" >
				<SetText></SetText>
				<PersonSpeak person="Anna">I'm sorry, but I have nothing new to tell about me.</PersonSpeak>
				<DoEvent>AnnaTalkAboutHerself</DoEvent>
				<EndEvent/>
			</if>
			<Alternatives>
				<Alternative flagSMBrandGoblins-7="false">
					<DoEvent now="true">AnnaFullName</DoEvent>
				</Alternative>
				<Alternative flagSMBrandGoblins-10="false">
					<DoEvent now="true">HowIBecameHis</DoEvent>
				</Alternative>
				<Alternative flagSMBrandGoblins-17="false">
					<DoEvent now="true">HowIBecameAnna</DoEvent>
				</Alternative>
				<Alternative flagSMBrandGoblins-13="false">
					<DoEvent now="true">TheTasteOfHome</DoEvent>
				</Alternative>
				<Alternative flagSMBrandGoblins-8="false">
					<DoEvent now="true">AnnaOnSlavePsychologyAndPresenceOfMind</DoEvent>
				</Alternative>
				<Alternative flagSMBrandGoblins-9="false">
					<DoEvent now="true">RhoshanAhna</DoEvent>
				</Alternative>
				<Alternative flagSMBrandGoblins-11="false">
					<DoEvent now="true">HisBrand</DoEvent>
				</Alternative>
				<Alternative flagSMBrandGoblins-12="false">
					<DoEvent now="true">OnHerRelationshipWithNealla</DoEvent>
				</Alternative>
				<Alternative flagSMBrandGoblins-14="false">
					<DoEvent now="true">AnnaOnPregnancy</DoEvent>
				</Alternative>
				<Alternative flagSMBrandGoblins-15="false">
					<DoEvent now="true">AnnaOnGoingHome</DoEvent>
				</Alternative>
				<Alternative flagSMBrandGoblins-16="false">
					<DoEvent now="true">MastersPrize</DoEvent>
				</Alternative>
				<Alternative flagSMBrandGoblins-28="false">
					<DoEvent now="true">BreakingThePrize</DoEvent>
				</Alternative>
			</Alternatives>
		</AnnaTalkAboutHerselfRandom>

		<AnnaGoblinLexicon>
			<for start="0" end="3">
				<if loop="0">
					<SetVar var1="random5"/>
				</if>
				<if loop="1">
					<SetVar var1="random5+5"/>
				</if>
				<if loop="2">
					<SetVar var1="random5+10"/>
				</if>
				<Choices>
					<Choice var1="1">
						<PersonSpeak person="Anna">Shak’ren - It essentially means master. It also means lover or love, owner, husband and HIM. Its basically assumed that if a women says him then without a given context their can only be one him she is referring to. For me he is my alpha, my omega, the centre of my being. I would give anything and everything to him, for him. I am his absolute slave, mind, body and soul; I live only to serve his needs and pleasure. I wouldn’t have it any other way and I hope that nothing changes in the afterlife; for me an eternity of serving him would be paradise. He is Shak’ren and I am his.</PersonSpeak>
					</Choice>
					<Choice var1="2">
						<PersonSpeak person="Anna">Va’kesh - Literally means I am or I belong. With the emphasis it means young woman or girl without the emphasis it means slave. In human I would say “I am a slave woman” in Goblak I can say all that just with “Vakesh”. There is no need to specify a slaves gender as all slaves are automatically considered feminine. Va’kesh’Lyn is the goblak word for a young or junior wife and Va’kesh’muti the one for mother or matron; I will let you figure out what the lack of emphasis signifies for those two.</PersonSpeak>
					</Choice>
					<Choice var1="3">
						<PersonSpeak person="Anna">Sol’vah/Sol’kesh - This word sol’vah roughly translates to human but it also implies fool or thoughtless. It literally means hunted one. Without the emphasis it means animal; especially game animals like dear and rabbits.\r\rI cannot identify myself as human in goblak as I am no longer hunted. Sol’kesh means one who belongs and is a special word for to people like me; slaves and/or clients. Without the emphasis it means livestock such as cattle or swine. Sol’vah’lyn means target and Sol’kesh’muti means breeding stock.</PersonSpeak>
					</Choice>
					<Choice var1="4">
						<PersonSpeak person="Anna">Sol’Shin - Sol’Shin literally means the hunter. It is the goblak word for a wood elf. Without the emphasis it essential means wolf or predator. Shin’kesh is the word used for an elven slave; without the emphasis it means “dog” or in the feminine “bitch”.</PersonSpeak>
					</Choice>
					<Choice var1="5">
						<PersonSpeak person="Anna">Dresh’kel - It literally translates to “fire birth”. It means to marry or name, without the emphasis it means to brand or enslave, it implies ownership, renewal and rebirth. A Dresh’kel’ta is a wedding or formal branding ceremony.</PersonSpeak>
					</Choice>
					<Choice var1="6">
						<PersonSpeak person="Anna">Go’Bak - This is the word for goblak; the goblin tongue. It means speech but it also Implies wisdom. Its spoken from the diaphragm. Words are built up from particles and the smoothness, emphasis or inflection of the word as well as its context can change its meaning. As you can imagine this is a barrier to the written word.</PersonSpeak>
					</Choice>
					<Choice var1="7">
						<PersonSpeak person="Anna">Taka’taka’taka - This is the word for all human languages. The word literally translates to foolishness or without emphasis; noise.</PersonSpeak>
					</Choice>
					<Choice var1="8">
						<PersonSpeak person="Anna">Ne'alla - It means love; specifically a woman’s love for her man. It also means submission or obedience. I cannot say that I love the Master without saying I obey him as well. Without the emphasis it means lust for a man, arousal and female sexuality. I can't say that I feel arousal without also saying I submit.</PersonSpeak>
					</Choice>
					<Choice var1="9">
						<PersonSpeak person="Anna">Torn'esh - Tradition, discipline, respect, teaching. It also means whip. When used as a verb then in the masculine tense it means he whips and in the feminine she is whipped.\rVa'kesh apt Torn'esh: I am taught\rVakesh apt Tornesh dis: I (slave) am being whipped/I respect\rShak'ren Tornesh Aye'kesh: Whip(teach) me(slave) master</PersonSpeak>
					</Choice>
					<Choice var1="10">
						<PersonSpeak person="Anna">Kroas - Put simply penis or cock. It also means club, authority and (Verb) domination. Single particle as its an important word. It implies action and is a very popular component of boys names. Masters brother has earned the name Gor'than Kroas; "mighty authority" or "large penis" which believe me is an understatement.\rIf I say that I want or love master cock I also say that I love or want to be dominated.</PersonSpeak>
					</Choice>
					<Choice var1="11">
						<PersonSpeak person="Anna">Kesh - It specificity means female and also refers to pussy. It implies being, fertility and subservience. Its very common in girls names; for example shak'rens first daughter was named eL'eu Kesh "water girl" or alternately "wet pussy".</PersonSpeak>
					</Choice>
					<Choice var1="12">
						<PersonSpeak person="Anna">Sha'han - Meaning the love of a man for his women. It implies domination and command. Without the emphasis it means erection. Its also a common boys name.</PersonSpeak>
					</Choice>
					<Choice var1="13">
						<PersonSpeak person="Anna">Kek'kiss - It means pleasure or indulgence. Without emphasis it means clitoris. When used as a verb it means orgasm or surrender. It is also a very common name for girls and slaves; Masters nephew has a human slave girl he has branded Ti'ra Kekkis or Honey (sweat) clit.</PersonSpeak>
					</Choice>
					<Choice var1="14">
						<PersonSpeak person="Anna">Sken'di - Semen; also means blessing. It implies right, need or responsibility.</PersonSpeak>
					</Choice>
					<Default>
						<PersonSpeak person="Anna">Ke'ind - Meaning womb. It implies motherhood; maternal instinct, nurturing. It also means duty or purpose. The wife of the chief was branded Sha'ki'ind (lit:his womb) by the husband at his wedding.</PersonSpeak>
					</Default>
				</Choices>
			</for>
			<DoEvent>9999</DoEvent>
		</AnnaGoblinLexicon>
	<!--   ________________________________________________   ANNA TALK END   ______________________________________________________    -->
	
	<!--   ________________________________________________   MAREK TALK START   ______________________________________________________    -->	
		<ConversationMarekMain>
			<ShowImage image='Images/Events/SMBrandGoblins/CampMarekWelcome.jpg' align='2'/>
			<AddText>Your footsteps lead you down the paths to the forest camp of the family Mar'ek. The air smells of wood smoke and exotic herbs. Mar'ek is sitting by his fire; tending it with a prod and the ocational log. He calls out in grettings to you.</AddText>
			<AddText>Looking around for Anna you see her </AddText>
			<Alternatives>
				<Alternative>
					<AddText>preparing food.</AddText>
				</Alternative>
				<Alternative>
					<AddText>in bondage.</AddText>
				</Alternative>
				<Alternative>
					<AddText>in a post sex stupor.</AddText>
				</Alternative>
				<Alternative>
					<AddText>caged.</AddText>
				</Alternative>
			</Alternatives>
			<PersonSpeak person="Ma'rek">Zeeke! #slavemakername hello. Come; sit with me awhile.</PersonSpeak>
			<AskQuestions>
				<if flagSMBrandGoblins-39="true" flagSMBrandGoblins-42="true">
					<Question event='MarekDoubletrouble'>Mar'ek there is some think I need to talk to you about. Its about #slave and me. We're pregnant Mar'ek.</Question>
				</if>
				<if flagSMBrandGoblins-42="true">
					<Question event='SlavepregMarek'>Marek we need to talk...#slaveis pregnant; we think its yours.</Question>
				</if>
				<if flagSMBrandGoblins-39="true">
					<Question event='PregnantProposition'>Marek we need to talk...I'm pregnant; its yours.</Question>
				</if>
				<Question event='MarekTalksAboutGoblins'>I'd like to hear more about your people.</Question>
				<Question event='MarekStorytime'>Tell me a story Mar'ek.</Question>
				<if flagSMBrandGoblins-43="false">
					<Question event='MarekFuck'>I am here for a good time Mar'ek.</Question>
				<else>if</else>
					<Question event='YourMedicine'>Would you like your medicine now #slavemaker?.</Question>
				</if>
				<Question event='MarekDrink'>I am always up for a good drink.</Question>
				<Question event='FertilityDrugMain'>The fertility drug sounds interesting.</Question>
				<Question event='9999'>Leave</Question>
			</AskQuestions>
		</ConversationMarekMain>
		
		<MarekTalksAboutGoblins>
			<ShowImage image='Images/Events/SMBrandGoblins/MarekTalkGoblin.jpg' align='2'/>
			<SetText></SetText>
			<PersonSpeak person="Ma'rek">What would you like to hear about?</PersonSpeak>
			<AskQuestions>
				<Question event='MarekTalksAboutGoblinsRandom'>I want to hear something new</Question>
				<if flagSMBrandGoblins-50="true">
					<Question event='MarekonSlavery'>1</Question>
				</if>
				<if flagSMBrandGoblins-51="true">
					<Question event='MarekonEssentialism'>1</Question>
				</if>
				<if flagSMBrandGoblins-52="true">
					<Question event='MarekonLove'>1</Question>
				</if>
				<if flagSMBrandGoblins-53="true">
					<Question event='MarekonSex'>1</Question>
				</if>
				<if flagSMBrandGoblins-54="true">
					<Question event='MarekonSexuality'>1</Question>
				</if>
				<if flagSMBrandGoblins-55="true">
					<Question event='MarekonFamily'>1</Question>
				</if>
				<if flagSMBrandGoblins-56="true">
					<Question event='MarekonIncest'>1</Question>
				</if>
				<if flagSMBrandGoblins-57="true">
					<Question event='MarekonSize'>1</Question>
				</if>
				<if flagSMBrandGoblins-58="true">
					<Question event='MarekonTentacles'>1</Question>
				</if>
				<if flagSMBrandGoblins-59="true">
					<Question event='MarekontheUseofTentacles'>1</Question>
				</if>
			</AskQuestions>
		</MarekTalksAboutGoblins>
		<MarekTalksAboutGoblinsRandom>
			<if flagSMBrandGoblins-50="true" flagSMBrandGoblins-51="true" flagSMBrandGoblins-52="true" flagSMBrandGoblins-53="true" flagSMBrandGoblins-54="true" flagSMBrandGoblins-55="true" flagSMBrandGoblins-56="true" flagSMBrandGoblins-57="true" flagSMBrandGoblins-58="true" flagSMBrandGoblins-59="true">
				<SetText></SetText>
				<PersonSpeak person="Ma'rek">I'm sorry, but I have nothing new to tell about Goblins.</PersonSpeak>
				<DoEvent>MarekTalksAboutGoblins</DoEvent>
				<EndEvent/>
			</if>
			<Alternatives>
				<Alternative flagSMBrandGoblins-50="false">
					<DoEvent now="true">MarekonSlavery</DoEvent>
				</Alternative>
				<Alternative flagSMBrandGoblins-51="false">
					<DoEvent now="true">MarekonEssentialism</DoEvent>
				</Alternative>
				<Alternative flagSMBrandGoblins-52="false">
					<DoEvent now="true">MarekonLove</DoEvent>
				</Alternative>
				<Alternative flagSMBrandGoblins-53="false">
					<DoEvent now="true">MarekonSex</DoEvent>
				</Alternative>
				<Alternative flagSMBrandGoblins-54="false">
					<DoEvent now="true">MarekonSexuality</DoEvent>
				</Alternative>
				<Alternative flagSMBrandGoblins-55="false">
					<DoEvent now="true">MarekonFamily</DoEvent>
				</Alternative>
				<Alternative flagSMBrandGoblins-56="false">
					<DoEvent now="true">MarekonIncest</DoEvent>
				</Alternative>
				<Alternative flagSMBrandGoblins-57="false">
					<DoEvent now="true">MarekonSize</DoEvent>
				</Alternative>
				<Alternative flagSMBrandGoblins-58="false">
					<DoEvent now="true">MarekonTentacles</DoEvent>
				</Alternative>
				<Alternative flagSMBrandGoblins-59="false">
					<DoEvent now="true">MarekontheUseofTentacles</DoEvent>
				</Alternative>
			</Alternatives>
		</MarekTalksAboutGoblinsRandom>


		<MarekonSlavery>
			<SetFlags flagSMBrandGoblins-50="true"/>
			<ShowImage image='Images/Events/SMBrandGoblins/MarekTalkGoblin.jpg' align='2'/>
			<PersonSpeak person="Ma'rek">You my dear are a slave. You are a slave for a reason; either through your own choices or the hand fate dealt you, you find yourself in bondage. You need to discover within yourself the reason you were placed here, learn from it, accept it; it is a part of what you are.</PersonSpeak>
			<PersonSpeak person="Ma'rek">You are no longer free, like as not will never know freedom. Your slavery is now the defining aspect of who you are. You need to understand and embrace it. If you cannot accept yourself, if you cannot be happy in of yourself; you will never know happiness.</PersonSpeak>
			<DoEvent>9999</DoEvent>
		</MarekonSlavery>

		<MarekonEssentialism>
			<SetFlags flagSMBrandGoblins-51="true"/>
			<ShowImage image='Images/Events/SMBrandGoblins/MarekTalkGoblin.jpg' align='2'/>
			<PersonSpeak person="Ma'rek">I follow the essential tradition. It is perhaps the most enlightened aspect of high goblin culture. Human heads are full useless nonsense. Ideas like nobility, honour, nation, pride and property. Liabilities in stray humans these are absolutely unacceptable in a slave. They get in the way of humans becoming fulfilled slaves; becoming fully owned beings. As a master I have a responsibility to my slaves to teach them right; to grind these petty stupidities out.</PersonSpeak>
			<AddText>He lovingly caresses Anna's back before playfully slapping her ass. She gives a muffled yelp around his raging hard on.</AddText>
			<PersonSpeak person="Ma'rek">It took nearly a year of tears, sweat and cum to polish away the rough edges and train her up to be a good little slave. Many more years under my care to bring out the beautiful, vivacious cunt you see before you. The simplicity and purity of her being is what make her my most valued possession.</PersonSpeak>
			<AddText>You see Anna wiggle her frogtide behind to lustily display her pussy. Her busy mouth purring in pleasure as she greedily gulps down on her masters cock. </AddText>
			<DoEvent>9999</DoEvent>
		</MarekonEssentialism>

		<MarekonLove>
			<SetFlags flagSMBrandGoblins-52="true"/>
			<ShowImage image='Images/Events/SMBrandGoblins/MarekTalkGoblin.jpg' align='2'/>
			<PersonSpeak person="Ma'rek">Love isn’t a trade, it’s not something you exchange and get something back for, nor is it an investment you get a return on. Love is… unconditional; its own reward. Nor is it finite, you always have more love to give.</PersonSpeak>
			<PersonSpeak person="Ma'rek">A real man loves his children unconditionally and would burn the world to protect them. A real slave loves her master unconditionally and without reserve; without expecting or demanding that he love her in return. Should she be sold then she should certainly love her new master but that does not mean that she should ever stop loving her old one. A slave cannot serve two masters but that does not mean she cannot love them all.</PersonSpeak>
			<DoEvent>9999</DoEvent>
		</MarekonLove>

		<MarekonSex>
			<SetFlags flagSMBrandGoblins-53="true"/>
			<ShowImage image='Images/Events/SMBrandGoblins/MarekTalkGoblin.jpg' align='2'/>
			<PersonSpeak person="Ma'rek">Love is not about sex; sex is a part of it but it is also apart from it and it is not necessary to it. I love my daughters but I wouldn’t</PersonSpeak>
			<AddText> He is interrupted when Ne'alla interjects over him; gesticulating suggestively</AddText>
			<PersonSpeak person="Ne'alla">Not True! What about all those times when you...</PersonSpeak>
			<AddText>He silences her with a warning look</AddText>
			<PersonSpeak person="Ma'rek">Ahem...Fine; bad example. I love and respect my brother but I do not...</PersonSpeak>
			<PersonSpeak person="Anna">Addha Al’dis co Ve…EEK!</PersonSpeak>
			<AddText>THWAK! The cane went swiftly to her ass, a second strike administered to Ne'alla for good measure</AddText>
			<PersonSpeak person="Ma'rek">AHEM!... Does NOT count. AS I was saying before these impertinent females so rudely interrupted me sex is good and all but as a slave you cannot and should not equate it to love. You will most likely be having sex with people you don’t love and do not or will never love you. Furthermore it is perfectly possible for you to love someone and never be permitted to be with them. That is your lot in life and it’s as true for a free man as it is for a slave girl; the only difference is you are free of the responsibility that goes with choice</PersonSpeak>
			<DoEvent>9999</DoEvent>
		</MarekonSex>

		<MarekonSexuality>
			<SetFlags flagSMBrandGoblins-54="true"/>
			<ShowImage image='Images/Events/SMBrandGoblins/MarekTalkGoblin.jpg' align='2'/>
			<PersonSpeak person="Ma'rek">As a slave you are free from the burden of certain choices; your sexuality being amongst them. I recommend you try to be flexible and keep an open mind to new experiences. If you are sold to a woman then it is highly likely that you mistress will desire you skills for herself as the kind of woman to buy a female sex slave tends to be of a certain persuasion.</PersonSpeak>
			<PersonSpeak person="Ma'rek">Even if you are only ever possessed by a man you should still expect to enjoy homosexual acts. This may be because you will have to serve a hospitality for your master female acquaintances or simply because it pleases your master to watch you embrace another woman.</PersonSpeak>
			<DoEvent>9999</DoEvent>
		</MarekonSexuality>

		<MarekonFamily>
			<SetFlags flagSMBrandGoblins-55="true"/>
			<ShowImage image='Images/Events/SMBrandGoblins/MarekTalkGoblin.jpg' align='2'/>
			<PersonSpeak person="Ma'rek">You’re a slave now; classic ideals of family virtue don’t really apply to you anymore. Your first priority is the service of your master and nothing must get in the way of that.</PersonSpeak>
			<PersonSpeak person="Ma'rek">Any children you bear your master are first and foremost his children and not yours. If he should acknowledge you as their mother than that is his right but you should not expect it. You should cherish them as his children; if he chooses to enslave them then that is his prerogative and you should cherish them as his property.</PersonSpeak>
			<PersonSpeak person="Ma'rek">As a slave the only family you are allowed to acknowledge is what it pleases your master to permit you. Even when two members of the same family are owned by the one master maintain a relationship between them can be difficult.</PersonSpeak>
			<PersonSpeak person="Ma'rek">Furthermore even if your relatives are free or enslaved to a different master it does not mean this can never happen. Many nobles like to acquire a matching set as it where and if they value highly enough may seek to take ownership of your family members. You should take that as a complement and try your best to aid him in this.</PersonSpeak>
			<DoEvent>9999</DoEvent>
		</MarekonFamily>

		<MarekonIncest>
			<SetFlags flagSMBrandGoblins-56="true"/>
			<ShowImage image='Images/Events/SMBrandGoblins/MarekTalkGoblin.jpg' align='2'/>
			<PersonSpeak person="Ma'rek">Slaves might have extended contact with a friend or family member because her master is extraordinarily affectionate and it pleases him to do so. It is most common in house slaves where entire families have served one house for generations.</PersonSpeak>
			<PersonSpeak person="Ma'rek">It can also be because the slave has free range and has the latitude to keep a family; this is more the case when a master owns many slaves -including entire families- and they live apart from him.</PersonSpeak>
			<PersonSpeak person="Ma'rek">Finally it can also be because their master enjoys having his slaves engage in incestuous acts. This is most relevant to your situation as it is one of the few ways someone not born to slavery can keep in touch with her relatives. If it pleases your master you must be ready and willing to do it.</PersonSpeak>
			<DoEvent>9999</DoEvent>
		</MarekonIncest>

		<MarekonSize>
			<SetFlags flagSMBrandGoblins-57="true"/>
			<ShowImage image='Images/Events/SMBrandGoblins/MarekTalkGoblin.jpg' align='2'/>
			<PersonSpeak person="Ma'rek">You humans are far too hung up on size. It’s not a competition; you are who you are. Men love breasts but most men are not fixated on massive mammories as anything more than a silly fantasy. I myself prefer smaller bosoms; “anything more than a mouthful is a waste” as they say. Your master will have chosen you knowing you knowing your size and if it’s good enough for him then who are you to argue?</PersonSpeak>
			<PersonSpeak person="Ma'rek">Enjoy your breasts; they will give you and your master pleasure, they will nourish his children. They are a gift of the earth mother.</PersonSpeak>
			<DoEvent>9999</DoEvent>
		</MarekonSize>

		<MarekonTentacles>
			<SetFlags flagSMBrandGoblins-58="true"/>
			<ShowImage image='Images/Events/SMBrandGoblins/MarekTalkGoblin.jpg' align='2'/>
			<PersonSpeak person="Ma'rek">Ah the beasts. I can understand your trepidation about tentacles but should the beasts take you they will not harm you. The best advice I can give you is to be of such value to you master as that he will be willing to rescue you.</PersonSpeak>
			<PersonSpeak person="Ma'rek">We have ways and means of dealing with them. They can smell women and are drawn to sex and violence. We use burning herbs to stupefy them and mask our scents with salves. Should you ever need help against them you can come to use; for a price. Mostly they are not normally are not normally more than a nuisance for us menfolk. If not …well it is hardly a fate worse than death.</PersonSpeak>
			<DoEvent>9999</DoEvent>
		</MarekonTentacles>

		<MarekontheUseofTentacles>
			<SetFlags flagSMBrandGoblins-59="true"/>
			<ShowImage image='Images/Events/SMBrandGoblins/MarekTalkGoblin.jpg' align='2'/>
			<PersonSpeak person="Ma'rek">My own people have a history with the tentacles. Their fluids have many valuable medicinal and magical properties and we have long used them. Why Anna here was a fine young man when I “acquired” him and it was through the use of tentacle extracts that we turned her into the vision of beauty you see here before you.</PersonSpeak>
			<PersonSpeak person="Ma'rek">Way back west the cities have breeding farms and most tribes keep a tentacle pit. Out here we can’t get settled enough to pull it off; besides I think it would strain the hospitality of the drow. We hunt them and trade their fluids instead.</PersonSpeak>
			<AddText>Mar’ek indicates a cluster of earthenware jars and sealed pots.</AddText>
			<PersonSpeak person="Ma'rek">If you are interested in some of my wears I could be persuaded to part with some; for a fee of course</PersonSpeak>
			<DoEvent>9999</DoEvent>
		</MarekontheUseofTentacles>

		<!--	<MarekTalkAboutMarek>   
				<Choices>
					<Choice flagSMBrandGoblins-7="false">
						<DoEvent now="true">xxx</DoEvent>
					</Choice>
				</Choices>
			</MarekTalkAboutMarek> -->

		<MarekFuck>
			<DoEvent now="true">GoblinSlaveSwap</DoEvent>
		</MarekFuck>

		<GoblinSlaveSwap>
			<SetText>One of the worst sins for a slave is jealousy. You don’t own yourself, you don’t own your master; you have no right to be jealous. You have no right to decide with whom you do or don’t sleep with. When I was teaching Anna this lesson I made her fuck as many men and women as possible. I ground into her that she’s my property and that I require her to fuck anyone on command; she knows she should put her back into it. I take pleasure in other women and she knows that she needs to be happy for my pleasure.</SetText>
			<AskQuestions>
				<ifnot slavegender="male">
					<Question event='GoblinMarekOnSlave'>Mar’ek fucks your slave</Question>
				</ifnot>
				<Question event='GoblinAnnaOnSlave'>Anna fucks your slave</Question>
				<ifnot gender="male">
					<Question event='GoblinMarekOnSM'>Mar’ek on female/herm slavemaker</Question>
				</ifnot>
				<if gender="female">
					<Question event='GoblinFemaleSMOnAnna'>Female slavemaker on Anna</Question>
				</if>
				<ifnot gender="female">
					<Question event='GoblinMaleSMOnAnna'>Male/Herm slavemaker on Anna</Question>
				</ifnot>
			</AskQuestions>
		</GoblinSlaveSwap>
		<GoblinMarekOnSlave>
			<HideImages/>
			<ShowImage image='Images/Events/SMBrandGoblins/MarekOnSlave' align='2'/>
			<AddText>Mar’ek sits her on his lap and strips her off as he tenderly kisses her. He then puts her on all fours and fucks her as he fingers her clit with one hand and controls her head with the other; forcing her to watch as Anna performs a long slow oral on your sex.</AddText>
			<DoEvent now="true">GoblinSlaveSwapEnd</DoEvent>
		</GoblinMarekOnSlave>
		<GoblinAnnaOnSlave>
			<HideImages/>
			<ShowImage image='Images/Events/SMBrandGoblins/AnnaOnSlave' align='2'/>
			<AddText>Anna kisses your slave and works her way down #slavehisher body to #slavehisher </AddText>
			<if slavegender="female">
				<AddText>pussy. </AddText>
			<else>if</else>
				<if slavegender="male">
					<AddText>cock. </AddText>
				<else>if</else>
					<AddText>cock and pussy. </AddText>
				</if>
			</if>
			<AddText>She performs oral sex on your slave bringing #slavehisher screaming over and over again.</AddText>
			<DoEvent now="true">GoblinSlaveSwapEnd</DoEvent>
		</GoblinAnnaOnSlave>
		<GoblinMarekOnSM>
			<HideImages/>
			<ShowImage image='Images/Events/SMBrandGoblins/MarekOnSM.jpg' align='2'/>
			<AddText>Anna holds your slave and forces her to watch as you fuck Mar’ek. He lies back as you perform a blowjob on him to get his dick good and hard. Then you mount up on his groin and impale yourself over and over on his cock, his calloused hands massaging your breasts and fondling your nipples.
			You feel #slave's eyes over your nude body as you writhe and pound yourself silly. Whilst you might be doing this for her benefit you don’t spare her the affirmation of a glance; instead your eyes are locked on the lucky goblin between your thighs. You hear a gasp behind you as lean over and give Mar’ek a lingering kiss. He grunts beneath you and you feel his see shooting out to cream your pussy.</AddText>
			<DoEvent>GoblinSlaveSwapEnd</DoEvent>
		</GoblinMarekOnSM>
		<GoblinFemaleSMOnAnna>
			<HideImages/>
			<ShowImage image='Images/Events/SMBrandGoblins/FemaleSMOnAnna' align='2'/>
			<AddText>Anna is in her own way still a very beautiful woman. You feel that her bronzed body is strong and limber from the exertions of her servitude. The shock of greying hair at her temples nor the slight wrinkles around her eyes do not detract from her loveliness.
			Your tongue can taste the soft blond strands of pubic hair that mound atop her moist pussy. You can feel her skill as she playfully nips and suckles on your nether lips. You can tell by the juices in your mouth and by the clenching of her vagina that she is enjoying this almost as much as you are.
			To one side you can hear your slave gasp and pant as Mar’ek fingers her to yet another orgasm as she watches you. The though spills you over the abyss and you drench Annas face in your juices.</AddText>
			<DoEvent>GoblinSlaveSwapEnd</DoEvent>
		</GoblinFemaleSMOnAnna>
		<GoblinMaleSMOnAnna>
			<HideImages/>
			<ShowImage image='Images/Events/SMBrandGoblins/MaleSMOnAnna' align='2'/>
			<AddText>Anna is in her own way still a very beautiful woman. You feel that her bronzed body is strong and limber from the exertions of her servitude. The shock of greying hair at her temples nor the slight wrinkles around her eyes do not detract from her loveliness.
			Belly to belly she is unselfconscious and totally assured in your arms. The command to fuck has been made and this slave woman gives herself over to it and to you with great gusto and consummate skill. You can feel her cunt clench rhythmically around the thrust of your cock as though milking you, her shapely thighs anchoring you deep in her pussy.
			To one side you can hear your slave gasp and pant as Mar’ek fingers her to yet another orgasm as she watches you. The though spills you over the abyss and you poor your jizz into Anna.</AddText>
			<DoEvent>GoblinSlaveSwapEnd</DoEvent>
		</GoblinMaleSMOnAnna>
		<GoblinSlaveSwapEnd>
			<ShowImage image='Images/Events/SMBrandGoblins/SwapEnd' align='2'/>
			<PersonSpeak person='Marek'>I enjoyed that. Because it pleases me it should please you too. Being jealous is possessiveness, selfish; it’s the last thing a good slave should feel. My body is mine to use and share as I see fit. Your body is mine to use and share as I see fit. This kind of thing happens and is likely to keep happening as long as you are a slave. I would rather you learned to enjoy it rather than suffer. So did you have fun as well?</PersonSpeak>
		</GoblinSlaveSwapEnd>
	<!--   ________________________________________________   MAREK TALK END   ______________________________________________________    -->


	<!--   ________________________________________________   GENERAL GOBLIN CAMP EVENT START   ______________________________________________________    -->
		<GeneralEventsCamp>
			<Alternatives>
				<Alternative>
					<DoEvent now="true">windingwood</DoEvent>
				</Alternative>
				<Alternative>
					<DoEvent now="true">wippinggirl</DoEvent>
				</Alternative>
				<Alternative>
					<DoEvent now="true">FlagrentDelectio</DoEvent>
				</Alternative>
			</Alternatives>
		</GeneralEventsCamp>
		
		<windingwood>
			<ShowImage image='Images/Events/SMBrandGoblins/lost in the woods.jpg' align='2'/>
			<AddText>You enter the woods trying to find mar’eks camp. You suppose you must of taken a wrong turn somewhere along the way because this track does not lead to where you wanted to go. After more than an hour of wandering around in circles you give up and make the long trek for home tired and despondent.</AddText>
			<Points>
				<Joy>-1</Joy>
				<Tiredness>2</Tiredness>
			</Points>
			<DoEvent>9999</DoEvent>
		</windingwood>
		<wippinggirl>
			<ShowImage image='Images/Events/SMBrandGoblins/Wipping Anna.jpg' align='2'/>
			<AddText>As you approach the camp you hear the shrill cries of a woman in pain. Hurrying closer you see Mar’ek standing by the bound figure of Anna. He has eschewed his customary cane for a bundle of bitch twigs and is beating Anna with some vigour.</AddText>
			<AskQuestions>
					<Question event='wippinggirl1'>I've seen enough</Question>
					<Question event='wippinggirl2'>I want to see more</Question>
			</AskQuestions>
		</wippinggirl>
		<wippinggirl1>
			<AddText>Its not for you to judge a man for disciplining his slave. You turn and leave; the Swish CRACK of the birch and her moans growing fainter as you depart.</AddText>
			<DoEvent>9999</DoEvent>
		</wippinggirl1>
		<wippinggirl2>
			<AddText>#Slave can’t tear her eyes from the tableau before her. Mar’ek alternates between heavy and light stokes, quick and slow, sometimes focused strikes and sometimes scattergun as he shifts his target between her back, thights, ass, breasts and pussy. Her moans are muffled by a stick tied as a bit.\r\r
			His exertions have caused him to raised quite a sweat. Pressing the birch against Annas face he lifts her head, removes the gag and says something to her softly.</AddText>
			<PersonSpeak person="Anna"> Anha ampt If’ty Solkesh. Ipt’na; Shak'ren TORNESH Aye'KESH!</PersonSpeak>
			<AddText>With a smile of satisfaction Mar’ek raises his birch and returns it with a meaty smack right across her branded arse. Anna screams out wrenching and sagging against her bonds; her legs drenched with her fluids.\r\r 
			You think you have seen quite enough and leave.</AddText>
			<DoEvent>9999</DoEvent>
		</wippinggirl2>
		<FlagrentDelectio>
			<ShowImage image='Images/Events/SMBrandGoblins/MarekOnAnna.jpg' align='2'/>
			<AddText>You come across the camp. Mar’ek has mounted Anna and is fucking his slave with long deliberate stoke of his cock into her. She is lying face down in the furs, her ass presented for her masters pleasure; her almost inhuman moans of ecstasy muffled by the ground; yipping with every thrust.\r
			You feel you are intruding on a private moment and leave the grove. </AddText>
			<DoEvent>9999</DoEvent>
		</FlagrentDelectio>
	<!--   ________________________________________________   GENERAL GOBLIN CAMP EVENT START   ______________________________________________________    -->
	

	<!--   ________________________________________________   GOBLIN ALE START   ______________________________________________________    -->	
		<MarekDrink>
			<ShowImage image='Images/Events/SMBrandGoblins/AleWelcome.jpg' align='2'/>
			<AddText>You meet Mar’ek at his camp and he offers you to come and sit and share his fire awhile. He puts on a pot of what smells like a rich earthy wine. When asked he offers you a drinking horn.</AddText>
			<PersonSpeak person="Ma'rek">This is Sej’Kesh -goblin ale; it’s very warming and best drunk piping hot. You might like to try some but be careful; it’s quite potent if your not used to it.</PersonSpeak>
				<AskQuestions caption='Want some?'>
					<Question event='NoDrink'>None for me</Question>
					<Question event='SMDrinkAle'>Yeah; I'll drink</Question>
					<Question event='SlaveDrinkAle'>#Slave; Try this</Question>
					<Question event='BothDrinkAle'>Sounds good; lets drink up #slave</Question>
				</AskQuestions>	
		</MarekDrink>			

		<NoDrink>
			<ShowImage image='Images/Events/SMBrandGoblins/AleNoDrink.jpg' align='2'/>
			<AddText>You turn him down. You leave him to enjoy his drink with his slave</AddText>
			<DoEvent>9999</DoEvent>
		</NoDrink>

		<SMDrinkAle>
			<if smlust="69+" smdominance="0" flagSMBrandGoblins-34="true">
				<DoEvent now="true">SMBingedrink</DoEvent>
			<else>if</else> <SetFlags flagSMBrandGoblins-34="true"/>
				<if smlust="69+">
					<DoEvent now="true">SMDrunksex</DoEvent>
				<else>if</else>
					<ShowImage image='Images/Events/SMBrandGoblins/AleDrink.jpg' align='2'/> <!-- maybe vary with how drunk aka how low dominance or high lust -->
					<AddText>It tastes hearty, savoury-salty, warming; like an alcoholic broth. You can feel the blood rushing to every part of you; filling you with vigor. You feel a little giddy; yea -potent.</AddText>
					<SMPoints>
						<Lust>10</Lust>
						<Dominance>-2</Dominance> 
						<Tiredness>2</Tiredness>
					</SMPoints>	
					<AskQuestions caption='want some?'>
						<Question event='NoDrink'>None for me</Question>
						<Question event='SMDrinkAle'>Yeah; I'll drink</Question>
						<Question event='SlaveDrinkAle'>#Slave; Try this</Question>
						<Question event='BothDrinkAle'>Sounds good; lets drink up #slave</Question>
					</AskQuestions>	
				</if>
			</if>
		</SMDrinkAle>
		
		<SMDrunksex>
			<SetText>You feel …hot. Your skins all a tingle. You begin to rub yourself moaning before you latch on to Mar’ek pawing and kissing him; unable to control yourself. He laughs.</SetText>
			<ifnot gender="male">
				<ShowImage image='Images/Events/SMBrandGoblins/AleSMDrunkSexFemale.jpg' align='2'/>
				<PersonSpeak person="Ma'rek">She's half cooked. Shall we finish this bird off by trussing her up and roasting her by the fire?</PersonSpeak>
				<AddText>Together Mar’ek and #slave help you out of your clothes and manoeuvre you onto all fours. With one strong hand Mar’ek caresses and controls your backside whilst the other skilfully jils your clitoris. #Slave grabs you by the hair and</AddText>
				<ifnot slavegender="female">
					<AddText>forces #slavehisher cock into your mouth; allowing you to suckle at it between fucking your face</AddText>
				<else>ifnot</else>	
					<AddText>grinds your face into her pussy, leaving you no choice but to part your lips and plunge your tongue into her folds.</AddText>
				</ifnot>
				<AddText>You almost choke as you feel Mar’ek rod gingerly slip into you and finding your pussy eager ram itself in all the way to the balls. With smooth slow forceful movements he pistons himself into you and the waves of pleasure roll up from your vagina, shuddering up your body before earthing themselves through your mouth into #slave. Mar’eks tempo builds faster and faster and finally expending himself as he crashes his sex into you and implanting his hot seed straight into the core of your being.</AddText>
				<if canimpregnate-slavemaker="Goblin"> 
					<if chance="10%">
						<Impregnate person='slavemaker' type='Goblin' count='1' gestation='20+random20'/>		
					</if>
				</if>
			<else>ifnot</else>
			<ShowImage image='Images/Events/SMBrandGoblins/AleSMDrunkSexMale.jpg' align='2'/>
				<PersonSpeak person="Ma'rek">Together Mar’ek and #Slave help you out of your clothes and manoeuvre you onto all fours. With one hand #slave caresses and controls your backside whilst the other skilfully strokes your cock. #slaveheshe slowly works #slavehisher way into your asshole.
				As you gasp Mar’ek you by the hair and slips his cock into your mouth; at first allowing you to suckle and play with it.\r\r
				You nearly choke as you feel Mar’ek tilt your head back and force himself in all the way to the balls. With smooth slow forceful movements he pistons himself as he fucks your face. Mar’eks tempo builds faster and faster, #slave keeping time with him as #slaveheshe sodomises you. Finally he expends himself as he crashes his sex into you and fills your mouth with the taste of his cum.\r\r</PersonSpeak>	
			</ifnot>
			<SMPoints>
				<Lust>-15</Lust>
				<Dominance>-5</Dominance> 
				<Tiredness>5</Tiredness>
				<Nymphomania>3</Nymphomania>  
			</SMPoints>
			<DoEvent>9999</DoEvent>
		</SMDrunksex>

		<SMBingedrink>
			<ShowImage image='Images/Events/SMBrandGoblins/AleSMDrunkDecide.jpg' align='2'/>
			<AddText>More. You want more, you NEED more, you must have MORE. Guzzle all of the ale but its still not enough. You dive for Mar’ek crotch desperate to drink his seed. You urgently suck his cock wanting, needing him in you. He withdraw himself at the last second to blow his load across you face and into your thirsty mouth. Somehow the taste of his semen on your tongue eases your desperate craving enough for you to speak.</AddText>
			<PersonSpeak person="#slavemakername"> Please, please please… Got to have some. Anything you want just please give me more</PersonSpeak>
			<AskQuestions caption='Anything? I want want you. Give yourself to me and I’ll see you get what you need.'>
				<Question event='GimmeGimmeGimme'>Yes yes YES. Take me, take me, TAKE ME Mar’ek. I am yours</Question>
				<Question event='Anythingbutthat'>No, just no…anything but that</Question>
			</AskQuestions>
		</SMBingedrink>
		
		<GimmeGimmeGimme>
			<ShowImage image='Images/Events/SMBrandGoblins/AleSMDrunkDecideBad.jpg' align='2'/>
			<PersonSpeak person="Mar'ek">Good, good; and you must call me Shak’ren now, you master insists</PersonSpeak>
			<if badends='true'>
				<DoEvent now="true">Marekslavebadend</DoEvent>
			<else>if</else>
				<DoEvent now="true">MareksNotEnd</DoEvent>
			</if>
		</GimmeGimmeGimme>
		
		<Anythingbutthat> <SetFlags flagSMBrandGoblins-34="false"/>
			<ShowImage image='Images/Events/SMBrandGoblins/AleSMDrunkDecideGood.jpg' align='2'/>
			<PersonSpeak person="Mar'ek">Then I am sorry but I have to cut you off tonight. Go home; get some rest. You will feel better in a few days</PersonSpeak>
			<AddText>You feel rotten and dejected; gradualy doing your best to crawl away from the camp and its enticing, arousing, enthralling drink.</AddText> 
			<SMPoints>
				<Lust>-15</Lust>
				<Dominance>3</Dominance> 
				<Tiredness>8</Tiredness>
				<Nymphomania>3</Nymphomania>  
			</SMPoints>
			<DoEvent>9999</DoEvent>
		</Anythingbutthat>

		<SlaveDrinkAle>
			<if lust="80+">
				<DoEvent now="true">Slavedrunk</DoEvent>
			<else>if</else>
				<ShowImage image='Images/Events/SMBrandGoblins/AleSlaveDrink.jpg' align='2'/>
				<AddText>You fill the horn and hand it to #slave. #slaveheshe first sips it then drinks it with great gusto. You see #slavehisher blush as #slaveheshe giggles and wipes #slavehisher mouth; #slaveheshe seems a little light headed.</AddText>
				<Points>
					<Lust>10</Lust>
					<Nymphomania>3</Nymphomania>
					<Intelligence>-2</Intelligence>
					<Temperament>-2</Temperament>
				</Points>

				<AskQuestions caption='Want some more?'>
					<Question event='NoDrink'>No more for me</Question>
					<Question event='SMDrinkAle'>Yeah; I'll have another</Question>
					<Question event='SlaveDrinkAle'>#Slave; your turn</Question>
					<Question event='BothDrinkAle'>Sounds good another round for me and #slave Mar'ek if you please</Question>
				</AskQuestions>	
			</if>
		</SlaveDrinkAle>		

		<Slavedrunk><!-- need version for female SM an futa slave -->
			<SetText> #slave begins to rub herself moaning before #slaveheshe latches on to Mar’ek pawing and kissing him; unable to control herself. He laughs.</SetText>
			<PersonSpeak person="Ma'rek">#slaveheshe's half cooked. Shall we finish this bird off by trussing #slavehimher up and roasting #slavehimher by the fire?</PersonSpeak>
			<if gender='1'>
				<ShowImage image='Images/Events/SMBrandGoblins/AleSlaveSexSMmale.jpg' align='2'/>
				<AddText>Together you and Mar’ek help #slave out of #slavehisher clothes and put #slave on #slavehisher back. With one hand you caresses her nipples whilst the other</AddText>
					<if slavegender="female">
						<AddText>jils her clitoris</AddText>
						<else>if</else>
							<AddText>strokes #slavehisher cock. </AddText>
					</if>
				<AddText>Mar’ek spreads #slavehisher thighs, lines himself up and shoves his cock inside #slavehimher. You feel #slavehisher frantic tongue lashing hold time with Mar’eks rhythm. In silent agreement he finishes deep inside #slave as you cum; drizzling your jiz down #slavehisher chin</AddText>
				<if chance="50%">
					<AddText> In silent agreement he finishes deep inside #slave as you cum; drizzling your jiz down #slavehisher chin</AddText>
					<if canimpregnate-slave="Goblin">
						<if chance="10%">
							<Impregnate person='slave' type='Goblin' count='1' gestation='20+random20'/>
						</if>
					</if>
					<else>if</else>
						<AddText>and fuck #slavehimher in time to Mar’eks rhythm. In silent agreement you both withdraw as you finish drenching #slavehisher face tits and abdomen in thick ropes of your cum.</AddText>
				</if>
			</if>
			<if gender='2'>
				<ShowImage image='Images/Events/SMBrandGoblins/AleSlaveSexSMfemale.jpg' align='2'/>
				<AddText>Together you and Mar’ek help #slave out of #slavehisher clothes and put #slave on #slavehisher back. You caresses #slavehisher nipples whilst you sit on #slavehisher face. Mar’ek spreads #slavehisher thighs, lines himself up and shoves his cock inside #slavehimher. You feel #slavehisher frantic tongue lashing hold time with Mar’eks rhythm. In silent agreement he finishes deep inside #slave as you cum; floding your juices down #slavehisher chin</AddText>
			</if>
			<if gender='3'>
				<ShowImage image='Images/Events/SMBrandGoblins/AleSlaveSexSMfuta.jpg' align='2'/>
				<AddText>Together you and Mar’ek help #slave out of #slavehisher clothes and put #slave on #slavehisher back. With one hand you caresses her nipples whilst the other</AddText>
					<if slavegender="female">
						<AddText>jils her clitoris</AddText>
						<else>if</else>
							<AddText>strokes #slavehisher cock. </AddText>
					</if>
				<AddText>Mar’ek spreads #slavehisher thighs, lines himself up and shoves his cock inside #slavehimher. You feel #slavehisher frantic tongue lashing hold time with Mar’eks rhythm.</AddText>
				<if chance="50%">
					<AddText> In silent agreement he finishes deep inside #slave as you cum; drizzling your jiz down #slavehisher chin</AddText>
					<if canimpregnate-slave="Goblin">
						<if chance="10%">
							<Impregnate person='slave' type='Goblin' count='1' gestation='20+random20'/>
						</if>
					</if>
					<else>if</else>
						<AddText>and fuck #slavehimher in time to Mar’eks rhythm. In silent agreement you both withdraw as you finish drenching #slavehisher face tits and abdomen in thick ropes of your cum.</AddText>
				</if>
			</if>
					
			<Points>
				<Lust>-5</Lust>
				<Nymphomania>3</Nymphomania>
				<Intelligence>-2</Intelligence>
				<Temperament>-2</Temperament>
				<Fuck>2</Fuck>
				<BlowJob>2</BlowJob>
			</Points>
			<DoEvent>9999</DoEvent>
		</Slavedrunk>
		
		<BothDrinkAle>
			<if smlust="69+" smdominance="0" flagSMBrandGoblins-34="true">
				<DoEvent now="true">SMBingedrink</DoEvent>
				<else>if</else>	<SetFlags flagSMBrandGoblins-34="true"/>
					<ifnot slavegender="male" gender="male" smlust="69-" lust="70-">
						<DoEvent now="true">DrunkThreesome</DoEvent>
					</ifnot>
					<else>if</else>
						<ifnot gender="male" smlust="68-">
							<DoEvent now="true">SMDrunksex</DoEvent>
						</ifnot>
						<else>if</else>
							<ShowImage image='Images/Events/SMBrandGoblins/Ale2Drink.jpg' align='2'/>
							<AddText>It tastes hearty, savoury-salty, warming; like an alcoholic broth. You can feel the blood rushing to every part of you; filling you with vigor. You feel a little giddy; yea -potent.</AddText>
							<Points>
								<Lust>10</Lust>
								<Nymphomania>3</Nymphomania>
								<Intelligence>-2</Intelligence>
								<Temperament>-2</Temperament>
							</Points>
							<SMPoints>
								<Lust>10</Lust>
								<Dominance>-5</Dominance>
								<Nymphomania>2</Nymphomania>
							</SMPoints>
							<AskQuestions caption='Want some more?'>
								<Question event='NoDrink'>No more for me</Question>
								<Question event='SMDrinkAle'>Yeah; I'll have another</Question>
								<Question event='SlaveDrinkAle'>#Slave; your turn</Question>
								<Question event='BothDrinkAle'>Sounds good another round for me and #slave Mar'ek if you please</Question>
							</AskQuestions>	
			</if>
		</BothDrinkAle>
		
		<DrunkThreesome>
			<ShowImage image='Images/Events/SMBrandGoblins/Ale3some.jpg' align='2'/>
			<AddText>You feel …hot. Your skins all a tingle, your breasts ache to be fondled, squeezed sucked, your pussy is screaming with an urgent demand to be fucked. You begin to rub yourself moaning before you  and #slave latch on to each other pawing and kissing and clawing at your clothing; unable to control yourself. Mar’ek laughs.</AddText>
			<PersonSpeak person="Mar'ek">Mind if I cut in? I think I have something you need right here</PersonSpeak>
			<AddText>He lays you down next to #slave; mounting over you. He kisses you whilst fondling #slave’s pussy, jilling her clit and plunging his fingers deep inside her. The look in his eyes isn’t askance; he looks at you with a dark possession; absolute ownership of your pussy as he takes you with his dick. He plunges his cock over and over inside injecting his claim straight to your womb.</AddText>
				<if canimpregnate-slavemaker="Goblin"> 
					<if chance="10%">
						<Impregnate person='slavemaker' type='Goblin' count='1' gestation='20+random20'/>		
					</if>
				</if>
			<Points>
				<Lust>-15</Lust>
				<Nymphomania>3</Nymphomania>
				<Intelligence>-2</Intelligence>
				<Temperament>-2</Temperament>
				<Fuck>2</Fuck>
				<BlowJob>2</BlowJob>
			</Points>
			<SMPoints>			
				<Lust>-15</Lust>
				<Dominance>-5</Dominance>
				<Nymphomania>2</Nymphomania>
			</SMPoints>
			<DoEvent>9999</DoEvent>
		</DrunkThreesome>
	<!--   ________________________________________________   GOBLIN ALE END   ______________________________________________________    -->


	<!--   ________________________________________________   GOBLIN FERTILITY DRUG START   ______________________________________________________    -->
		<FertilityDrugMain>
			<ShowImage image='Images/Events/SMBrandGoblins/Drug.jpg' align='2'/>
			<PersonSpeak person="Mar’ek">We like to be in charge; masters of ourselves and our environment. It’s an important part of who we are. Nature does he own thing; we study and understand nature because it gives us the illusion of control. Sometimes through understanding we learn true control.</PersonSpeak>
			<PersonSpeak person="Mar’ek">Long ago we learned to master women; to control her mind, to dominate her life, to possess her body. Add to that we know the secrets to impose our will over female fertility. I don’t just mean contraceptives or watching the moon. We know how to make a slave receptive to seed at her masters convenience.</PersonSpeak>
			<PersonSpeak person="Mar’ek">Each family has its own formula; its own fertility medicine. I can’t speak to effectiveness of them all but I can guarantee mine works; albeit it’s much more potent when fresh. For a price I can make some up for your slave and administer it myself now or for you to take away and use later.</PersonSpeak>

			<AskQuestions>
				<Question event='ConversationMarekMain'>No thank you; another time perhaps</Question>
				<Question event='FertilityDrugAnswerTwo'>I’ll have some for later</Question>
				<Question event='FertilityDrugAnswerThree'>Yes I’d like some for my slave</Question>
				<ifnot gender="male">
					<Question event='FertilityDrugAnswerFour'>For…me… please?</Question>
				</ifnot>
			</AskQuestions>
		</FertilityDrugMain>

		<FertilityDrugAnswerTwo>                       <!--Needs effect-->
			<HideImages/>
			<ShowImage image='Images/Events/SMBrandGoblins/Drugforhome.jpg' align='2'/>
			<PersonSpeak person="Mar’ek">Taking a pestle and mortar Mar’ek begins gathering grinding and mixing ingredients. “Lets see; …Honey …Pine nut flower …Mint … Sol milk …Nin’shin venom … Fern spores and my own special ingredient; Rhoshan Ah’na</PersonSpeak>
			<AddText>With that his slave drops to her knees and immediately administer a blowjob to her master before spitting the resultant load into the pot.\r\rMar’ek seal the potion and hands to you.</AddText>
			<PersonSpeak person="Mar’ek">Its one dose taken oraly, takes effect almost immediately and lasts for up to a day. Let me know how it works out for you.</PersonSpeak>
			<DoEvent>9999</DoEvent>
		</FertilityDrugAnswerTwo>

		<FertilityDrugAnswerThree>                     <!--Needs effect - still text missing!-->
			<AskQuestions>
				<if gender="female">
					<Question event='FertilityDrugAnswerThreeA'>I think you’ll have to handle it.</Question>
				</if>
				<ifnot gender="female">
					<Question event='FertilityDrugAnswerThreeB'>I’ll take it from here</Question>
				</ifnot>
				<Question event='FertilityDrugAnswerThreeA'>You do the honours; I insist.</Question>
			</AskQuestions>
		</FertilityDrugAnswerThree>
		<FertilityDrugAnswerThreeA>                     <!--Needs effect-->
			<HideImages/>
			<ShowImage image='Images/Events/SMBrandGoblins/DrugSlaveGoblin.jpg' align='2'/>
			<AddText>Smiling mischievously the goblin gently parts #slave's thighs with firm caresses to expose her moist and twitching sex to lay his still soft manhood against it. Mar’rek presses her arms firmly to the earth as he softly kisses and nips up the side of her neck to whisper sweet nothings in her ear.\r\r</AddText>
			<AddText>Mar’ek pulls back a little and greedily swallows her screams of pleasure as his throbbing dick penetrates her spamming pussy and works its way in down to his balls fucking her briskly her to a shuddering orgasm before filling her belly with his hot seed. #slave's orgasms strongly and looks up at him happily. Mar’ek gets up from his work satisfied and in a good mood offers you a discount.</AddText>
			<PersonSpeak person="Mar’ek">It’s absolutely no problem at all; I’m happy to help.</PersonSpeak>
			<if chance="30%">
				<Impregnate type='Goblin' count='1' gestation='20+random20'/>
			</if>
			<DoEvent>9999</DoEvent>
		</FertilityDrugAnswerThreeA>
		<FertilityDrugAnswerThreeB>                     <!--Needs effect-->
			<HideImages/>
			<ShowImage image='Images/Events/SMBrandGoblins/DrugSlave.jpg' align='2'/>
			<AddText>You caress and sooth your slave as you expose and fondle her hardening nipples and sodden pussy. You hold her down as she bucks and thrashes to the rhythm of your pounding cock; orgasming strongly as you seed her womb.\r\rYou thank the goblin for his potion and help your slave unsteadily to her feet before leading her home.</AddText>
			<if chance="30%">
				<Impregnate type='Yours'/>
			</if>
			<DoEvent>9999</DoEvent>
		</FertilityDrugAnswerThreeB>

		<FertilityDrugAnswerFour>                     <!--Needs effect - still text missing!-->
			<HideImages/>
			<ShowImage image='Images/Events/SMBrandGoblins/DrugSM.jpg' align='2'/>
			<PersonSpeak person="Mar’ek">So you wish to experience the joys of motherhood for yourself? It would be my honour and my pleasure to help you do that. Now let me see; …Honey …Pine nut flower …Mint … Sol milk …Nin’shin venom … Fern spores …ah that’s almost everything</PersonSpeak>
			<AddText>He said as he ground the ingredients to a thin paste.</AddText>
			<PersonSpeak person="Mar’ek">Your sure about this? Yes? Good</PersonSpeak>
			<AddText>Mar’ek says as he draws you into his arms. Looking into your eyes he gently kisses your lips; conquering your mouth with his skilled tongue. Holding the cup up to your lips he softly says to “drink”. The look he gives you compels you drink the almost sickly sweet fluid.\r\r</AddText>
			<AddText>You feel the effects almost immediately. A great golden warmth centred on your womb spreads out to fill your being. Your skin feels hyper sensitive and your clothes rough and restraining. You feel you pulse race and begin to pant heavily as if you had just run a mile. Dizzy you fall to your knees before Mar’ek.\r\r</AddText>
			<AddText>Griping you hair in one hand he takes out his eager manhood with the other. The smell of it is incredible to you. You can’t help yourself as you rub your face in his groin and peck and lick at his genitals. Controlling you by your hair he pulls you head back to look up at him and caresses his swollen gland against your face; glossing you sensitive lips with precum. “Drink” he says as he thrusts his thick shaft between you quivering lips and into your throat. It’s all you can do to swallow down on your saliva as he fucks your face.\r\r</AddText>
			<AddText>You when his rich earthy jism explodes from his cock to seep over your tongue and down your neck you feel the change in your body instantly. The warmth of the drug erupts into a hot needy fire suffusing your being. The tingling building between your legs begins to spasm urgently demanding attention and drenching your panties in a flood of juices. Your legs cut out from beneath you and you fall writhing to the ground tearing at your clothes wanting –no needing to be naked; to be seen, to be touched, to be held, to be fondled and fingered and kissed and groped and fucked. You can barely assemble to words yet your somehow manage to cry out.</AddText>
			<AskQuestions>
				<Question event='FertilityDrugAnswerFourA'>Fuck me! fuck me! I want cu-COCK. Gods. Ju-jus-just FUCK ME!</Question>
				<ifnot slavegender="female">
					<Question event='FertilityDrugAnswerFourB'>#slave please, please, please I NEED you.</Question>
				</ifnot>
			</AskQuestions>
		</FertilityDrugAnswerFour>
		<FertilityDrugAnswerFourA>                     <!--Needs effect - still text missing!-->
			<HideImages/>
			<ShowImage image='Images/Events/SMBrandGoblins/DrugSMGoblin.jpg' align='2'/>
			<PersonSpeak person="Mar’ek">Gladly</PersonSpeak>
			<AddText>His eager hands running over your body kindling your passion and striping you of your remaining clothes. Gesturing to the slaves to restrain your arms he firmly grips your legs and leavers apart your thighs before pinning your twitching crotch beneath his weight. Fondling your breasts and kissing up from them over your neck to your ear as you writhe and grind yourself against him.</AddText>
			<PersonSpeak person="Mar’ek">This feeling, this wanting, this needing; this is how a woman should feel. I could make you feel like this over and over again were you mine</PersonSpeak>
			<AddText>Mar’ek jams his meaty shaft into your eager womanhood; slamming himself into your body over and over and over again until he can bare it no more and his seed burst forth; greedily milked by your vagina to quench the fire burning in your anticipating womb. You orgasm very strongly and feel a deep sense of satisfaction as you feel his semen filling you.</AddText>
			<PersonSpeak person="Mar’ek">You could feel this way all the time; were you my slave</PersonSpeak>
			<AddText>Mar’ek helps you to your feet and wishes you the best of luck in conceiving. He insists that this time is free though he doesn’t like to make a habit of just giving things away.</AddText>
			<if chance="50%">
				<Impregnate person='slavemaker' type='Goblin' count='1' gestation='20+random20'/>
			</if>
			<DoEvent>9999</DoEvent>
		</FertilityDrugAnswerFourA>
		<FertilityDrugAnswerFourB>                     <!--Needs effect-->
			<HideImages/>
			<ShowImage image='Images/Events/SMBrandGoblins/DrugSMSlave.jpg' align='2'/>
			<AddText>Rolling you over and pushing you to all fours #slave exposes your pussy and forcefully enters you. The pounding of their firm shaft swiftly fucks you to orgasm and your spasaming pussy milks their cum for your waiting womb and quenching the lust that grips you.\r\rYou kiss #slavehimher as you help each other up. You get the feeling that neither of you are going to get much sleep tonight.</AddText>
			<AddText>Rolling you over and pushing you to all fours #slave exposes your pussy and forcefully enters you. The pounding of their firm shaft swiftly fucks you to orgasm and your spasaming pussy milks their cum for your waiting womb and quenching the lust that grips you.\r\rYou kiss #slavehimher as you help each other up. You get the feeling that neither of you are going to get much sleep tonight.</AddText>
			<if chance="50%">
				<Impregnate slave='Slavemaker' type='Human'/>
			</if>
			<DoEvent>9999</DoEvent>
		</FertilityDrugAnswerFourB>
	<!--   ________________________________________________   GOBLIN FERTILITY DRUG END   ______________________________________________________    -->
	

	<!--   ________________________________________________   GOBLIN PREGNANCY START   ______________________________________________________    -->
		<PregnantProposition>  <SetFlags flagSMBrandGoblins-43="true"/>  <SetFlags flagSMBrandGoblins-39="false"/>
			<ShowImage image='Images/Events/SMBrandGoblins/PregnancyToldMarek.jpg' align='2'/>
			<AddText>Mar'ek Looks at you a little stunned. He flashes a smile. There is something in his eyes, lust and joy yes but something else too.</AddText> 
			<PersonSpeak person="Ma'rek"> I... that's really wonderful news. I'm happy for you. I promise if you let me I'll make sure you don't regret this. I just need a little while to process this; I never get used to it.</PersonSpeak>
			<if smdominance="19-">
				<PersonSpeak person="#slavemaker">Hold me Mar'ek</PersonSpeak>
				<AddText>Some time passes as you sit on his lap, held in his arms and resting your head on his shoulder. With one hand he caresses your belly</AddText>
				<else>if</else>
				<PersonSpeak person="#slavemaker">I can give you a little time but we need to talk about this.</PersonSpeak>
				<AddText>You sit and tend the fire whilst Mar'ek gathers his thoughts</AddText>
			</if>
			<PersonSpeak person="Ma'rek"> There are some things you need to know. Because this is my child it won't be quite the same as what you might have been led to expect. For a start this child is unlikely to be a human being; there is no such thing as a half goblin either. Your daughter –and yes it's very likely to be a daughter- will almost certainly be fully goblin. I am goblin and goblin men breed true most of the time; it’s why we can take so many human women without breeding ourselves out of existence. \r\r I don't mean to worry you but goblin pregnancies can be hard on you humans. Our females carry for about seven months but this isn't always as regular humans. For our slaves pregnancy can vary from between six and almost ten months; this can make birthing difficult and potentially dangerous. \r\r I can help, whatever you decide it is my responsibility to help as best as I can. If it were up to me -if you were mine- I'd take you back home with me. Our medicines are just plain better than humans; I've seen far too many humans sick or dying needlessly. Our birth matron knows exactly what to look out for, she has a lot of experience with these kind pregnancies; something you won't find in Mioya. My family will be there to support you, to help you out with the baby.</PersonSpeak>
			<AskQuestions caption='Please will you let me take care of you'>
				<if smdominance="29-">
				<Question event='PregnantProTakeMeAway'>I'm frightened Mar'ek; I want you to take me away from all this. As you say; please look after me</Question></if>
				<Question event='PregnantProIFinishThenCome'>Mar'ek I can't. I have responsibilities here, I can't just walk away whenever I feel like it. When I finish #slaves training I'll come with you I promise.</Question>
				<Question event='PregnantProMyLifeIsHere'>I am sorry Mar'ek. It’s a kind offer but my life is here. I can't walk away; I won't</Question>
			</AskQuestions>
		</PregnantProposition>	

		<PregnantProTakeMeAway>
			<if badends='true'>
				<ShowImage image='Images/Events/SMBrandGoblins/PregnancyToldMarekBad.jpg' align='2'/>
				<PersonSpeak person="Mar'ek">Absolutely my dear and please; call me Shak'Ren</PersonSpeak>
				<DoEvent>Marekslavebadend</DoEvent>
				<EndEvent/>
			<else>if</else>  <SetFlags flagSMBrandGoblins-37="true"/>
				<ShowImage image='Images/Events/SMBrandGoblins/PregnancyToldMarekMiddle.jpg' align='2'/>
				<PersonSpeak person="Mar'ek">I'd love to but first you have responsibilities. #slave here still needs her mistress. Don't worry; we still have time. Once you've tide up the loose ends I will take you home and treat you right.</PersonSpeak>
				<DoEvent>GSWIP</DoEvent>
				<!-- <DoEvent>9999</DoEvent> -->
				<EndEvent/>
			</if>
		</PregnantProTakeMeAway> 

		<PregnantProIFinishThenCome>
			<if smdominance="29-"> <SetFlags flagSMBrandGoblins-37="true"/>
				<ShowImage image='Images/Events/SMBrandGoblins/PregnancyToldMarekMiddle.jpg' align='2'/>
				<PersonSpeak person="Mar'ek">You’ve made the right decision slavemaker. Things will go exactly as they should; trust me</PersonSpeak>
			<else>if</else>  <SetFlags flagSMBrandGoblins-40="true"/>
				<ShowImage image='Images/Events/SMBrandGoblins/PregnancyToldMarekGood.jpg' align='2'/>
				<PersonSpeak person="Mar'ek">Slavemaker I understand. You have your priorities and I respect that. When you are ready I’ll be here for you</PersonSpeak>
			</if>
			<DoEvent>GSWIP</DoEvent>
			<!-- <DoEvent>9999</DoEvent> -->
		</PregnantProIFinishThenCome>

		<PregnantProMyLifeIsHere>
			<ShowImage image='Images/Events/SMBrandGoblins/PregnancyToldMarekBest.jpg' align='2'/>
			<PersonSpeak person="Mar'ek">I completely understand, if there is anything you need, you feel that there is anything wrong or if you change your mind please let me know.</PersonSpeak>
			<DoEvent>9999</DoEvent>
		</PregnantProMyLifeIsHere>

		<SlavepregMarek>  <SetFlags flagSMBrandGoblins-42="false"/>
			<ShowImage image='Images/Events/SMBrandGoblins/PregnancySlave.jpg' align='2'/>
			<PersonSpeak person="Mar'ek">Interesting... that's interesting. Goblins don't normally "buy" slaves that we don't know can conceive our offspring. But as she can that means she has real value to our people. I would be quite willing to purchase her; if you've a mind to sell.</PersonSpeak>
			<AskQuestions caption='I would like to purchase her'>
				<Question event='SlavepregMarekYes'>I think we can do a deal here</Question>
				<Question event='SlavepregMarekNo'>No can do</Question>
			</AskQuestions>		
		</SlavepregMarek>
	
		<SlavepregMarekYes>  <SetFlags flagSMBrandGoblins-41="true"/>
			<AddText>Mar'ek agrees to purchase slave and take delivery of her on completion of her training. In the mean time he says that he would appreciate if you would bring #slave to visit him so he can check on her health and progress.</AddText>
			<DoEvent>GSWIP</DoEvent>
			<!-- <DoEvent>9999</DoEvent> -->
		</SlavepregMarekYes>

		<SlavepregMarekNo>
			<if GuildMember="true">
				<PersonSpeak person="#slavemakername">I'm sorry but she already has an owner; I don't have the right to sell her to you. I came to ask for your advice</PersonSpeak>
				<else>if</else>
				<PersonSpeak person="#slavemakername">That's not why I came here. I was considering keeping her for myself. I could do with some advice.</PersonSpeak>
			</if>
			<PersonSpeak person="Mar'ek">I'll tell you what I'll do. You bring her to me and I'll check her over every now and then. I have some "Medicine" that can help.</PersonSpeak>
			<DoEvent>9999</DoEvent>
		</SlavepregMarekNo>

		<MarekDoubletrouble> <SetFlags flagSMBrandGoblins-39="false"/>	<SetFlags flagSMBrandGoblins-42="false"/>   <SetFlags flagSMBrandGoblins-43="true"/>
			<ShowImage image='Images/Events/SMBrandGoblins/Pregnancy2.jpg' align='2'/>
			<PersonSpeak person="Mar'ek">Mine? Of course they're mine; you wouldn't be telling me else. Cad'ra do ga fruf'nic. Well this is a... a day and no mistake. \r\r
			You have decisions to make. Pregnancy can be very hard on our slaves. We can help you; I can help you through this. I know the dangers and I know how to deal with or prevent most of the difficulties you two are likely to face. \r\r
			I would like you to come home with me. As to #slave; I'll buy her off you if you would permit it. You will both be safe and well amongst my people. If you decide not to come I can try my best to take care of you here; it is the least I can do</PersonSpeak>
			<AskQuestions caption='Please would you come?'>
				<if smdominance="29-">
					<Question event='MarekDoubletroubleA'>Yes mar'ek...take us both</Question>
				</if>
				<if smdominance="39-">
					<Question event='MarekDoubletroubleB'>Yes; that sounds like a good idea</Question>
				</if>
				<Question event='MarekDoubletroubleC'>You can buy slave but my life is here mar'ek</Question>
				<Question event='MarekDoubletroubleD'>I won't sell #slave to you but when I am done with her I will come with you.</Question>
				<if smdominance="50+">
					<Question event='MarekDoubletroubleE'>No dice Mar'ek</Question>
				</if>
			</AskQuestions>	
		</MarekDoubletrouble>

		<MarekDoubletroubleA> <!-- needs a alternative for badends on -->
			<PersonSpeak person="#slavemakername"> You can have #slave. I want to come home with you right now. Take me away from all this.</PersonSpeak>
			<if badends="true">
				<ShowImage image='Images/Events/SMBrandGoblins/Pregnancy2Bad.jpg' align='2'/>
				<DoEvent>Marekslavebadend</DoEvent>
				<EndEvent/>
			<else>if</else> 
				<SetFlags flagSMBrandGoblins-37="true"/> 
				<SetFlags flagSMBrandGoblins-41="true"/>
				<ShowImage image='Images/Events/SMBrandGoblins/Pregnancy2Middle.jpg' align='2'/>
			</if>
			<DoEvent>GSWIP</DoEvent>
			<!-- <DoEvent>9999</DoEvent> -->
		</MarekDoubletroubleA>

		<MarekDoubletroubleB> <SetFlags flagSMBrandGoblins-41="true"/>
			<PersonSpeak person="#slavemakername">I'll sell her to you and come back with you when I've settled a some things here.</PersonSpeak>
			<if smdominance="29-"> 
				<SetFlags flagSMBrandGoblins-37="true"/>
				<ShowImage image='Images/Events/SMBrandGoblins/Pregnancy2Middle.jpg' align='2'/>
				<PersonSpeak person="Mar'ek">You’ve made the right decision #slavemaker. Things will go exactly as they should; trust me</PersonSpeak>
			<else>if</else> 
				<SetFlags flagSMBrandGoblins-40="true"/>
				<ShowImage image='Images/Events/SMBrandGoblins/Pregnancy2Middle.jpg' align='2'/>
				<PersonSpeak person="Mar'ek">#slavemaker I understand. You have your priorities and I respect that. When you are ready I’ll be here for you</PersonSpeak>
			</if>
			<DoEvent>GSWIP</DoEvent>
			<!-- <DoEvent>9999</DoEvent> -->
		</MarekDoubletroubleB>

		<MarekDoubletroubleC> <SetFlags flagSMBrandGoblins-41="true"/>
			<ShowImage image='Images/Events/SMBrandGoblins/Pregnancy2Middle.jpg' align='2'/>
			<AddText>Pleased with his purchase Mar'ek assures you that he will be here in case you "need" anything</AddText>
			<DoEvent>9999</DoEvent>
		</MarekDoubletroubleC>

		<MarekDoubletroubleD>
			<PersonSpeak person="#slavemakername">I won't sell #slave to you but when I am done with her I will come with you.</PersonSpeak>
			<if smdominance="29-">
				<SetFlags flagSMBrandGoblins-37="true"/>
				<ShowImage image='Images/Events/SMBrandGoblins/Pregnancy2Middle.jpg' align='2'/>
				<PersonSpeak person="Mar'ek">You’ve made the right decision #slavemaker. Things will go exactly as they should; trust me</PersonSpeak>
			<else>if</else>
				<SetFlags flagSMBrandGoblins-40="true"/>
				<ShowImage image='Images/Events/SMBrandGoblins/Pregnancy2Middle.jpg' align='2'/>
				<PersonSpeak person="Mar'ek">#slavemaker I understand. You have your priorities and I respect that. When you are ready I’ll be here for you</PersonSpeak>
			</if>
			<DoEvent>GSWIP</DoEvent>
			<!-- <DoEvent>9999</DoEvent> -->
		</MarekDoubletroubleD>

		<MarekDoubletroubleE>
			<ShowImage image='Images/Events/SMBrandGoblins/Pregnancy2Good.jpg' align='2'/>
			<PersonSpeak person="#slavemakername">No Mar'ek. I won't walk away from my life here. I'll come and see you when I need help.</PersonSpeak>
			<DoEvent>9999</DoEvent>
		</MarekDoubletroubleE>
			<!--Pregnancy proposals - End-->
	
		<YourMedicine>
			<ShowImage image='Images/Events/SMBrandGoblins/PregnancyMedicine.jpg' align='2'/>
			<PersonSpeak person="Mar'ek">When you came to me I said I’d be there for you whatever you chose and I stand by that. You need. And you need me…more than you know. As told you goblin pregnancies are hard on human women. And as I said we know the best ways to deal with it. Your body needs to acclimatize to goblin, you need me; you need my seed in your body. </PersonSpeak>
			<AddText>Somehow this doesn't sound very convincing<if smdominance="40-">, but you are afraid of what might happen if he is telling the truth</if>.</AddText>
			<AskQuestions caption='you need my seed in your body'>
				<if smdominance="29+">
					<Question event='YourMedicineA'>Not this time you randy old goat</Question>
				</if>
				<if smdominance="20-">
					<Question event='YourMedicineB'>I need you now Mar'ek</Question>
				<else>if</else>
					<Question event='YourMedicineB'>What the hell; why not. The damage is already done anyway</Question>
				</if>
			</AskQuestions>	
		</YourMedicine>

		<YourMedicineA>
			<PersonSpeak person="Mar'ek">As you will #slavemaker. But know that I am not Joking; you'll need to be well and truly fucked every now and then. And it's not just because you've got a pussy.</PersonSpeak>
			<DoEvent>9999</DoEvent>
		</YourMedicineA>

		<YourMedicineB>
			<Alternatives>
				<Alternative>
					<DoEvent now="true">SlavemakerBlowsMarek</DoEvent>
				</Alternative>
				<Alternative>
					<DoEvent now="true">MarekFucksPregnantSlavemaker</DoEvent>
				</Alternative>
				<Alternative>
					<DoEvent now="true">MarekAnnaCreampie</DoEvent>
				</Alternative>
				<Alternative>
					<DoEvent now="true">Blowbyproxy</DoEvent>
				</Alternative>
			</Alternatives>
		</YourMedicineB>
		<SlavemakerBlowsMarek>
			<ShowImage image='Images/Events/SMBrandGoblins/MedicineSMblow.jpg' align='2'/>
			<AddText>You kneel in front of this goblin man; the father of the baby growing inside of you. His cock is hard and heavy against your face, strong with the heavy musk of his maleness making you feel light headed. You gently suckle and lick on the proffered member, stroking his shaft with a supple touch as he caresses you hair. \r\r
			You can feel his penis slowly push back and forth in your mouth as Mar’ek strains not to just thrust under your tongue lashing. As you taste the first beads of his precum you feel something click inside your head. You begin to suck more ardently, stroking and bobbing deeper and faster and with your free hands you masturbate your nipples and
			<ifnot gender="female"> 
				cock
			<else>ifnot</else>
				clit
			</ifnot>
			, fingering your pussy. \r\r
			With a grunt Mar’ek takes control of your head. Griping you by your hair and ears he thrusts in earnest, winning his full length as you finger fuck yourself silly. Gasping for breath you are saved by the gout of seed welling up from his balls and pouring into you, filling you mouth, gushing down your throat and spilling from your lips and nose onto your trembling breasts.  \r\r
			Something reacts, a spasaming sensation surging up from the center of your being; ripping out from the seat of your womanhood to spill you into the well of orgasmic pleasure. When you come to you find you breasts wet with milk. </AddText>
			<DoEvent>9999</DoEvent>
		</SlavemakerBlowsMarek>
		<MarekFucksPregnantSlavemaker>
			<ShowImage image='Images/Events/SMBrandGoblins/MedicineSMMarek.jpg' align='2'/>
			<AddText>You take off your clothes and you lay there on the blanket naked and venerable; your thighs parted to expose you sex to his dark gaze. How many women has he seen laid out there for him; waiting for his rough hands, wet mouth and emerald cock to come and take them. On seeing it you no longer care; it’s going inside you tonight and that’s all that matters. \r\r
			He lays with you, putting his weight and his strength over you, his hands fondling your breasts and working you nipples his cock rubbing against 
			<ifnot gender="female"> 
				yours
			<else>ifnot</else>
				pussy
			</ifnot>
			. His mouth locked against your lips, exploring you with his tongue. In no rush to get on with proceedings</AddText>
			<PersonSpeak person="#slavemakername">…Shak’ren ro..roshan kesh Anna </PersonSpeak>
			<AddText>Needing no further encouragement he pins your arms and gives you a look that pierces your very soul even as his shaft pierces your body in one smooth thrust. He fucks you, his cock penetrating you over and over again he suckles on your breasts moving from one to another. \r\r
			You feel this buzzing inside you; filling your head and making thought impossible. Looking over to you left you see Anna. Exiled from her masters furs tonight she writhes and masturbates against the bonds holding her tight as she watches him fuck you. Her moans muffled by the gag. \r\r
			Mar’ek ponding is growing more incessant; harder and faster until his cock blasts out his seed and pumps it in you with a final few thrusts. The moment you feel his semen inside of you feel cataclysmic waves of pleasure roll through you like liquid fire; only quenched by the flood of orgasm. When mar’eks lips find your mouth again your questing tongue finds the taste of milk.</AddText>
			<DoEvent>9999</DoEvent>
		</MarekFucksPregnantSlavemaker>
		<MarekAnnaCreampie>
			<ShowImage image='Images/Events/SMBrandGoblins/MedicineAnnaMarek.jpg' align='2'/>
			<AddText>Anna mounts her reclining master. Alternatively Leaning forward to kiss and caress her master and pushing herself upright writhing and dancing on his reclining body as she frots herself against him until her juices flow freely. \r\r
			She screams for her master as she impales herself on his rock hard cock; penetrating all the way till her pussy is presses against him. Throwing her hands in the air she fucks herself vigorously crying out in goblin; her tits bouncing up and down as her masters hands play across her belly, ass, and pussy. Mar’ek roars as his semen pumps into her. \r\r
			Withdrawing herself from her spent master the slave woman crawls unsteadily to you and smiling offers up the fruit of her labour to you. You lick the spatters of semen from her thighs and abdomen circling closer to her center as you feel your prize tingling on your tongue. Fixing on her pussy you probe the folds of her lips chasing out the spooge for your thirsty mouth. Plunging inside her you lap the juice from the well of her womanhood. Your task finished you gently take her clit in your teeth and nibble and suckle at her; fucking her with your dexterous fingers. She cums strongly; pouring her juice through your lips and over your face. \r\r
			As you pull up from her pussy you see Mar’ek looking at you and your stained breasts speculatively.</AddText>
			<DoEvent>9999</DoEvent>
		</MarekAnnaCreampie>
		<Blowbyproxy>
			<ShowImage image='Images/Events/SMBrandGoblins/MedicineSlaveMarek.jpg' align='2'/>
			<AddText>You hold #slave as #slaveheshe kneels in front of Mar’ek. You whisper into #slavehisher ear….</AddText>
			<PersonSpeak person="#slavemakername">begin…</PersonSpeak>
			<AddText>#slave starts by placing #slavehisher hands on his hips and wetting his gland with #slavehisher mouth. #slaveHeShe blows across his heat as #slaveheshe looks up at him and into #slavehisher dark eyes. You massage the tension out of #slavehisher nude body; you feel #slavehisher muscles rippling under your hands. \r\r
			With her fingers #slave plays up and down his thighs as she licks in long strokes from his balls up his shaft; just brushing around the rim of it’s head. You kiss #slavehisher shoulders and neck; the flesh quivering between the gentle bites of your teeth. \r\r
			Taking Mar’ek gland in between #slavehisher hands #slaveheshe swallows his penis working it back and forth with #slavehisher mouth; #slavehisher tongue lashing forth to lick his shaft again. 
			<if slavegender="2">
				You masturbate her; feathering her labia before you plunge your fingers into the moist core of her being; brushing her clit with every stroke. 
			<else>if</else>
				You grip #slavehisher shaft stroking it with a firm grasp; caressing #slavehisher head with your thumb.
			</if>
				With the other you -fondle her breasts and- tweak her nipples
				<if ispregnant="true">thin streams of milk wetting your hands</if>. \r\r
			Mar’ek cums; filling #slaves mouth and spattering #slavehisher face; ropes of his pearlescent seed. You nibble at #slavehisher ear and #slaveheshe turns and kisses you; pushing #slavehisher loaded tongue past your lips. His seed passes between you; lubricating your sticky mouths. #Slave dribles the semen for you to catch; licking your face as it escapes from you. Your busy fingers bring #slavehimher and #slaveheshe orgasms in your arms. In a few minutes all the seed is gone; consumed by your mutual thirst. Mar’ek is watching the two of you embrace; a satisfied look in his eyes.</AddText>
			<DoEvent>9999</DoEvent>
		</Blowbyproxy>
	<!--   ________________________________________________   GOBLIN PREGNANCY END   ______________________________________________________    -->
	

	<!--   ________________________________________________   ANNA STORY START   ______________________________________________________    -->

		<AnnaGivesHead>
			<HideImages/>
			<ShowImage image='Images/Events/SMBrandGoblins/000.jpg' align='2'/>
			<PersonSpeak person="#slavemakername">Hello...Rhoshan An'ha</PersonSpeak>
			<AddText>Anna looks a little surprised then gives you a big hungry smile. She drops to her knees in front of you and </AddText>
			<if dressworn-slavemaker='-1'>
				<AddText>leaning forward Anna sets to work with her oral ministration to you groin.</AddText>
			<else>if</else>
				<AddText>helps you out of your clothes and under things to expose your gentiles for her ministrations.</AddText>
			</if>
			<if gender="Male">
			<AddText>She takes a firm grip of your cock with one hand gently stroking you whilst suckling on your balls and nipping at your scrotum. Her soft lips flutter up your hard shaft and part to envelop you swollen gland in her warm wet mouth. Her tongue sweeps damp arks across your inflamed skin as she sucks on your most sensitive part.\r\r</AddText>
				<AddText>She begins to bob her head backwards and forwards fucking her face on you as she massages your balls and thighs. Working herself deeper on you; One-two-three and holding the full length of you in her convulsing throat before beginging the cycle again.\r\r</AddText>
				<AddText>Suddenly your balls tighten and she backs off. Looking you in the eyes she finishing you with her hands and blowing your load over her face and open mouth. Anna pauses for a minuet for you to admire her cum soaked features. Rather than simply swallowing she motions slavename over and embraces her. Anna kisses her deaply; sharing your seed with her.\r\r</AddText>
			<else>if</else>
				<if gender="Dickgirl">
					<AddText>She takes a firm grip of your cock with one hand gently stroking you whilst suckling on your clit licking you labia. Her soft lips flutter up your hard shaft and part to envelop you swollen gland in her warm wet mouth. Her tongue sweeps damp arks across your inflamed skin as she sucks on your most sensitive part.\r\r</AddText>
					<AddText>She begins to bob her head backwards and forwards fucking her face on you as she finger fucks you pussy and jills your clit. Working herself deeper on you; One-two-three and holding the full length of you in her convulsing throat before beginging the cycle again.\r\r</AddText>
					<AddText>Suddenly your vagina clenches and she backs off. Looking you in the eyes she finishing you with her hands and blowing your load over her face and open mouth. Anna pauses for a minuet for you to admire her cum soaked features. Rather than simply swallowing she motions slavename over and embraces her. Anna kisses her deeply; sharing your seed with her.\r\r</AddText>
				<else>if</else>
					<HideImages/>
					<ShowImage image='Images/Events/SMBrandGoblins/Anna - Blowjob (Lesbian)' frame="random3"/>
					<AddText>Anna presses your labia together and caresses your pussy with her lips. She then parts you and gently probes you intimate parts with her tongue, circing and massaging the insides of your pussy. With a cry of pleasure you fell her wet tongue spear inside you, vigorously tongue fucking you as she finds her rhyme, causing your juice to flow into Annas mouth. She is unable to swallow all of your jizz and she dribbles down her chin to drip onto her breasts.\r\r</AddText>
					<AddText>Sensing your near she focuses her efforts on you clit. Locking down to suckle at the pinnacle of your womanhood as she continues to fuck your pussy and now asshole using her skilled fingers. Your climax rips though you and you rain you juice all over Annas face. Anna pauses for a minuet for you to admire her jizz soaked features. Rather than simply swallowing she motions slavename over and embraces her. Anna kisses her deeply; sharing your taste with her.\r\r</AddText>
				</if>
			</if>
			<AddText>Anna continues to kiss #slave passionately whilst you recover your bearings. By now you know her better than to thank her for her attentions; she would take it as an insult to her strange pride in her slavery. As you extricate #slave from her embrace you give her a small nod of acknoladgement and bid her goodbye. As you leave she bows to you and remains prostrate until after you are gone.</AddText>
			<DoEvent>9999</DoEvent>
		</AnnaGivesHead>

		<AnnaFullName>  <SetFlags flagSMBrandGoblins-7="true"/>
			<PersonSpeak person="#Slavemakername">Anna wasn’t it?</PersonSpeak>
			<PersonSpeak person="Anna">Thank you for remembering the name of this lowly slave, #master. My full goblin name is rho’shan’ah’na but most everyone calls me Anna.</PersonSpeak>
			<PersonSpeak person="#Slave">That’s a pretty name, if you don’t mind me asking does it mean anything?</PersonSpeak>
			<PersonSpeak person="#Slavemakername">And who is Shak’ren; Mar’ek?</PersonSpeak>
			<AddText>Looking down Anna plucks a flower from her hair and begins to twirl it in her fingers.</AddText>
			<PersonSpeak person="Anna">The Master is he; yes. Goblin names have meaning; usually more than one. #Master, was very considerate when He branded me with such a beautiful and cleaver name. Goblin words have multiple meanings dependent on context. The emphasis in the middle of a word changes its meaning. Ah’Na means flower; when referring to a woman it means her face but it can also be used to refer to a pretty slave girl or a woman in general. When talking about something like a flower, plant or wild animal Rho’Shan means to pick, to take, to claim, to choose ; when it’s about to goods or chattel it means to possess or own. Roshan means to partake, to use or make use of</PersonSpeak>
			<PersonSpeak person="Anna">I always thought Ah’Na was such a prissy name for a silly slave like me. Most everyone calls ma Anna, Ne’alla calls me Anna, I call me Anna. Anna really is a much better name for this slave. I haven’t thought of Anna by that silly human name in years. I love it that everybody calls me ‘CUNT’; suits me, don’t you think #master?</PersonSpeak>
			<AddText>Looking up she smiles mischievously as she tucks the primrose into her vagina and using the forefingers and thumb of both her hands she forms a downward pointing triangle over her forward thrusting Venus</AddText>
			<PersonSpeak person="Anna">To roshan a SLAVE like me means to FUCK ME. I Love my name. I Love that HE BRANDED me with it. I LOVE how I feel like HIS chosen flower or how I am HIS SLAVE with the tone of His voice! I love it how He makes me WET with a name! I LOVE being HIS FUCKING CUNT! I love when HE go “roshan AnnA” SLAVE open NOW! Ready, NOT, MASTERs KROAS NEED FUCKING ANNA!</PersonSpeak>
			<AddText>Anna is panting heavily and swaying. Her glistening pussy is driping wet and her juice is running down her legs. Slowly regaining some of her former composure she removes the sodden flower and stairs at it for a moment.\r\rReplacing the drenched blossom behind her ear the as she absently smears her girl cum all over her face and hair, dribbling jiz over her still heaving breasts.</AddText>
			<PersonSpeak person="Anna">Being Ah’Na is not so bad either. Shak’ren needs His face time to.</PersonSpeak>
			<DoEvent>9999</DoEvent>
		</AnnaFullName>

		<AnnaOnSlavePsychologyAndPresenceOfMind> <SetFlags flagSMBrandGoblins-8="true"/>
			<PersonSpeak person="Anna">Being a slave means no longer thinking of yourself or for yourself. But it does not mean that you should stop thinking slavename. A master can tollerate a stupid slave; many masters enjoy them. A thoughtless slave is a bad slave. A selfish slave is no slave at all.\r\r
			No longer thinking for yourself is more than just accepting what your told. When your master tells you that something is so then it is true. You have to school yourself into believing what he tells you. You also have to accept that sometimes your master makes mistakes, lies to you or changes his mind. That is his prerogative a it is not for anyone who truly thinks of herself as a slave to judge or correct him.\r\r
			Being a good slave means observing your master closely. Knowing his moods, routines and ques. Being ready to serve his needs at a moments notice; sometimes without him even noticing that your doing it. When you are serving his pleasure you have got to remember that it is his pleasure that is your highest priority and not yours. You should know both his body and yours inside and out. You should know without being told those dark looks that means cum now. Those little ques that say suck me harder or go slowly.\r\r
			In the end a good slave is a thoughtful and mindful one.</PersonSpeak>
			<Points>
				<Intelligence>random2</Intelligence>
				<Temperament>-1</Temperament>
				<Sensibility>2</Sensibility>
			</Points>
			<DoEvent>9999</DoEvent>
		</AnnaOnSlavePsychologyAndPresenceOfMind>

		<RhoshanAhna> <SetFlags flagSMBrandGoblins-9="true"/> <SetFlags flagSMBrandGoblins-6="true"/>
			<PersonSpeak person="Anna">My master has given me permission to allow his friends to call me by my full name whilst he is not present. If it pleases you #master #slavemakername you may call me Rhoshan ah’na.</PersonSpeak>
			<PersonSpeak person="#Slavemakername">What is that supposed to mean?</PersonSpeak>
			<AddText>Anna simply looks at you with a knowing smile that says “You’ll see”</AddText>
			<AskQuestions>
				<Question event='AnnaLeave'>Fine I’ll find out myself. Farewell Anna.</Question>
				<Question event='AnnaGivesHead'>Fine play it like that; Rhoshan Ah’na</Question>
			</AskQuestions>
		</RhoshanAhna>

		<HowIBecameHis> <SetFlags flagSMBrandGoblins-10="true"/>
			<ShowImage image='Images/Events/SMBrandGoblins/000.jpg' align='2'/>
			<PersonSpeak person="Anna">I wasn’t born a slave you know. I know it’s kind of hard to imagine but I was “free” once upon a time. It’s been so long and I have changed so much that I have a very hard time thinking of me back. Before I became Anna my human name was Antony and as you may have heard I was a foolish young man. I lived with my family near the southern borders of Mioya.\r\r
			My father was the richest and most influential man in town. He was a very intense and organized person; a fervent believer. He had the will to control, scrupulous standards and eye for detail. He made everything and everyone his business and if he wasn’t happy he would never leave anything alone until he got his way. And he wasn’t happy with me.\r\r
			I was his opposed; I was a quiet, shy young man with a love of nature and tranquillity. If this wasn’t bad enough I started to attract certain rumours; though I still had no idea of quite how close they were to the truth at that time. It started because my brother and I used to have all the village girls fawning over use. My brother loved it but I was never interested; I felt that all they wanted was my families money. They never really saw me, wanted me. Their attentions left me cold and I brushed them off as best I could.\r\r
			My father arranged a marriage for me; for both of us. I think he felt that he was doing me a favour; that a good woman would “sort me out”; protect the “families reputation” from roomers of my “unnatural disposition”. And Sahra was a good woman; solid, sensible, kind …pretty even to me. Had I not been the way I was I could have been happy with her.\r\r
			Had I one once of courage I would have refused; I wasn’t strong enough. I did what I always did with my father and took the path of least resistance. I tried; I really tried to love her. She was a wonderful person and I think she really did love me. I liked her; she was my friend but try as I might I couldn’t love her in the way she deserved. As the day came closer I panicked. I took the coward's way out; I ran.\r\r
			I had never been more ashamed of myself. I had hurt Sahra so badly; I and led her on and let her down. I couldn’t go back; there was no home to back to anyway any more. I had no future, no hope and no desire to carry on. I threw myself into the river and meant to end it; to escape my shames. In a way I succeeded; Antony died that day.\r\r
			When I came to the first thing I saw was Masters dark eyes looking into mine. The first thing I felt was his lips on mine; breathing the life back into me. He had saved my life; risked his own to save that the worthless hide of a total stranger. He held me in his strong arms and shared his warmth with me. Built a fire to keep me by; helped me shed the sodden tatters of my old life.\r\r
			I had never seen a goblin before. They seldom came north of the border back then but I had heard tales from the traders; of strange men of odd hues from the south west. They were freely welcome in the dark elven courts but again not of them.\r\r
			Master was young man back then. He had exotic features, his nude skin was grey green and displayed his wirer muscled physique. He looked proud, strong, wild and free; everything I wasn’t. He was beautiful to me. I sat by his fire and unburdened myself to him; I told him my story and thanked him for my life. I wasn’t thinking straight then but I felt that I owed him that much; even if he couldn’t understand it. Talked until my throat was horse and my words ran out. After we sat in silence as he tended the fire.\r\r
			My eyes were drawn to his oh so male part and I simply couldn’t look away. I felt the blood rushing to my face and to other things besides as I felt a familiar sense of shame. And then he saw me, saw what I was looking at and what it did to me him, saw how it affected me. He astonished me; rather than the disgust and contempt I was expecting he turned to me and shifted his hands to give me a better view. When he saw what that did to me he gave me this kind of “like what you see?” smile and a speculative look. At the time I didn’t know quite what was going on behind those dark eyes. All I could see was that he had had an idea and he liked it; he liked it a lot.\r\r
			“Want this? Don’t be ashamed” where the first human words he said to me as he gestured to his half erect member. As red as I was, as hard as I was I couldn’t deny it. “I want you for myself; be mine.” It was all I could do to gasp out a tiny little “yes” and that was that. Master saved my life; took my life and remade it anew. I owe him all that I am; master enslaved me mind, body and soul. It is right that I am his property to use as he sees fit. I am his and I couldn’t imagine being any other way.</PersonSpeak>
			<Points>
				<Intelligence>2</Intelligence>
				<Sensibility>1</Sensibility>
			</Points>
			<DoEvent>9999</DoEvent>
		</HowIBecameHis>

		<HowIBecameAnna> <SetFlags flagSMBrandGoblins-17="true"/>
			<HideImages/>
			<ShowImage image='Images/Events/SMBrandGoblins/000.jpg' align='2'/>
			<PersonSpeak person="Anna">Back before I became Anna, before I became his slave girl I was briefly his slave boy. Master had given me an acceptance I did not know I craved; helped me to see myself for what I really am. We were traveling home, from the place where I was born to the place where I belong. Being with him was wonderful. I was content to continue on in that way. The only fly in the ointment was that he would not make love to me; he said he wanted to wait until he saw his people. I couldn't wait to arrive, eager and resolute; I had no idea of what he had in store for me when we got home. 
			When we arived at the tribe Shak'ren took me to see three goblins; His father the chief, his oldest brother and the tribal shaman at her lodge. He embraced his kin and spoke for a long time with his brother. I didn't know it then but he was kind of arranging a loan or favour to pay for what he had planned for me next. The shaman I learned was actually quite old though you couldn't tell that to look at her back then. She inspected me and drank this wyrd potion; I still don't know what was in it but I can tell you what it did. Gro'Bhagh kissed me then Shak'ren had me kneel; she removed her loin cloth to reveal one of the biggest cocks I had ever seen. I heard of futas mind you, met a few in my time but I had never seen the meat of the difference before. This was not futa. Where you would expect to find to find her pussy was nothing but blank skin and old scars. I later found out that "she" was a wal'lach; a gelding.\r\r
			Shak'ren told me to suck so what could I do but suck? I had been practicing on Shak'ren on the way and it was a chance to show off I supposed. Besides Shak'ren was right their behind me; this wasn't cheating but sharing. I though that if I did this he would finally fuck me; I was right but not in the way I imagined. Her pre-cum tasted strange; almost sickly sweet. I began to feel good but bad at the same time; hot and light headed. My chest, balls and perineum began to tingle, my cock and nipples were filled with pins and needles. She came screaming and I swallowed; she didn't leave me any other choice but to swallow. As she with drew the pleasure and pain and orgasm hit me. I think I recall my shriek went up an octave or two before I passed out.\r\r
			When I came to I was naked an bound in the warmth a fire lit tent. Strange as it sounds I didn't notice I was female at first. Shak'ren was there, kneeling between my legs; nude and rock hard for me. It was only when my penis failed to react to him that I noticed that it was missing; that I was endowed with the other things instead.\r\r
			When I asked him why he had done this and if this was permanent he said to me "Antony I know all this may come as something of a shock to you but it really is for the best. You are as you always should have been, the girl I saw in you trying to escape her prison and you will remain so for the rest of your life." I would have questioned him about it more; protested about what was done without my consolation or consent but he never gave me the chance. Master took my breath away with first his lips and then his hands and ultimately his cock. He had made me a girl and when he took my virginity he made me a woman; his woman. As he fucked me I felt all my objections dissolve bit by bit with every thrust. When he came inside me I knew that this was what I had waited for; that this was everything I had wished for and more besides, all because of this goblin man inside of me.\r\r
			When he was finished he tuned me over and told me to bite the fur and present my ass for him. Then he said "I have done this to you for two reasons. The first and more practical reason is I really do prefer girls but I was bound by my promise to you. To resolve these things I decided to remake you to be a better match for me. The second and most important is that your life is possessed of a story; and the story of Antony the runaway bridegroom ends with his death as a man. I chose this ending for; I chose to make you my bride rather than to see you dead. Antony is no more; you are Rho'shan An'ha now -My lovely flower, my Fucking Cunt". And then he branded me.
			I've been his slave ever since. I don't regret the exchange of my freedom or of my manhood; I don't view it as a loss. I am happier as a slave woman that I ever was as a free man. I love being his cunt, I love Masters Pussy. I love how this pussy makes Anna feel, I love how Master uses it to serve His pleasure, I love how it has brought His children into the world.</PersonSpeak>
			<Points>
				<Intelligence>1</Intelligence>
				<Sensibility>3</Sensibility>
			</Points>
			<DoEvent>9999</DoEvent>
		</HowIBecameAnna>

		<HisBrand> 	<SetFlags flagSMBrandGoblins-11="true"/>  <!-- need text revision -->
			<ShowImage image='Images/Events/SMBrandGoblins/000.jpg' align='2'/>
			<PersonSpeak person="Anna">I remember clearly the day He first fucked me. It was the day he branded me.</PersonSpeak>
			<PersonSpeak person="#slave">Branded?</PersonSpeak>
			<AddText>Smiling and without hesitation or embarrassment Anna performs a half turn and bends over at the waste; giving you and slavename a full unimpeded view of her firm ample backside and slightly downy pussy. Blazoned across most of her left buttock is an intricate circular design of thick dark lines. You had always assumed that brands cruel and ugly blemishes that marred a slaves skin and trust; but this is something else. Not some backstreet butchery; this is very much an exquisite work of art.\r\r
			She remains still as she allows your fingers to explore the curved tracery without protest; trembling only slightly as you delicately caresses the tracts across her perineum and part of her labia. The brand has clearly been added to and partly redone and darkened over the years. Withdrawing your hand you ponder; This took consummate skill on the part of the ironsman.</AddText>
			<PersonSpeak person="#slave">“Its beautiful“I never imagined; But did it hurt badly? what does it all mean? </PersonSpeak>
			<AddText>Turning her head and smiling Anna gently takes slave names hand and takes it on a journey across the canvas of her skin.\r\rAt the very centre she wrests #slave hand on Y shaped cross surrounded by three dots in the middle of a small circle with five short radial lines crossing its circumference.</AddText>
			<PersonSpeak person="Anna">“We start at as with all stories at the beginning. This is the beginning of my life -my true life. This cross is the mark of the Shak’ren -my Master. He is –as it should be- first, foremost and at the centre of all things; this mark was etched into my being by His hand as is His right. Surrounding Him is the circle of kinship the symbol of the tribe. This was burned by the Shak’yon –the chief as a symbol of belonging and accent of the tribe to His ownership of me.</PersonSpeak>
			<AddText>Her hand begins to spiral outwards as she explains the meanings of the various marks. Most of the more complicated markings appear to be tattoos rather than brands. #slave's fingers brushes against in inverted triangle.</AddText>
			<PersonSpeak person="Anna">“This one represents when Master became a trader” A little cross come next “this one is the day I neally died and how He saved me.</PersonSpeak>
			<AddText>On and round the hand goes, Anna explaining each mark as it passes.</AddText>
			<PersonSpeak person="Anna">The first year, when I learned to speak, when I stopped thinking like a human and started thinking in goblin</PersonSpeak>
			<AddText>Anna Moves the hand across to a tattooed thick wavy line snaking up her perineum and spitting at the base of her genitals terminating in branded points on the labia on either side of her vulva.</AddText>
			<PersonSpeak person="Anna">This one is so I never forget the lesson I needed to learn entertaining in the tent of men and why I needed to learn it.</PersonSpeak>
			<AddText>#slave's hand was guided to a row of four circles and two dots branded into the top of her buttock. One circle is tattooed blue, two red and the last over branded solid and inked black.</AddText>
			<PersonSpeak person="Anna">These represent the children I bore for Him. This red one is for Ne’alla, this black one is for the child I lost and these dots for the twins I failed to carry.</PersonSpeak>
			<AddText>Her hand indicates four concentric circles. The inner three are made of dotted lines but the fourth is a thin black line with six dots branded into it.</AddText>
			<PersonSpeak person="Anna">Each of these circles represents four years of the life He has given me. When I became His He promised that after four years He would sell me to a human husband if I so wished it. Each line represents that I chose to remain as His rho’shan’ah’na. This fourth line is different; it is solid because it represents eternity; I have decided to remain His slave. To be His property for as long as I live is all I could ever want.</PersonSpeak>
			<AddText>Moving #slave hand from her backside Anna turn to face her and brings it up across her breasts to an isolated dot burned right over her heart.</AddText>
			<PersonSpeak person="Anna">This one, this one’s for Anna, this one’s for me. This represents the day I met Him. The day he rescued me from my life. The day He took the life I gave Him. The day my old life ended and the day the one I live for Him began.</PersonSpeak>
			<AddText>Smiling weakly she looks #slave in the eye.</AddText>
			<PersonSpeak person="Anna">In answer to your first question yes it hurt. It always hurts. Rebirth is supposed to hurt. Some things should never be forgotten.</PersonSpeak>
			<AddText>You bid Anna fare well and leave. You both have much to think about and head home in near silence. #Slave appears lost in thought and does not seem to notice as you slip behind. You watch #slavehisher buttocks move to and fro as #slaveheshe walks; considering the possibilities.</AddText>
			<Points>
				<Temperament>-1</Temperament>
				<Morality>2</Morality>
				<Sensibility>1</Sensibility>
			</Points>
			<DoEvent>9999</DoEvent>
		</HisBrand>

		<OnHerRelationshipWithNealla> <SetFlags flagSMBrandGoblins-12="true"/>
			<ShowImage image='Images/Events/SMBrandGoblins/000.jpg' align='2'/>
			<if isslaveowned='Nealla'>
				<PersonSpeak person="Anna">My daughter. By beautiful beloved Ne’alla. I always loved her and I was proud to be her mother. Strange isn’t it; that I couldn’t tell that for her until she was gone. I won’t be sad that she a slave and I’m not angry at you for taking her. Master had decided to sell her long ago; grew up Ne’alla knowing this. She was always going to be sold to a human; its part of what keeps the tribe alive. I knew she wouldn’t be coming back with us.
				Being a slave to the right master is a wonderful life. I think master sensed you were the right man to enslave my daughter. I hope you can understand. And if she ever gives you trouble then let her know from me that she will never be too old to put across my knee.</PersonSpeak>
				<SMCorruption>-5</SMCorruption>
			<else>if</else>
				<PersonSpeak person="Anna">I am not Ne’alla mother. I am her Dam. I raised her, nursed her, birthed her, and carried her in my womb. Shak’ren conceived her within me but I am not her mother. She is his acknowledged child and so can never be my daughter; It’s a cultural thing.</PersonSpeak>
			</if>
			<DoEvent>9999</DoEvent>
		</OnHerRelationshipWithNealla>

		<TheTasteOfHome> <SetFlags flagSMBrandGoblins-13="true"/>
			<ShowImage image='Images/Events/SMBrandGoblins/000.jpg' align='2'/>
			<PersonSpeak person="#slavmakername">You said that slaves are subject to much worse. You sound like you speak from experience. Can you tell me about It?</PersonSpeak>
			<PersonSpeak person="Anna">It was back when I was young. I was an idiot; I did something, something awful I am still ashamed of. I Disappointed my master and I let myself down so badly. I hadn’t been a slave for more than a month but I thought I knew it all. I thought I knew what love was all about, what being a woman was all about, what being a slave was about; I knew nothing.\r\r
			I thought that I loved my shak’ren; that being with him was all that mattered. I thought that loving your master; that just doing and learning what you were told was enough. I thought I was being a good slave. I didn’t even know how wrong I was. My mistake was that I loved Him like a women loves her man and not like a slave should lover her master; I didn’t really understand the concept of what it meant to be a Master; to be MASTERED.\r\r
			Shak’ren had a guest. An old friend had come to pay him a visit. She saw me, desired me, asked for me and master ordered me to eat her pussy. I was an idiot, a fool. I refused him; I embarrassed him in front of his friend, in front of the tribe, I broke my promise to obey him. In retrospect I was surprised that he didn’t sell me on the spot. He had me chained outside, completely naked and exposed with only a camp fire for warmth for three days. I was on my knees with my arms spread out to the side, defenceless and unable to fend for myself.\r\r
			Slaves would feed me, clean me, whip me, bring me almost to the point of orgasm over and over and over again and again and again. These women humiliated me in ways I didn’t know were possible, took from me pride I didn’t know I still had. They feed me some kind of tea to make me want more and more pleasure. What my master did to me was worse than even that. He didn’t touch me, didn’t talk to me, didn’t even look at me. He fucked woman after woman right there in front of me and I am ashamed to say I almost hated him then if I didn’t hate myself more back then. In those three days I learned more about myself as a slave and as a woman than I ever had before.\r\r
			When they finally cut me down my master still wouldn’t look at me. A slave; his new favourite I thought gave me his orders. I was to go to the mens tent and live there. I was to offer myself to everyman who came in there and fuck any and all who wanted me. I was to obey their commands and to fuck any slave they ordered me to. I was to remain there until my master sent for me; if he sent for me.\r\r
			Was there for two months and in all that time I never saw nor heard from my master. I must have fucked every man in the tribe save one three times over and gods knows how many besides. Before my time there I was still wearing a slave shift and feeling very embarrassed about it. After a few weeks I was absolutely naked at all times and fine with it. Before I was struggling to kiss properly in public. On the very first night there I was in a cage to perform audience participation sex shows with men, women and things I had never seen before and I was front and centre every night; sometimes three times a night. I had almost given up hope when Master summoned me.\r\r
			I went before Shak’ren. I Had expected a lecture, a whipping, a test; something. He just sat there looking at me whilst I begged, and I grovelled and I dragged my tits and pussy through the dirt to kiss his feet. After that he get up opens of the flap and low and behold it’s the friend from the first time and Master just gives me this look. I am not an Idiot. I can see a second chance and I knew there would be no third chance. I tell you my tongue was lodged so far up her cunt by the time her loincloth hit the floor that I could lick her uterus. The only times my mouth came off her vulva was when she tapped out for a bit of the old bump and grind or if she wanted it somewhere else; pretty much everywhere in fact. It went back in immediately after and stayed there until the small hours of the night.\r\r
			The next day Master made absolutely no mention of the tent, his friend or the chains. He said that my Goblak is lagging behind and that my tirade yesterday included an embarrassing number of human words; he was counting. He takes out his cane and tells me to present my breasts, ass and pussy for punishment and gives me fifty of the best and makes me count it up in goblak. I took every stroke with relief because it meant he had accepted me again. After His cock slick with juice was the best thing I ever tasted; it was the taste of home.</PersonSpeak>
			<Points>
				<Obediance>-1</Obediance>
			</Points>
			<DoEvent>9999</DoEvent>
		</TheTasteOfHome>

		<AnnaOnPregnancy> <SetFlags flagSMBrandGoblins-14="true"/>
			<ShowImage image='Images/Events/SMBrandGoblins/000.jpg' align='2'/>
			<PersonSpeak person="Anna">I have always enjoyed being pregnant; the thought of that new life growing inside me fills me with joy. Amongst the goblins pregnancy is; well it’s different then it is amongst humans. Goblin pregnancies can be very hard on us slaves so most goblins go to great lengths to ensure the health of the baby and the safety of His slave.\r\r
			Exercise is very important. Childbirth can be trying at the best of times. Strong abdominal muscles, a good set of lungs and a strong heart all go a long way to making it safer; making it all the more likely that you deliver His child live and hale to Him. Being lazy, being waited on hand and foot is never what being a slave is all about; all the more so for a pregnant one. An idle slave deserves only the whip.\r\r
			They know that human women have a tendency to reject the baby; to miscarry. They know its a lot worse in first timers or women who've miscarried before. Master knows that if a goblin impregnates his slave and simple stops fucking her the chances of complications rises. When I was pregnant with His first Master has told me that even though I was already with His child it is best that I swallow good seed with both my lips regularly and often.\r\r
			Master also knows that goblins who are possessive of their pregnant slaves are more likely to lose either or both the child and the slave. When I was pregnant I would often sleep with Masters family. When I had Ne'alla inside me I was fucked by almost every tribesman; they took time away from their mates and slaves just to ensure our health. Master says it is because of the animal spirits of us slaves reacting badly to the soul of the child. The strength of her Master and the tribe must be used to force her spirit into submission; so the soul of the unborn can suckle on her and grow strong. Once her spirit successfully is Mastered the first time she will usually serve him well again and again. Some slaves have spirits that are too strong and will never submit; I have always pitied them because they will never know the joy of true slavery.</PersonSpeak>
			<DoEvent>9999</DoEvent>
		</AnnaOnPregnancy>

		<AnnaOnGoingHome> <SetFlags flagSMBrandGoblins-15="true"/>
			<ShowImage image='Images/Events/SMBrandGoblins/000.jpg' align='2'/>
			<PersonSpeak person="Anna">I remember I was His slave for about a year when He took me back to see my birth village. It can be dangerous for a master to do this. Sometimes a slaves birth family will resent her master for taking her; sometimes they don't want to see her this way or indeed back at all. This is partly why a slave should never try to contact her family without her masters express permission. Having said that it can be good for a slave for her old friends and family to see her like that. It was a good way for Master to demonstrate and reinforce His absolute power over me.\r\r
			In my case their was little actual danger of attack or "rescue" though we did draw odd looks. No one could recognized me. I was nothing to them; just some slave bitch. Master took me to the town hall; to trade he had tolled the villagers. I learned that my family was saying that I was dead. Only some people bought it but it was the polite fiction.\r\r
			My father was away; gone to Mioya on business and to "inspect stock". I learned later that he had was a guild investor and owned a controlling stake in a slave bordello. Imagine that; my father the prim and proper temperance man made the family fortune off the trade of slave pussy just like me. Shak'ren dealt with my brother. I always find it easier to pretend I don't speak human by zoning out the words and focusing on the body language. I didn't hear what was being discussed or traded; not my business. Instead I tried to read my brother; all through the meeting he was distracted by me. The way he watched me said he wanted badly to fuck me; and I played him, I teased him and Master got a very fair deal out of him. I was a little shocked when Master told me he had offered to sell me to him. I didn't need to be because I knew I could trust Master; my brother could not buy me, father would never let him keep me. He did sweeten the deal by offering to lend me to him for the night; an offer my brother simply couldn't refuse.\r\r
			I was a good slave that night. Master tells me to fuck and I fucking well put my back into it. My brother fucked me -no I fucked him in his marital bed and I didn't hold back. It was a little easier because I pretended that I couldn't really speak human, only a few very basic words and gestures. Fucking him wasn't the hardest thing I have ever done as a slave. Giving him my full attention, energy and skill wasn't even the hardest thing I did that day. He was always handsome, the mother spirit had been generous in his clay when she made that certain part of him and he knew exactly how to use it. Fucking him was easy; no enjoying it was hard. It was the strangeness of it all; this was my dear older brother mounting me. Eyes that always sparkled with levity looking at me with that hungry male darkness. Strong arms I had often depended on holding me tight. A tongue so skilled and playful in jest showing equal skill as it danced with mine. A mouth that I had often laughed with as a child locked sucking on my breast. Firm hands so dexterous with cards exploring every inch and crevice of me. His cock hot and hard and eager for me, fucking me in places a brothers cock should never go. Further more he was a married man. I was best man at his wedding; his wife was a dear friend of mine. It was the strangeness of it that was preventing me from enjoying it and it was starting to impede his.\r\r
			As a slave that is unacceptable. Unacceptable that my personal hangups where interfering with the pleasure and satisfaction of the man between my thighs; a man -brother or not- Shak'ren ordered me to fuck. I hadn't told him but Master knew who he was to me; how couldn't he? Master always knows. He must have known how I would react, must have done. This was His test; a lesson for me and one I was determined to pass. If I couldn't ignore it or pretend that it didn't effect me then I had to accept it, embrace it, enjoy it even. He smelled good and male and sex. The way he looked into my eyes as he kissed me wasn't the look of a man at his brother, nor at his sister, nor even at his wife; he looked at me like I was his bitch, his piece of fuck meat to play with. This man lying over me, ramming his weight and strength into me. This was my fucking BROTHER... FUCKING ME! And he was so fucking good! His hot COCK pounding my wet CUNT balls deep over and over and over again. With that I was wet and wild for him; his BITCH in heat and my brothers cock could taste it. I did MASTER proud, I proved that Anna is first, foremost and forever his SLAVE. If father had been there that night I'd have FUCKED him too; and enjoyed it.\r\r
			I screamed to him in goblin that he was my brother; that I missed him and loved him and always would and that he should fuck me harder even as he came inside me for the third time that night. Now when we go back there my brother still wants me; still gets to have his wild night in me. I am grateful to Master for allowing this fucking cunt such intimate contact with her family. Grateful; if a little stiff and sore afterwards.</PersonSpeak>
			<Points>
				<Morality>-2</Morality>
				<Temprement>1</Temprement>
				<Charisma>2</Charisma>
			</Points>
			<DoEvent>9999</DoEvent>
		</AnnaOnGoingHome>

		<MastersPrize>	<SetFlags flagSMBrandGoblins-16="true"/>
			<ShowImage image='Images/Events/SMBrandGoblins/000.jpg' align='2'/>
			<PersonSpeak person="Anna">When Shak'ren took me back to my village what he was after was more than just simple trade. When he had Gro'Bhagh turn me into Anna; Gifted pussy as it were she did it as a favor to him because of her "husband" and his brother; the goblin who is now known as chief Gor'thran Kroas. A favor he intended to repay in kind. Whilst I was busy distracting my brother Master was making a deal with him. Because of me; because of what I did with him that night my brother had agreed to let Shak'ren choose one of the unmarried townswomen and enslave her. This wasn't as drastic a concession as you might imagine as unmarried women above a certain age in that town tended to be either widows or what you might call awkward. At least in my fathers time "disruptive" people in that town where quietly "encouraged" to leave; people that didn't take the hint -particularly unmarried women- had a tendancy to "disapear". When I found out what I had helped cause I was proud but a little part of me was ashamed and worried as well. I know know that what i felt then was wrong of me; I should have been pleased for Master accomplishment.\r\r
			Shak'ren gave me a very difficult decision. He said to me "You know these people rhoshan Anna. Go, find, pick one; and bring her to me." This was one of the hardest things I have ever done; perhaps the most difficult test Master ever put to me. I went clothed for the first time in almost a year as not to draw unwanted atention. Master had to help dress me as I had no idea how to wear girls cloths; it felt very odd and uncomfortable yet somehow natural.\r\r
			As I set off back into town my mind began to whirl. I had to choose one of my family, friends or neighbours and turn her into a slave just like. Someone I knew would find out what I had willingly become. If I chose poorly I would humiliate Shak'ren. If I chose to well she might supplant me in his eyes. All these thoughts cycled through my mind as I walked the familiar streets of my old home. Somehow and without thinking I found myself at the front door of Sarhas house. Shak'ren would say "Kroas auf Pet'zen rhoshan Des Anna" the authority of the spirits possessed this flower; or a more direct translation "the cock of the tale fucked this cunt".\r\r
			Sarha came out. I could see that she was pale and had lost weight. Sarha was wearing the morning veil; morning for me. When she saw me she stopped and looked at me shocked; on some level she recognized me and couldn't quite believe it. When I saw the tears beginning to well in her eyes I wanted to rip all that morning black off of her and make her feel loved, happy and secure; like every slave should. I knew in my heart then that I had found Masters slave. My Sarha stripped and whipped, bound, branded and fucked over and over again by the goblin men.\r\r
			I smiled at her, beckoned her, and without a word took her by the hand and into bondage led her. Master met us in a clearing by the edge of the great forest. Sarha was afraid of Him when He appeared out of the gloom but I held her firmly by the hand and reassured her. He didn't praise me but I could tell he approved of my choice. Sahra watched me as I stripped naked, kissed his left nipple and prostrated myself before him. Womens clothes had felt surprisingly good but I Shak'rens sight I don't any part of me not exposed to Him. I think she was too astonished to run. He lifted me to my knees by my hair and kissed me; owning my mouth. I could feel that Sarha was tense, she wanted to run but couldn't.\r\r
			Mar'ek "The townsfolk have grown weary of you. If you remain as you are eventually its master will sell you to the fleshpots of Mioya; I don't think you want that Sarha. Anna is mine; I saved her from her self and so she belongs to me. She is precious to me; I have made her happy and safe and soon she will bear my child. I have agreed to save you from your sorrow and grief Sarha. You will come with me; you will belong amongst my kin and they will cherish you. You will know the happiness, love and comfort that comes from a simpler way of life; a better one. The choice has been made for you by those who call you friend for you benefit."\r\r
			We took her. I grabbed her from behind whilst master put a noose around her head. I held her arms as he gagged her cries and bound them. He gave me the knife to use. I cut her free from her sorrowful raiment. I liberated her skin too long denied the kiss of the sun or the comforting touch of society. She stood teary eyed, shaking and naked as a newborn before us. Which she kind of was in a way; a new born slave. Master reached down and using his fingers tested her pussy and licked them before offering me his hand to taste in the tradional way. I felt elated; like a triumphant hunter over his kill or an adventurer atop a mountain. For the first time in my life I had helped Master take a free human being and turn her into a slave; and it felt good. She was beautiful to me then; like some piece of carved alabaster and she stirred me in ways I had never felt for another woman before; I wanted her like the old me was supposed to want her but never quite could.</PersonSpeak>
			<Points>
				<Temprement>1</Temprement>
			</Points>
			<DoEvent>9999</DoEvent>
		</MastersPrize>

		<BreakingThePrize> <SetFlags flagSMBrandGoblins-28="true"/>
			<HideImages/>
			<ShowImage image='Images/Events/SMBrandGoblins/000.jpg' align='2'/>
			<PersonSpeak person="Anna">Master had taken sarha but he hadn’t broken her. Not yet. We led her deeper into the forest and pinned her spread eagle on the ground, the dappled sunlight playing across her bare breasts and exposed pussy. Naked, vulnerable and utterly helpless before his authority. He thought it best to take his time, to show her what she should expect and to allow me to warm her to the idea. I lay atop her belly to belly; my face nestled in her mound whilst my tongue set to work to silently persuade her one woman to another the joy of slavery. He gave me a little time to work on her before Master set to with his own efforts. Lifting me up he penetrated my womanhood and holding my rear still he fucked me barely an inch from the end of Sarhas nose and I was dripping juice all over her face. I felt her react to us. I felt her vagina convulse around my tongue, felt her nipples respond to my touch, heard the indrawn breath and moans muffled by the gag of her own panties. It was so very hard not to bring her but that honor belonged to Master. When He came we exploded our fluids across her vision. Before she was beautiful but seeing her stretched out and sticky was breath taking.\r\r
			I licked her face and breasts clean of his seed; making sure that Sarha could see what I was doing I sucked him back up to full strength for her. I supported her head with my creamed pussy as master mounted her. I will never forget the look on My Sarhas face as Master penetrated her virgin pussy; his perfect emerald shaft making deep rhythmic thrusts into her pale trembling body. Nor will I forget the moment when her first orgasm took her; the first of many that day.\r\r
			When taking her back her home it was I who helped her become settled into the life of a slave. I wasn't allowed to speak human to her so I had to teach her her first words of goblin. It was my hand that held the leash, my arm that raised the whip when she faltered and if Master wasn't satisfied with her progress He would string us up and whip us both. She slept between us but whilst Master was the one inside her she would turn to me for comfort and reassurance. Master fucked her as a man should fuck his slave but I made love to her one slave to another; he broke her and I rebuilt her.\r\r
			When we retuned home Master gave Sarha to his brother Kroas. Now Kroas was a mans man with no ardour for the female flesh; Kroas felt it was a pity that I became Anna and offered to take me as I was. His choice of "wife" and of his slaves very much reflected this lifestyle. They are happy together and this would be all well and good but she could provide him no children. That's why they needed someone like Sarha and Kroas was delighted with the gift. He branded her as “the chained mere” and my Sarha was no more.\r\r
			Using means arcane his wife Gro'Bhagh ensured that her first and only child to Kroas was the son they craved. After that they had little use for her as she did not suit their tastes sexualy and they thought it too risky for her to bare another of his children. They sold her as wife to one of the local frontiersmen and she seems happy and well pleased with her man when we visit her. Her eldest daughter Kekiss is held slave by the chiefs son Kroas Sha'han; its a family name as the big cock tends to be one of the things that get handed down.</PersonSpeak>
			<Points>
				<Nymphomania>2</Nymphomania>
				<Temprement>2</Temprement>
			</Points>
			<DoEvent>9999</DoEvent>
		</BreakingThePrize>

		<LanguageBarrier> <SetFlags flagSMBrandGoblins-18="true"/>	<SetFlags flagSMBrandGoblins-19="true"/>
			<ShowImage image='Images/Events/SMBrandGoblins/000.jpg' align='2'/>
			<PersonSpeak person="#slavemakername">You don’t seem to be able to talk our language when Mar’ek is around but you seem to get along just fine when he isn’t here. Could you tell me why?</PersonSpeak>
			<PersonSpeak person="Anna">Most goblins don’t speak human languages at all and most slaves don’t speak better than a rough pigeon goblin dialect. They use human slaves as translators. You must understand that Shak’ren is a speaker. It’s His to negotiate on the behalf of the tribe. Speekers are tasked with persuading humans to sign themselves in to slavery; just like He did for me. He can’t afford to have a slave that gives people the impression that He is using a translator; it smacks of incompetence. If I wanted to stay with him I had to learn.\r\r
			When He took me in he made it his business to drum goblin into me. He forbade me from talking in Maraduke. Me not talking Maraduke protects His reputation from slander and it helped me to learn. Me talking in near flawless goblak enhances His prestige as they believe that only the most gifted speaker can teach a human to speak properly like a real person.\r\r
			The rule is that I am only allowed to speak in human languages when its unavoidable; and Shak’ren gets to decide when that applies. When He is with us He can speak for me so it’s not unavoidable. I am supposed to pretend I don’t understand this language so if you want to address me you will have to ask him to translate for us. If he allows it you have to understand that he may not translate the question you ask and if he allows me to answer the one you hear may not be the one I give.</PersonSpeak>
			<PersonSpeak person="#slavemakername">What happens if you speak our language?</PersonSpeak>
			<PersonSpeak person="Anna">One to six strikes with His cane for each proper noun, verb or adjective and one per two other words. Sometimes I get away with a good spanking depending on what He needs me for or the severity. For a conversation; last I got three sand turns of the whip…about ¾ of an hour.</PersonSpeak>
			<PersonSpeak person="#slave">It’s a good job he didn’t find out about our last conversation then.</PersonSpeak>
			<PersonSpeak person="Anna">Off Couse He did; that’s what I got the whipping for.</PersonSpeak>
			<PersonSpeak person="#slave">How?</PersonSpeak>
			<PersonSpeak person="Anna">Because I told Him; just as I will about this one</PersonSpeak>
			<PersonSpeak person="#slave">Why would you do that?</PersonSpeak>
			<PersonSpeak person="Anna">I have a responsibility to obey my Shak’ren. It is the duty of a slave to report her crimes to her Master and ask for the appropriate punishment. When He returns later I will tell Him about this and beg Him to Whip me for at least an hour and a half like I deserve, he’ll be lenient so it will probably end up something like an hour to half an hour.</PersonSpeak>
			<PersonSpeak person="#slave">Couldn’t you just not tell him?</PersonSpeak>
			<PersonSpeak person="Anna">I can’t, I won’t. I must serve. He is Master. Anna is slave; that is all.</PersonSpeak>
			<PersonSpeak person="#slave">Perhaps we shouldn’t come back, if this is going to get you into trouble.</PersonSpeak>
			<AddText>Anna is suddenly serious dropping to her knees and prostrating her nude body before you.</AddText>
			<PersonSpeak person="Anna">Please don’t stop. #master #slavemakername I beg of you. These conversations are a joy to me and I have missed this kind of human contact for too long</PersonSpeak>
			<PersonSpeak person="#slavemakername">Won’t your master get upset and punish if you continue to defy him?</PersonSpeak>
			<PersonSpeak person="Anna">My Shak’rens law is that I am forbidden to speak in human or with humans under pain of the lash. As long as I continue to submit myself to His discipline His will is unbroken. It is only whipping; If this was truly a concern to Him His punishment of me would be far worse. Do not concern yourself with this slaves deserved punishment; we are whipped or worse for less or no reason every day.</PersonSpeak>
			<PersonSpeak person="#slavemakername">And what of us; will your master grow angry at us for defying his ban?</PersonSpeak>
			<PersonSpeak person="#slavemakername">Shak’ren would never do that over something so trivial as a stupid stubborn cunt like me. He is a just and kind master. You should feel free to speak of anything I said to you with Him. Ask; ask Him to show you just how good and fare He truly is. Ask Him to demonstrate my punishments for you and you will see for yourself that He is all that I know Him to be. He is my Master and I love being his; whips and all.</PersonSpeak>
			<DoEvent>9999</DoEvent>
		</LanguageBarrier>

		<AnnaOnMaids> <SetFlags flagSMBrandGoblins-20="true"/>
			<HideImages/>
			<ShowImage image='Images/Events/SMBrandGoblins/000.jpg' align='2'/>
			<PersonSpeak person="Anna">I remember this girl, she was Va’kesh, his maid and a sign of his wealth and privalage. Sho’lahl was a goblin whilst Shak’ren had paid for her she wasn’t actually his slave per say. She wore his collar but not his brand. Its below wife but above the rank of slave. Some masters treat their maids almost as well as they treat their wives and others no better than their slaves; shak’ren was of the former variety.\r\r
			Most goblin women spend at least a few years as a maid before they marry. Sho’lahl thought master was going to marry her. She was pregnant with his child after all; most maids do marry after their first birth and master was unmarried.\r\r
			Lhal didn’t like watching, she didn’t like putting on a show, she didn’t like women and she didn’t like me. I was pregnant at the time and she did not like that; she wanted Shak’ren to get rid of me. He put her in her place.\r\r
			He forbid her clothing and leashed our collars together with just a few inches of leather; I spent three months bound to her. We ate together, bathed together, slept together. We sucked cock together, were fucked together, whipped together, punished together, screamed together, came together. When you hold a woman close and seen her face wracked with pleasure or pain, to know that she has done the same to you and that in a little while probably will again; it forms a bond.\r\r
			When He cut us free we kissed and scissored then and there. The sight of His women together; our bellies swollen with His children; out moist pussies grinding as we moaned and called out to the Master was too much for him. He took out His Cock and we took turns to stroke and suck him until he came all over our bodies. He was so impressed that he invited some of his friends around the next night for a repeat performance.\r\r
			Shak’ren sold her as wife to one of his cosines shortly after. I thing he was taken by how well she had sucked his cock; how she laughed and smilled when he jizzed over her face, how skilfully she court some of it and the way she looked in his eyes as she swallowed. I danced for the guests at her wedding and I prepared her passage for his cock. I remember how proud and happy she was when he branded her thigh with his mark.</PersonSpeak>
			<Points>
				<Lust>2</Lust>
				<Nymphomania>1</Nymphomania>
			</Points>
			<DoEvent>9999</DoEvent>
		</AnnaOnMaids>

		<AnnaOnPublicSex> <SetFlags flagSMBrandGoblins-21="true"/>
			<HideImages/>
			<ShowImage image='Images/Events/SMBrandGoblins/000.jpg' align='2'/>
			<PersonSpeak person="Anna">There is a difference between public sex and private.\r\r
			When Master publicly fucks or punishes me its a way for him to show his prowess and dominance. The positions we he uses are meant to display by value; my body, my pleasure and my submission. Many younger goblins tend loud, showy an energetic; its all very fun and I enjoy being a party favor as much as the next slave but it isn't at all mature. Like many older goblins Master prefers to be slower, more measured; showing off my training, aesthetics senses and skill. Its as much for the pleasure of the audience as it is for the participants.\r\r
			Private sex between master and slave is different. Master doesn't have to worry about his face or status. Master can focus on his pleasure, on his desires, on his needs. I love showing off for my master but I love to have intimate time with him alone or with another. When its just master and us and he binds me its because he desires to punish or humiliate me. I love to be able to just focus on pleasing my master.</PersonSpeak>
			<Points>
				<Lust>2</Lust>
				<Intelligence>1</Intelligence>
				<Morality>-0.5</Morality>
			</Points>
			<DoEvent>9999</DoEvent>
		</AnnaOnPublicSex>

		<AnnaOnAnimism> <SetFlags flagSMBrandGoblins-22="true"/>
			<ShowImage image='Images/Events/SMBrandGoblins/000.jpg' align='2'/>
			<PersonSpeak person="Anna">For goblins animism is more than just wearing ears and going Nya now and then. Its older, deeper, darker. Its the first way they ever understood and interacted with humanity. It's completely embedded in their culture and it heavily it colors the way they see us.\r\r
			You see humans like me/us don't have actual souls per say. We have animal spirit totems instead. I learned when I became Anna that my spirit is the rabbit. Its the delusion of being people that makes us so silly and petty and cruel. Animals aren't like that; animals are true to their instincts. By abandoning her personality, her humanity and embracing her inner animal a captive girl becomes a much happier slave woman. Master is no animist and yet he had me envisage myself as a rabbit. Master would reward me by having me frolic as a rabbit. I loved being his rabbit; when Anna gets to play bunny hops and nibbles on master carrot.\r\r
			Lots of slaves -particularly child slaves- are given the names of animals. Child names are usually affectionate; 'playful puppy', 'happy bunny', 'fluffy kitten'. When they get old enough to be of real use to the Masters they are branded with a new altered name to reflect that.\r\r
			True traditional animist tribes are quite different to Masters. They live away from well settled human lands; in the wild places of the world. Animist think of humans as livestock or prey. They don't talk to us, let us speak language or wear clothes; animals don't wear clothes. Animist tribes don't bargain or negotiate or trade with humans. To them we are just prey for the taking; to be trapped or hunted down.</PersonSpeak>
			<Points>
				<Temperament>-1</Temperament>
				<Sensability>1</Sensability>
				<Refinement>-0.5</Refinement>
				<Joy>2</Joy>
			</Points>
			<DoEvent>9999</DoEvent>
		</AnnaOnAnimism>

		<AnnaOnCannibalism> <SetFlags flagSMBrandGoblins-23="true"/>
			<ShowImage image='Images/Events/SMBrandGoblins/000.jpg' align='2'/>
			<PersonSpeak person="Anna">You must understand that goblins will eat human.\r\r
			After a battle goblin warriors eat the hearts of their slain enemies. This is so they can take on the strength of their worthy opponents; it’s a mark of respect. It’s also a celebration festival for a victory as welll as a funeral feast for the fallen.\r\r
			When slaves like me die the tribe usually harvests and eat certain body parts. It is a communion; a thanksgiving for our lives and a way so that we can be physically and spiritually be one with the tribe even in death. We believe our spirits nourish and empower the tribe; that if we are worthy someday we might be reborn as goblin slaves.\r\r
			Goblins can and do enslave women for their milk; I myself nursed many goblin babes in my time. However only animists still hunt humans for their meat. Strict animist tribes are known to sacrifice and feast on their slaves at their high holy nights.</PersonSpeak>
			<Points>
				<Morality>-1</Morality>
				<Joy>-2</Joy>
			</Points>
			<DoEvent>9999</DoEvent>
		</AnnaOnCannibalism>

		<AnnaOnFurries> <SetFlags flagSMBrandGoblins-24="true"/>
			<ShowImage image='Images/Events/SMBrandGoblins/000.jpg' align='2'/>
			<PersonSpeak person="Anna">Animist goblins teach us slaves to behave like animals. Some go a lot further than that. Goblin blood is active. It can be used to weaken a slave’s physical and mental grip on her humanity.Small changes are not unusual. Master has bought and traded slaves with minor animal characteristics. Things like tales, inhuman ears or animal eyes. I witnessed the shaman transform one of masters’ slaves; he made cat claws to grow out of her fingers.\r
			I have heard tales that powerful flesh crafters have the power to turn humans in to furries, moemon or even animals. They say that goblin wrought slaves are fertile to the Masters. None of the fury slaves I ever knew got pregnant but they were captures. I was once fucked by a deep wilds trader who said his mere was a centaur. I don’t know if it was true but he had the biggest cock I ever tasted.\r
			I wonder what I’d be like as a Moemon?</PersonSpeak>
			<Points>
				<Joy>1</Joy>
			</Points>
			<DoEvent>9999</DoEvent>
		</AnnaOnFurries>

		<AnnaOnNudity> <SetFlags flagSMBrandGoblins-27="true"/>
			<HideImages/>
			<ShowImage image='Images/Events/SMBrandGoblins/000.jpg' align='2'/>
			<PersonSpeak person="Anna">For me nudity isn't about being sexual or arousing. It about being one with nature, about giving up the trappings and comforts of my old life, about exposing this body and spirit to Master. Being naked doesn't make Master or any other male goblin want a girl more; it just makes her a slave. If she is his slave he can have her any way he wants. If she isn't his slave then its up to her master whether a male can have her. \r\r
			Goblins find clothed women far more arousing than nude ones; they see naked bodies everyday. It allows the imagination to run free. It implies you are apart, free; just ready and waiting to be taken in and taught proper manners. Goblins love a good challenge. Some men like to play dress up. To give their slaves the role of the naive village girl, the defiant warrior or the haughty princess; all just waiting for their master to teach them their place. \r\r
			Slaves usually wear clothes in the cold of winter. They like the cold. They don't do much hunting or travelling in the winter and they have many festivals that time of year. Lets just say that there is a reason that most children are conceived in the dark of winter. As a result goblins find the standard slave winter wear highly erotic. It covers and warms yet at the same time allows him to make full use of us without exposing us to the cold; well not too much at any rate. </PersonSpeak>
			<DoEvent>9999</DoEvent>
		</AnnaOnNudity>
	<!--   ________________________________________________   ANNA STORY END   ______________________________________________________    -->
    
    <!--   ________________________________________________   MAREK STORY START   ______________________________________________________    -->
		<MarekStorytime>
			<AskQuestions caption='What would you like to hear'>
				<Question event='MarekStorytimeRandom'>I want to hear a new story</Question>
				<if flagSMBrandGoblins-25="true">
					<Question event='LucyAndJustine'>I want to hear the harvest sisters again</Question>
				</if>
				<if flagSMBrandGoblins-26="true">
					<Question event='ThreeBrothers1'>I want to hear the three brothers again</Question>
				</if>
				<Question event='9999'>On second thoughts lets not</Question>
			</AskQuestions>		
		</MarekStorytime>

		<MarekStorytimeRandom>
			<if flagSMBrandGoblins-25="true" flagSMBrandGoblins-26="true">
				<SetText></SetText>
				<PersonSpeak person="Ma'rek">I'm sorry, but I have nothing no new stories to tell.</PersonSpeak>
				<DoEvent>MarekStorytime</DoEvent>
				<EndEvent/>
			</if>
			<Alternatives>
				<Alternative flagSMBrandGoblins-25="false">
					<DoEvent now="true">LucyAndJustine</DoEvent>
				</Alternative>
				<Alternative flagSMBrandGoblins-26="false">
					<DoEvent now="true">ThreeBrothers1</DoEvent>
				</Alternative>
			</Alternatives>
		</MarekStorytimeRandom>		
		<MoralFail>
			<PersonSpeak person="#slave"> I am sorry mister Mar'ek. I cant decide. I just can't work out the right answer.</PersonSpeak>
			<PersonSpeak person="Ma'rek">Sometimes a hidden meaning is meant to stay hidden. That is alright. After all its not for nothing that you belong to your #Master. #heshe will teach you what you should think...that's probably just as well. We can decide these things for you; It is what us masters are here for after all</PersonSpeak>
			<Points>
				<Temperament>-1</Temperament>
				<Intelligence>-1</Intelligence>
			</Points>
			<DoEvent>9999</DoEvent>
		</MoralFail>
		
		<LucyAndJustine> <SetFlags flagSMBrandGoblins-25="true"/>
			<PersonSpeak person="Ma'rek">There is a town nestled in a clear valley the great forest. In that town lived a man of note. He had a wife he married for her respectability and 	money and a maid her took for her lusty body and fair face. Each bore him a daughter. From his wife Justine; the apple of his eye. From his maid Lucy; his perpetual shame. Resolved to be rid of Lucy he went down to the wise men of the green woods. This year there would be a harvest festival of the old rights 
			and Lucy its queen.\r\r
			Lucy was chosen as mistress of the summer and queen of the harvest. At first she was happy and full of pride. She was lauded and showered with flowers and the attentions of the towns men. And yet in the back of her mind doubt; her sire had never done a kind thing for her before nor would the old folk look or speak with her.\r\r </PersonSpeak>
			<DoEvent>LucyAndJustine1</DoEvent>
		</LucyAndJustine>
		<LucyAndJustine1>
			<PersonSpeak person="Ma'rek">Justine was jealous of her bastard sister. For the first time in her life she wasn't the center of attention. The adulation went to Lucy and not Justine. Lucy came to meet with Justine. As Lucy prompted Justine said that they could trade places; that it would be fun. Lucy jumped at this; a chance to taste the life of privilege, a chance to escape the niggling fear of what the harvest festival had in store for her.\r\r
			And so it was done. Lucy took to the fine silks well enough but fond her sisters life stuffy and constrained. Justine enjoyed the freedom of the streets and loved the attention of the festivals though found the work and responsibilities of her sister difficult to bear.\r\r
			And all was seemingly good till the harvest night. Justine went down to the woods to finish the old covenant. The father drank heavily into his cups that night. Lucy interrogated her faithless father and inebriated he boasted his deed. Horrified by what she had been a party to Lucy ran down to the hollows to 
			rescue her sister.\r\r</PersonSpeak>
			<DoEvent>LucyAndJustine2</DoEvent>
		</LucyAndJustine1>
		<LucyAndJustine2>
			<PersonSpeak person="Ma'rek">When Lucy came upon the glade she found her sister Justine about to choose her new master. Lucy demanded they stop at once. That a terrible injustice had 
			been done and that she would not part with her sister. Goblins never missed a beat; in tune to the rhythm of the stories. By that nights end the sisters would never be parted again. Each bores one half of their brand; ever after they served together under the same.\r\r</PersonSpeak>
			<DoEvent>LucyandJustineMoral</DoEvent>
		</LucyAndJustine2>

		<LucyandJustineMoral>
			<HideImages/>
			<ShowImage image='Images/Events/SMBrandGoblins/pauper.jpg' aling="2"/>
			<PersonSpeak person="Ma'rek">Cheek to cheek. Breast to breast;\r
			Two slaves bound together in the same nest.</PersonSpeak>
			<PersonSpeak person="Ma'rek">I hope you enjoyed my story. Can you think about it #slave. All goblin tales are true. They carry hidden meaning and power to those who understand them them. Will you try?</PersonSpeak>
				<AskQuestions caption='What would you like to hear'>
				<Question event='LandJMoral1'>Family is more important</Question>
				<if sensibility="40+">
					<Question event='LandJMoral2'>Justine was too vain</Question>
				</if>
				<if intelligence="40+">
					<Question event='LandJMoral3'>Slavery is equality</Question>
				</if>
				<if obedience="40+">
					<Question event='LandJMoral4'>Lucy was wrong</Question>
				</if>
				<if morality="40+">
					<Question event='LandJMoral5'>The father was cruel</Question>
				</if>
				<if temperament="40+">
					<Question event='LandJMoral6'>Goblins are tricky</Question>
				</if>
				<Question event='MoralFail'>I can't think</Question>
			</AskQuestions>		
		</LucyandJustineMoral>
		<LandJMoral1>
			<PersonSpeak person="#slave">It is better to be bound as a slave with your sister than to be free without her.</PersonSpeak>
			<PersonSpeak person="Ma'rek">As is right and proper</PersonSpeak>
			<Points>
				<Joy>1</Joy>
				<Morality>2</Morality>
				<Sensibility>1</Sensibility>
			</Points>
			<DoEvent>9999</DoEvent>
		</LandJMoral1>
		<LandJMoral2>
			<PersonSpeak person="#slave">Justine was a jealous attention whore. She wasn't sensitive to the needs and fears of her sister. She walked blindly into danger. In the end she deserved everything she got.</PersonSpeak>
			<PersonSpeak person="Ma'rek">Humility is important to goblins to; its one of the first things we teach new slaves.</PersonSpeak>
			<Points>
				<Temperament>1</Temperament>
				<Morality>1</Morality>
				<Sensibility>1</Sensibility>
			</Points>
			<DoEvent>9999</DoEvent>
		</LandJMoral2>		
		<LandJMoral3>
			<PersonSpeak person="#slave">They let status get in the way of being family. As slaves they are equals; free be sisters.</PersonSpeak>
			<PersonSpeak person="Ma'rek">You know I never quite saw it that way before but I do see what you mean. As slaves you differ in actual net worth but you share the same status. In the end all slaves are as sisters.</PersonSpeak>
			<Points>
				<Temperament>-1</Temperament>
				<Morality>1</Morality>
				<Intelligence>2</Intelligence>
				<Conversation>1</Conversation>
			</Points>
			<DoEvent>9999</DoEvent>
		</LandJMoral3>
		<LandJMoral4>
			<PersonSpeak person="#slave"> Lucy shouldn't have tried to fight fate. She tricked her sister and got them both enslaved. She felt guilty for what she had done; she knew she didn't deserve freedom.</PersonSpeak>
			<PersonSpeak person="Ma'rek">It is important to obey your but it is also important to forgive. When you become ours you are purged of your old life. A girl is absolved of her sins and leaves her pain and name behind; she is reborn as a new slave.</PersonSpeak>
			<Points>
				<Obedience>2</Obedience>
				<Morality>1</Morality>
				<Refinement>1</Refinement>
				<Temperament>-1</Temperament>
			</Points>
			<DoEvent>9999</DoEvent>
		</LandJMoral4>
		<LandJMoral5>
			<PersonSpeak person="#slave"> He shouldn't have treated Lucy like that. He didn't deserve either of them. They took Justine to punish him for neglecting Lucy. They are probably better off as slaves than his daughters.</PersonSpeak>
			<PersonSpeak person="Ma'rek">I can tell you that as a people we don't like child neglect; or spousal abuse for that matter. We have always tried to our best to take in the vulnerable and give them a new family; its a part of who we are.</PersonSpeak>
			<Points>
				<Temperament>1</Temperament>
				<Morality>2</Morality>
			</Points>
			<DoEvent>9999</DoEvent>
		</LandJMoral5>
		
		<LandJMoral6>
			<PersonSpeak person="#slave">Goblins are cunning and love enslaving women. If you have a pussy and you value your freedom you need to think long and hard before dealing with them.</PersonSpeak>
			<PersonSpeak person="Ma'rek">Of course, we are Goblins after all.</PersonSpeak>
			<Points>
				<Temperament>2</Temperament>
				<Intelligence>1</Intelligence>
			</Points>
			<DoEvent>9999</DoEvent>
		</LandJMoral6>
		
		<ThreeBrothers1>
			<SetFlags flagSMBrandGoblins-26="true"/>
			<PersonSpeak person="Ma'rek"> Briac the strong, Lornar the silverd and Den the sly where three brothers. \r
			They where of old fast friends but they did each love the fair maid Greta. \r
			Her hair was as spun gold, her cheeks rosy hue and her voice peals of music; she was truely the fairest maid in all the land. \r
			Her heart was young and fickle as is the way of maids \r
			had she affection for the Mighty and proud Briac \r
			So to the pleasing continence and honeyed words of Lornar stirred her loins \r
			For ill favored Den she felt naught but contempt. \r\r
			Nixu was a wise and powerful shaman, learned in the ways of fairness and the heart. \r
			Fearing the loss of his beloved the Eldest brother Briac sought Nixu of sage word and counsel \r
			"Oh wise goblin, I am but a rude man, my brother is a man of beauty, how may I outshine him and I claim the fair Gretas heart?" \r
			"You are the stronger but your brother is of temper black. Challenge him for maiden fair, taunt him \r
			win or loose your strength and love will be show and he will be revealed, she will want of him no more. \r
			Thus did Briac challenge the middle brother and his pride stung he rashly accepted the duel. \r\r
			Lonar was no mans fool and sensing the danger sought out Nixu for aid. \r
			"Oh wise goblin, I am but a weak man, my brother is a man of might, How may I defeat him and win the fair Gretas heart?" \r
			The goblin brought forth a potion of bull's baked blood and bade him \r
			"Drink this on the day of battle, victory will surely be yours." \r
			Lonar agreed and took the daught, eager now for conflict and the maids victory. \r\r
			Den the sly was the most patient and quick witted of his brothers. \r
			He had planned to wait, surely the fair Greta would tier of his quarrelsome elder siblings and on that day he would be there. \r
			But now duel would resolve the conflict once and forever, his day would never come, so he sought out Nixu's aid \r
			"Oh wise goblin, I am but a forsaken man, my brothers duel in for her. How may I outwit them and steal the fair Gretas Heart?" \r
			The goblin brought forth a bone knife, leather bindings and a halter. \r
			"Take you this shaft and it thought your breast pierce, your lovers spirit will take flight \r 
			As this form bind her and take her, none can stop you. \r
			Do this when the melee draws all focus, bring her before me \r
			I will take the blade, cut the bonds; release the spell and return life's spirit to your heart. \r
			With this halter about her neck she will evermore belong to any he that takes the maiden's head."</PersonSpeak>
			<DoEvent>ThreeBrothers2</DoEvent>
		</ThreeBrothers1>
		<ThreeBrothers2>
			<PersonSpeak person="Ma'rek"> And thus the day of battle dawned, all the brothers made ready. \r
			Lonar and Briac met before the assembled multitude, all knew the tale and all awaited resolution, \r
			the flighty Greta stood to watch her admirers battle for her. \r
			Both the brothers resolute and sure. His cause just and victory certain. \r 
			Briac taunted the prideful Lonar just as Nixu had bade him but he only smiled faintly. \r
			Lonar brought the potion to his lips and drunk deeply of it, just has nixu bade he. \r\r
			Sinews of iron grew and wrapped around his writhing frame. Horns sprung forth and foot spit to cloven hoof. Lonar stood now towering over foe, \r
			lashing forth claws in single mighty blow slew he his horrified brother; victory his just as Nixu promised. \r
			Lonar threw back his great head and bellowed out his triumph, he strode forward to claim his prize \r
			Fair Greta gazed upon his fell countenance and turned from him and quit the village. \r 
			He was revealed and she would have none of him; just as nixu had promised. 
			With shaft and spear Lonars kinsmen slew the beast. \r\r
			Den took the knife as the goblin bade him, to his eyes all the world was as of shadow \r
			From nixus dark cave he spyed a distant light and knew his beloved. \r
			His spirit took flight through stone and air, hoaving in on his goal. \r
			Den espied the fleeing Greta and seized her, binding her fast and feintd. \r
			Bearing captive Den flew fourth, soul seeking flesh, for there he would claim his unwilling bride.</PersonSpeak>
			<DoEvent>ThreeBrothers3</DoEvent>
		</ThreeBrothers2>
		<ThreeBrothers3>
			<PersonSpeak person="Ma'rek">
			In to dark cave Den brough her. The wise goblin knew the deed was done, \r
			in one fluid movement he took firm the blade, ripped it from Dens breast and cut loose the maids bonds; \r
			she awoke, her beauty radiant even in the dark as Dens soul took root once more in his mortal frame.\r
			But all was not well for from his his heart blood pored forth; nixus spell had death not stopped, only stayed \r
			he, the last of the brothers proud perished; his lifes blood spent \r
			Wise Nixu, learnered in the ways of fairness and the heart knew it was good; \r
			the three brothers who should never had raised hand or plotted against the other had received their just reward. \r 
			Brothers are brothers first and forever; to betray that is to betray all.\r	</PersonSpeak>
			<DoEvent>ThreeBrothers4</DoEvent>
		</ThreeBrothers3>
		<ThreeBrothers4>
			<PersonSpeak person="Ma'rek">
			The poor maid wept, her tears bitter salt. She knew not where she was nor how she came. Her thief lie slain. \r
			Hope sprang within as was her saviour not Nixu, learnered in the ways of fairness and heart? \r
			"Oh wise and merciful goblin, I am a maiden cast adrift, my loves lie fallen and I am stolen far from home. \r
			What must I do? How shall I be saved? who will hold fair Gretas Heart?" \r\r
			"Fear, not" He spake "Dry your tears, today justice hoves true. \r
			All is not yet lost, I see your heart and body have already fair and just claim, \r
			I swear you will yet know hearth and home, husband and babe. \r
			Kneel before me, With this cord I knot the ties that bind about your neck \r
			by my power you shall know the man to own your heart, \r 
			the one who will mark you his and take	you as bride ever more." \r\r
			She sat quiet and stirred, her tears of grief and fear shone with hope anew. \r
			She knelt before his wisdom and compassion, closing her eyes and bowing her head \r
			"Yes, use your power, show me this man true, \r
			let him come and claim me, mend my broken heart"\r
			The learnered goblin secured firm the bridal, thrust his claim and took the fair maids head, by his power mastered her. \r
			The young maid Greta; foolish and fair in equal measure -though maid no longer, her love was never certain. \r
			Her breast sought strength, her loins sought charm, but no swain chose she. \r
			Now heart and body are rightly owned, Nixu's due for four oaths kept, \r 
			branded bride for mastering groom, babes in arms by warm homes hearth; just as Nixu promised. \r
			Slave she of him that holds her leash; Greta his evermore, just as Nixu promised.</PersonSpeak>
			<DoEvent>ThreeBrothersMoral</DoEvent>
		</ThreeBrothers4>
		<ThreeBrothersMoral>
				<HideImages/>
				<ShowImage image='Images/Events/SMBrandGoblins/pauper.jpg' align='2'/>
				<PersonSpeak person="Ma'rek">So what did you think of that one? Three brothers is old but its one of my favourites. It hales back to a time when we where more free to be of ourselves. Can you puzzle out the inner understanding of this one #slave?. You might learn something</PersonSpeak>
					<AskQuestions caption='What would you like to hear'>
					<Question event='ThreeBrothersMoral1'>Blood is thicker</Question>
					<if sensibility="40+">
						<Question event='ThreeBrothersMoral2'>Den was a fool</Question>
					</if>
					<if morality="40+">
						<Question event='ThreeBrothersMoral3'>Nixu was cruel</Question>
					</if>
					<if intelligence="40+">
						<Question event='ThreeBrothersMoral4'>Karma's a bitch</Question>
					</if>
					<if temperament="40+">
						<Question event='ThreeBrothersMoral5'>Greta should have chosen</Question>
					</if>
					<Question event='MoralFail'>I can't think</Question>
				</AskQuestions>		
		</ThreeBrothersMoral>
		<ThreeBrothersMoral1>
			<PersonSpeak person="#slave">Family mustn't kill each other; should not betray each other. Not over her, not at all.</PersonSpeak>
			<PersonSpeak person="Ma'rek">Wise and true. There is a world of women out there to woo or enslave but only one of your bother.</PersonSpeak>
			<Points>
				<Morality>2</Morality>
				<Sensibility>1</Sensibility>
			</Points>
			<DoEvent>9999</DoEvent>
		</ThreeBrothersMoral1>		
		<ThreeBrothersMoral2>
			<PersonSpeak person="#slave">Den was a fool. You can't just steel away a womans body and expect her to love you.</PersonSpeak>
			<PersonSpeak person="Ma'rek">Nice sentiment but you really can. A womans heart is very adaptable; very pragmatic at times. Its an old survival trait; a basic instinct we goblins know full well how to exploit.</PersonSpeak>
			<Points>
				<Temperament>-1</Temperament>
				<Intelligence>2</Intelligence>
				<Consitution>1</Consitution>
			</Points>
			<DoEvent>9999</DoEvent>
		</ThreeBrothersMoral2>
		<ThreeBrothersMoral4>
			<PersonSpeak person="#slave">They shouldn't have gone to Nixiu to help them betray each other; that was just asking for trouble.</PersonSpeak>
			<PersonSpeak person="Ma'rek">We believe in karmic retribution; though sometimes it needs a helping hand. If you ask us for healing expect healing. If you ask for mischief expect mischief, if you ask for treachery then expect treachery.</PersonSpeak>
			<Points>
				<Joy>1</Joy>
				<Morality>1</Morality>
				<Intelligence>1</Intelligence>
			</Points>
			<DoEvent>9999</DoEvent>
		</ThreeBrothersMoral4>
		<ThreeBrothersMoral3>
			<PersonSpeak person="#slave">He tricked the brothers into murder. Right from the start he was out to steal Greta for himself.</PersonSpeak>
			<PersonSpeak person="Ma'rek">Sometimes justice can be harsh. Three brothers loosing themselfs and each other over one woman does not end well. Such conflicts tear families apart and can disrupt whole comunities. Sometimes the bad apples; the bad seed must be purged to preserve the flock, sometimes examples must be made.</PersonSpeak>
			<Points>
				<Joy>-1</Joy>
				<Morality>2</Morality>
				<Temperament>1</Temperament>
			</Points>
			<DoEvent>9999</DoEvent>
		</ThreeBrothersMoral3>
		<ThreeBrothersMoral5>
			<PersonSpeak person="#slave">That woman should have made a choice and stuck with it; even if the choice was to have none of them. Because she wouldn't make up her own mind she ended up having no choice at all.</PersonSpeak>
			<PersonSpeak person="Ma'rek">Harsh words but true. Remember though that Greta could have walked out of there instead she gave her choice to Nixu and he chose himself. I think she allowed Nixu to take rather than return to loneliness and shame.</PersonSpeak>
			<Points>
				<Temperament>2</Temperament>
				<Morality>1</Morality>
				<Intelligence>1</Intelligence>
			</Points>
			<DoEvent>9999</DoEvent>
		</ThreeBrothersMoral5>		
	<!--   ________________________________________________   MAREK STORY END   ______________________________________________________    -->
		
	<!--   ________________________________________________   GOBLIN BADEND START   ______________________________________________________    -->	
		<Marekslavebadend>
			<if pregnancytype-slavemaker="Goblin" pregnancytype-current='Goblin'>
				<ShowImage image='Images/Events/SMBrandGoblins/000.jpg' align='2'/>
				<AddText>You recline naked on the furs next to #slave. Your swollen pregnant bellies and breasts resting against each other; her slave collar securely leashed to the iron ring permanently welded around your neck. You arms and legs are bound in an embrace; holding you together for hours and forcing you to rub your pussies up against each other every time either of you shift. You have no inclination to sit; the brand forever burned into your ass still hurts too much for you to consider it. Right now you would almost welcome the whip if it meant you could move and stretch again. \r\r
				You both lie there awake; listening to Sha'ren making love to Anna in the darkness. You wonder which one of you will be next. You hear a cry of pleasure in the darkness; it won't be long now. You wonder what he will do to you when he comes to fuck you once again.  \r\r
				Once you where the #master; the naked girl in your arms your slave. Now she is your sister in bondage. You bare the mark of the same iron, the tracts of the same whip, the seed from the same cock, the children of the same loins; slaves of the same master. \r\r
				Sensing a presence you look up to see Master standing over you. A whip in one hand and his cock in the other; dripping warm semen and vaginal juices onto your face as Master smiles darkly at you. It's your turn...</AddText>
			<else>if</else>
				<if pregnancytype-slavemaker="Goblin">
					<ShowImage image='Images/Events/SMBrandGoblins/000.jpg' align='2'/>
					<AddText>
					You sit naked on the soft furs warming yourself by the fire. About your familiar collar is the comforting weight of the leash restraining you to a stake. In your arms is the most precious thing in your small world. The green baby girl you bore for your Master. His daughter is suckling milk from your breasts.\r\r
					The Master is lustily fucking you bound sister slave; taking her from behind like a bitch in heat. You hear Anna's muffled cries as she screams out her pleasure around the gag. You giggle; judging by the tempo if his meaty thrusts it won’t be long before its time for Master to have his cock cleaned again and Annas all tied up at the moment. Your mouth and pussy moisten in anticipation.\r\r
					“Slave want milk too” Is the thought repeating over and over in your mind</AddText>
					<else>if</else>
						<ShowImage image='Images/Events/SMBrandGoblins/000.jpg' align='2'/>
						<AddText>Two years; two years since he leashed your destiny, two years since he mastered your pussy, two years since he branded your flesh as his; to own and use and fuck as he sees fit.\r\r
						The collar Master sew around your neck is chained to your elder sister slave Anna and has been for months. She has been of great comfort to you in your convalescence. She is helping you into your traveling harness; pulling a knotted crotch rope over your swollen belly to your bound hands. Smiling she embraces you as closely as your pregnant body will allow. She caresses your hair and backside, leaning in she licks His semen from your chin before kissing you to steal the lingering taste of his manhood from your mouth.\r\r
						Your hear your master call your you by your new name; your real name. "Tornesh Kekiss"; The chained pleasure, the disciplined clitoris, the whipped orgasm. You sometimes dimly remember that once you wore a different name, once you held the whip, once slaves served at your pleasure. You feel the unborn life stirring within you and the memory fades...Bliss\r\r
						You feel the comforting and familiar tug of the leash firmly held in your masters grip. His dark eyes surveys your body filled with absolute possession; his rock solid erection displaying his approval of you. Your nude body tenses in anticipation for the meaty...THWAK of his cane against your ass. You are away; jogging through your forest home; your eyes fixed on the horizon and a new day in your own small world.</AddText>
				</if>
			</if>
			<DoEvent>9800</DoEvent>
		</Marekslavebadend>

		<MareksNotEnd> <SetFlags flagSMBrandGoblins-38="true"/>
			<ShowImage image='Images/Events/SMBrandGoblins/000.jpg' align='2'/>
			<AddText>The last few days -has it been only days? Its felt more like weeks- They have pass by in a blur of sex and bondage; orgasm after orgasm. You have spent most of this time bound and blind folded. When you weren't being fucked you were being whipped or degraded or scant hours spent in restless sleep. Your throat is horse with cries of pain, pleasure, submission and all three at once. You feel like you have thrown up and you can still taste the vile whatever it was he force fed you. Suddenly you are almost blinded by the light as the hood is removed and you see Mar'ek standing naked over you.</AddText>
			<PersonSpeak person="Mar'ek">I've come to a decision about what to do with you. I've decided not to keep you as a slave, at least not yet; no offense. I already have a good slave here and more at home, I don't really need another right now and to be honest I am not as young as I don't have the time to train you properly out here. I could sell you. I don't know the local markets and none of my regular contacts live near here so I may not get the best price for you. Still I could fetch a hansom profit on your ass.</PersonSpeak>
			<PersonSpeak person="Mar'ek">I've decided to let you go; put you on a long leash as it were. As I said I don't have any local contacts; not like you do. You would be far more useful to me at large; a sol’kesh - a domestic client. At the end of the day I am a trader and I go were the profit is. I need a competitive edge, an in to the mioyan markets; that you.</PersonSpeak>
			<PersonSpeak person="Mar'ek">Perhaps if this experience still holds an appeal to you I can persuade you to consent to be my slave at a latter more convenient date. I promise you will never want for the firm hand of a kind master. I think next time you will put up more of a fight but I look forward to the challenge.</PersonSpeak>
			<AddText>Reaching for the rope around your neck Mar'ek hesitates.</AddText>
			<PersonSpeak person="Mar'ek">Now the time has come to release you I find I don't want you to leave; my dick feels sad to see you go. Before you run along won't you kiss him better for me?</PersonSpeak>
			<ChangeTime>4</ChangeTime>
			<SMPoints>			
				<Lust>-20</Lust>
				<Dominance>-15</Dominance>
				<Nymphomania>10</Nymphomania>
			</SMPoints>
			<if canimpregnate-slavemaker="Goblin"> 
				<if chance="10%">
					<Impregnate person='slavemaker' type='Goblin' count='1' gestation='20+random20'/>		
				</if>
				<if chance="10%">
					<Impregnate person='slave' type='Goblin' count='1' gestation='20+random20'/>		
				</if>
			</if>
			<DoEvent>9999</DoEvent>
		</MareksNotEnd>
	<!--   ________________________________________________   GOBLIN BADEND END  ______________________________________________________    -->
	<GSWIP>
		<ShowImage image='Images/Events/SMBrandGoblins/000.jpg' align='2'/>
		<SetText>Work in Progress, for updates look at futanaripalace.com - Slave Maker - Proposed-addion-to-SM-world</SetText>
		<SetFlags flagSMBrandGoblins-37="false"/>
		<SetFlags flagSMBrandGoblins-40="false"/>
		<SetFlags flagSMBrandGoblins-41="false"/>
		<DoEvent>9999</DoEvent>
	</GSWIP>
	</Events>
</Language>		