<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!-- vars and flags
savedvar1_RedLily = blowjob skill
savedvar2_RedLily = day counter
savedvar3_RedLily = bathroom

flagRedLily_1 = 
flagRedLily_2 = 
flagRedLily_3 = did fight Poison
flagRedLily_4 = 
flagRedLily_5 = 
flagRedLily_6 = 
flagRedLily_7 = 
flagRedLily_8 = 
flagRedLily_9 = 
flagRedLily_10 = 

-->


<!-- Text to put
"Red Lily","You can either visit the Red Lily and look around, or work here (especially if contractually obligated)."

if(_root.NumEvent == 10275)
      {
         super.AutoAttachAndShowMovie("scarlet_happy",1,1,1);
         _root.SetText("She places her hand on your head, she begins muttering under her voice. You stare at her, your body becoming unresponsive. At once a magical energy surges toward you. It feels controlled and restrictive in nature somehow. You could easily repel it, but you feel that this is the oath. With some reluctance you accept it inside of you.\n\n");
         _root.Person_Speak("Queen","Very well. You\'re now bound to me for the time being, I\'ll release you if you desire after the business at hand is done. You shall not communicate this to anyone. I am half demon, this has been passed down matrilinealy for numerous generations. A pendant has also been passed down as well. It has the ability to suppress the nastier side effects of being a half demon if one is pure enough. On the other hand if someone is very corrupt it can be used as a tool of power. To the point; it lost, and must be recovered. Normally I would send my agents out, but they are all female at soul. The reason them being female is inconvenient is because the pendant curses all human females who touch it, making them subservient to the wearer. Hence why I keep a staff of all female servants. I have an agent at the Red Lily whom can further spell out the specifics. She\'ll contact you at the bar if you socialize a bit. Look out for a broom as an identifier. Keep in mind there is a rather large reward for re-obtaining the pendant.",false);
         this.agent_red = true;
         _root.SetSMCustomTrainingDetails("Red Lily","You can either visit the Red Lily and look around, or work here (especially if contractually obligated).");
         _root.ShowSMCustomTraining();
         return true;
      }

if(_root.NumEvent == 10214)
      {
         _root.AddText("");
         _root.PersonSpeak("Women","Fair enough, see you some other time toy.",true);
         _root.AddText("");
         return true;
      }

if(_root.NumEvent == 10235)
      {
         _root.SetText("You give a sheepish shake of your head and return to the bar.");
         _root.DoEvent(10230);
         return true;
      }

if(_root.NumEvent == 10275)
      {
         super.AutoAttachAndShowMovie("scarlet_sad",1,1,1);
         _root.SetText("You sadly shake you head no. Without knowing more about what you\'re swearing your loyalty for, you can\'t throw it away on a whim, even for a friend. The queen nods in understanding, but looks sad and disappointed none the less.");
         this.courtvisit = -1;
         return true;
      }

if(_root.NumEvent == 10202)
      {
         _root.SetText("The lady shrugs her shoulders and walks off");
         this.bathroom = -1;
         return true;
      }

if(_root.NumEvent == 10204)
      {
         _root.SetText("You shake your head in disgust realizing this is unbecoming for you to in front of " + _root.SlaveName + ", and vow to avoid this area.");
         this.bathroom = -1;
         return true;
      }

if(_root.NumEvent == 10209)
      {
         _root.SetText("You spend the rest of the time wandering around with " + _root.SlaveName + ", but don\'t see much going on. Overall though, it was a tranquil walk.");
         _root.Points(0,0,0,0,0,3,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,3,0,0);
         return true;
      }
-->
<Language>

	<Credits> 
		last edited 2015/11
	</Credits>

	<Events>
	

		<Initialise>
		</Initialise>
		

		<UpdateDateAndItems>
		</UpdateDateAndItems>
				

		<EarlyMorning>
		</EarlyMorning>


		<StartMorning>			
		</StartMorning>
		

		<Daily>
		</Daily>

		<StartEvening>
		</StartEvening>
		
		
		<Walk>

			<TownCenter>
			</TownCenter>

			<Palace>
			</Palace>

			<SlaveMarket>
			</SlaveMarket>

			<Slums>
				<RLContractOffer>
					<SetText>While walking through the slums a woman approaches you.\r\r</SetText>
					<PersonSpeak person="Women">Ha! #slavemakername you've made a name for yourself as an entertainer, thanks to your exploits in a certain bathroom. You've got natural skills, so naturally I'd love to have you as a temporary attraction for my business. I would pay handsomely of course, and your slave in training may also work for me. All you have to do is sign this contract. If not, I won't trouble you further, but your business at the stalls will dry up.</PersonSpeak>
					<if smdominance="25+">
						<AskQuestion caption='Do you agree to sign?'>
							<Question event=''>Yes</Question>
							<Question event=''>No</Question>
						</AskQuestion>
					<else>if</else>
						<AddText>\r\r You can feel the proposition making you wet just by thinking about it, you know you can\'t refuse her offer thanks to your submissive nature.</AddText>
						<AskQuestion caption='Do you agree?'>
							<Question event=''>Yes</Question>
						</AskQuestion>
					</if>
				</RLContractOffer>
			</Slums>

			<BeachSwim>
			</BeachSwim>

			<BeachWalk>
			</BeachWalk>

			<BeachPrivate>
			</BeachPrivate>

			<BeachRocks>
			</BeachRocks>

			<DocksPort>
			</DocksPort>

			<DocksSlavePens>
			</DocksSlavePens>

			<Farm>
			</Farm>

			<Forest>
			</Forest>

			<DeepForest>
			</DeepForest>
			
			<RuinedTemple>
			</RuinedTemple>

			<Lake>
			</Lake>

		</Walk>

		<RLSmellRoxyNo>
			<if slavegender='1'>
				<SetText>You resist the urge to smell the girl, although it seems like #slave has not, thanks to his noticeably erect dick.</SetText>
			</if>
			<if slavegender='2'>
				<SetText>You resist the urge to smell the girl, although it seems like #slave has not, thanks to her puffy nipples.</SetText>
			</if>
			<if slavegender='3'>
				<SetText>You resist the urge to smell the girl, although it seems like #slave has not, thanks to her noticeably erect dick, and her puffy nipples.</SetText>
			</if>
		</RLSmellRoxyNo>
		<RLSmellRoxyYes>
			<SetText>As you inhale the slaves intoxicating aroma a, fire forms in your loins. Searching for the closest public place you find a familiar bathroom. You tell #slave to go wait outside as you enter the familiar public bathrooms. You enter the same stall as the last time. You quickly strip and give yourself the quickest route to satisfaction as possible.\r\r As you begin walking out your waist feels heavier. You see a pouch tied to it full with gold and a note attached: it reads in a manly scrawl "More to cum". As your ponder this you hear an vaguely familiar laughter, however you can't locate the source after looking up.</SetText>
		</RLSmellRoxyYes>

		<RLPalaceToiletGloryHole>
			<SetText>You tell #slave to wait outside once again. She gives a quizzical, but sharp look before sighing in resignation.\r\r You find what seems like your personal stall unoccupied once again and take a seat on the toilet. As you do, a large circular plunger comes off with a audible pop on the right side of the stall. As you look at it a bit shocked, a thick cock fills the hole.</SetText>
			<if smdominance='25-'>
				<AddText>Your submissive mentality screams at you to take the cock. You joyfully follow that particular call. </AddText>
				<AddText>You gingerly take the cock and stroke it till it becomes hard, </AddText>
				<if gender='3'><AddText>while you take your other hand and begin stroking your own cock, </AddText></if>
				<AddText>then you concentrate on stimulating your pussy. </AddText>
				<AddText>After getting it hard, you take the massive cock in your mouth and suck it. After a short while you hear a girlish grunt and semen explodes into your mouth. You end up swallowing a vast majority semen, however a little bit dribbles down your chin. As you prepare to clean off another cock replaces the last one. You perform the same task over, not once, but seven more times. </AddText>
				<AddText>Spent, you do your best to clean yourself off the splatters that got on both you and your clothing with the toilet paper in the stall. As you do a large bag of gold is slid underneath the stall, also attached with a note.\r "Very entertaining to watch, come to the slums if you want more."\rYou leave and spot #slave waiting for you.\r\r</AddText>
				<SMMoney>100</SMMoney>
				<if slavegender='3'>
					<PersonSpeak person='#slave'>I must admit, you do have quite a talent for sucking cocks.</PersonSpeak>
					<AddText>\r\r You tell her to drop the subject before returning home.</AddText>
				</if>
				<if slavegender='2'>
					<PersonSpeak person='#slave'>You reek of cum, and it looks like you missed a bit of cum on the inside of your thigh. Figures you would be doing that.</PersonSpeak>
					<AddText>\r\rYou blush and wipe the rest of it away with your hand. With murder in your eye you tell #slave to never talk about this ever again.</AddText>
				</if>
				<if slavegender='1'>
					<PersonSpeak person='#slave'>I must admit, you do have quite a talent for sucking cocks.</PersonSpeak>
					<AddText>\r\r You tell him to drop the subject before returning home.</AddText>
				</if>
			</if>
			<if smdominance='75-' smlust='75+'>
				<AddText>You look at the cock with lustful greed, already planning on what fun you can have with it. </AddText>
				<AddText>You gingerly take the cock and stroke it till it becomes hard, </AddText>
				<if gender='3'><AddText>while you take your other hand and begin stroking your own cock, </AddText></if>
				<AddText>then you concentrate on stimulating your pussy. </AddText>
				<AddText>After getting it hard, you take the massive cock in your mouth and suck it. After a short while you hear a girlish grunt and semen explodes into your mouth. You end up swallowing a vast majority semen, however a little bit dribbles down your chin. As you prepare to clean off another cock replaces the last one. You perform the same task over, not once, but seven more times. </AddText>
				<AddText>Spent, you do your best to clean yourself off the splatters that got on both you and your clothing with the toilet paper in the stall. As you do a large bag of gold is slid underneath the stall, also attached with a note.\r "Very entertaining to watch, come to the slums if you want more."\rYou leave and spot #slave waiting for you.\r\r</AddText>
				<SMMoney>100</SMMoney>
				<if slavegender='3'>
					<PersonSpeak person='#slave'>I must admit, you do have quite a talent for sucking cocks.</PersonSpeak>
					<AddText>\r\r You tell her to drop the subject before returning home.</AddText>
				</if>
				<if slavegender='2'>
					<PersonSpeak person='#slave'>You reek of cum, and it looks like you missed a bit of cum on the inside of your thigh. Figures you would be doing that.</PersonSpeak>
					<AddText>\r\rYou blush and wipe the rest of it away with your hand. With murder in your eye you tell #slave to never talk about this ever again.</AddText>
				</if>
				<if slavegender='1'>
					<PersonSpeak person='#slave'>I must admit, you do have quite a talent for sucking cocks.</PersonSpeak>
					<AddText>\r\r You tell him to drop the subject before returning home.</AddText>
				</if>
			</if>
			<AskQuestion caption='Do wish to suck on the cock?'>
				<Question event='RLPalaceToiletGloryHoleYes'>Yes</Question>
				<Question event='RLPalaceToiletGloryHoleNo'>No</Question>
			</AskQuestion>
		</RLPalaceToiletGloryHole>

		<RLPalaceToiletGloryHoleYes>
			<SetVar savedvar1_RedLily='savedvar1_RedLily+1'/>
			<SetVar savedvar3_RedLily='3'/>
			<SetText>You gingerly take the cock and stroke it till it becomes hard, </SetText>
				<if gender='3'><AddText>while you take your other hand and begin stroking your own cock, </AddText></if>
				<AddText>then you concentrate on stimulating your pussy. </AddText>
				<AddText>After getting it hard, you take the massive cock in your mouth and suck it. After a short while you hear a girlish grunt and semen explodes into your mouth. You end up swallowing a vast majority semen, however a little bit dribbles down your chin. As you prepare to clean off another cock replaces the last one. You perform the same task over, not once, but seven more times. </AddText>
				<AddText>Spent, you do your best to clean yourself off the splatters that got on both you and your clothing with the toilet paper in the stall. As you do a large bag of gold is slid underneath the stall, also attached with a note.\r "Very entertaining to watch, come to the slums if you want more."\rYou leave and spot #slave waiting for you.\r\r</AddText>
				<SMMoney>100</SMMoney>
				<if slavegender='3'>
					<PersonSpeak person='#slave'>I must admit, you do have quite a talent for sucking cocks.</PersonSpeak>
					<AddText>\r\r You tell her to drop the subject before returning home.</AddText>
				</if>
				<if slavegender='2'>
					<PersonSpeak person='#slave'>You reek of cum, and it looks like you missed a bit of cum on the inside of your thigh. Figures you would be doing that.</PersonSpeak>
					<AddText>\r\rYou blush and wipe the rest of it away with your hand. With murder in your eye you tell #slave to never talk about this ever again.</AddText>
				</if>
				<if slavegender='1'>
					<PersonSpeak person='#slave'>I must admit, you do have quite a talent for sucking cocks.</PersonSpeak>
					<AddText>\r\r You tell him to drop the subject before returning home.</AddText>
				</if>
		</RLPalaceToiletGloryHoleYes>
		<RLPalaceToiletGloryHoleNo>
			<SetVar savedvar3_RedLily='-1'/>
			<if smdominance='50-'>
				<SetText>Your eyes go wide eyed at the cock. You scramble off the toilet, you unsteadily unlock the stall with your shaky hands. As you run through the bathroom, you see a large group of futa women ponder curiously at you. Tears running down your eyes you exit the bathroom where #slave is waiting on you. Before she can say anything you tell her you're crying because some moron was smoking particularly strong hashish. In your head you vow not to be caught dead in that bathroom.</SetText>
			<else>if</else>
				<SetText>You take a deep breath to compose yourself. You walk out and find a stable full of futa's examining you. You give yourself a self assured smirk before calmly returning to #slave, whom you continue on with.</SetText>
			</if>
			<DoEvent>9999</DoEvent>
		</RLPalaceToiletGloryHoleNo>

		<RLPalaceToiletPoisonpt1>
			<SetFlag flagRedLily_3='true'/>
			<SetText>As you enter the restroom a woman follows in from behind. The first thing that draws your attention is her forearm thick cock, which bounces loudly against her midriff as she walks. As your gaze lingers on her she gives you a sly wink, rubs her finger against her belly collecting some of the precum film. She takes her finger and oh so suggestively sucks on it.</SetText>
			<DoEvent>RLPalaceToiletPoisonpt2</DoEvent>
		</RLPalaceToiletPoisonpt1>
		<RLPalaceToiletPoisonpt2>
			<if smdominance='35-'>
				<PersonSpeak person='Women'>Hmm... just looking at you I can tell. Let's do something very very fun my dear... I promise I'll make it worth your time, and that you'll love it.</PersonSpeak>
				<AddText>\r\rMore money plus more fun equals irrefutable offer for your nature.\rYou shake your head yes, she takes her hand cuffs and gently restrains your arms behind your back. Next, she ties a blindfold around your eyes saying something about how much more fun secrets are.</AddText>
				<DoEvent>RLPalaceToiletPoisonpt3</DoEvent>
			<else>if</else>
				<SetText>She quickly pushes you onto the tile in the bathroom. Without ceremony she quickly penetrates leaving you gasping. She grasps your hair and begins pounding you in dual pain/pleasure rhythm. After a few minutes of this you finally orgasm coating her cock in your juices. Smiling she removes her cock from your pussy and expertly drives into your anus. Originally there is a sharp burning sensation, but it quickly subsides thanks to your self supplied lube. After what feels like hours, but is more nearly five minutes she releases her hot load into your rectum. Instead of subsiding like a normal person she continues for a couple minutes leaving your innards full of her cum.\r\r</SetText>
				<PersonSpeak person='Poison'>You were a pretty good fuck girl. Maybe later if you're feeling more adventurous I could bring some of my friends and really throw a party.</PersonSpeak>
				<AddText>She continues to hold your hair, effectively keeping you in place. She then easily slides three coin bags into the opening of your vagina. On the third she keeps pushing... and pushing... your legs begin to quiver... and she keeps pushing, finally after she is elbow deep she begins to withdraw. Slowly at first, then quickly in an open palm leaving her hand drenched as you orgasm yet again. Licking her fingers she says, "this way you won't blow it all just after you got it", with a mischievous grin.</AddText>
				<SMMoney>300</SMMoney>
				<DoEvent>9999</DoEvent>
			</if>
		</RLPalaceToiletPoisonpt2>
		<RLPalaceToiletPoisonpt3>
			<SetText>After this she calmly walks with you to a carriage she seems to have hired prior to this. After riding for what feels like half an hour, but is probably less, she helps you out of a carriage onto a dirt road. She then quietly murmurs with someone.\r\r</SetText>
			<PersonSpeak person='Woman'>Thanks for being such a good sport dearest. Because of you being such a good girl, I\'ll even go easy on you.</PersonSpeak>
			<AddText>\r\rRough hands grab you lead you for a bit. The hands then undress you and remove your blindfold. You find yourself in a locker room, but as you are taking it in you feel, then see, a syringe plunge into your shoulder. The man who does it grins then says, "don't worry, just some Gaman, it'll help you last longer."\r With that the man helps you redress, then leads you outside in front of nation's largest arena. He quickly guides you through a door on its side that is well guarded.</AddText>
			<DoEvent>RLPalaceToiletPoisonpt4</DoEvent>
		</RLPalaceToiletPoisonpt3>
		<RLPalaceToiletPoisonpt4>
			<SetText>You walk through the door, only to see you have ended up in a metal cage with a crowd of men cheering around you. Across from you in the cage is your familiar "friend". An announcer in the middle simply announces you as the challenger, which gets a few pity claps from the crowd around you.\r</SetText>
			<PersonSpeak person='Announcer'>The champ accepts the challenge, putting her undefeated 64 win steak by way of 58 submissions on the line. You know her, you love her, the one and only Poison.</PersonSpeak>
			<AddText>\r\rAfter this you hear a bell ring, you raise your fists in preparation to fight. Seeing this, the crowd just laughs at you. Looking around trying to figure out why, you suddenly tumble to the ground with Poison over you. She hits you twice on the arm causing you to lose feeling and movement in them. As you\'re about to roll over, you stop as she somehow able to do the same thing to your legs with two surgical strikes. Smiling, Poison gets off your immobile body and undresses much to the whooping and hollering of the crowd. Poison then proceeds to rip your clothing down the middle, exposing your breasts. She then says, "lucky I promised to go easy, I would really love to break something as delicious as you." She then deep throats you, tweaking your nipples, destroying any thought of biting down. She continues her deep throating, causing you to get tunnel vision. She still yet continues her rhythmic thrusts, you are now presented with a decision, blackout or tap out. Yes-Tap out, No-Blackout</AddText>
			<YesNoQuestion>RLPalaceToiletPoisonpt4</YesNoQuestion>
		</RLPalaceToiletPoisonpt4>
		<RLPalaceToiletPoisonpt4Yes>
			<SetText>As you tap out Poison gets a wicked grin on her face, then says "Oh we will have so much fun toy." The announcer the comes on, although you can\'t figure out where, thanks to your head still swimming.\r\r\r</SetText>
			<PersonSpeak person='Announcer'>Oh! What a match..., this one still had ten minutes left for you gamblers! Congratulations champ on your fifty ninth new slave!</PersonSpeak>
			<if badend='true'>
				<AddText>\r\rYou're lead away in chains. As for your fate? At first you resist, but the mistress quickly and brilliantly grinds that out of you in a short time. Eventually, you end up love being under the Mistress, she treats you very well as long as you listen. You think you're her favorite, although that bitchy Cammy tries to out-whore you sometimes. The only downside is that sometimes the Mistress is busy, but she is amazingly nice enough to let you earn some spending money sharing your body with the world.</AddText>
				<DoEvent>9800</DoEvent>
			<else>if</else>
				<AddText>\r\rYou look around stunned, your throat soar from the beating it took from her massive shaft. As you sit there gazing in space you're chained and led away back into the bowels of the arena. As you take in the room around you Poison walks in with a winning smile on her face.\n\n</AddText>
				<PersonSpeak person='Poison'>Ha, we sure gave them a show! I hope I didn't frighten you too much with the whole act, but it is more convincing if you don't know what is really happening.</PersonSpeak>
				<AddText>\n\nWith that the chains are released and you are allowed to leave with a heavier purse, but much less dignity.</AddText>
				<SMMoney>500</SMMoney>
				<SMPoints><Dominance>-15</Dominance></SMPoints>
				<DoEvent>9999</DoEvent>
			</if>
		</RLPalaceToiletPoisonpt4Yes>
		<RLPalaceToiletPoisonpt4No>
			<SetText>Unbeknown to you Poison is true to her word and keeps  her shaft firmly impaled down your throat, saving you ten minutes of near suffocating. You pass out after a few seconds. As you reawaken your arms and legs are oddly sore, but thankfully you can still move them. You take a second, clearing your throat which tastes salty. After this you notice the smell of a thick cum in your nose. You look around and find yourself in the old bathroom, seeing a large bag of gold floor you take a second to compose yourself and leave.</SetText>
			<DoEvent>9999</DoEvent>
		</RLPalaceToiletPoisonpt4No>

		<RLPalaceToiletNormal>
			<SetText>As you enter the restroom, you see </SetText>
			<if timesVisited='2+'>
				<AddText>the same familiar </AddText>
			<else>if</else>
				<AddText>a </AddText>
			</if>
			<AddText>women standing in the corner casually reclining against the wall. Her lips draw into a smile, as her eyes trace around your figure. </AddText>
			<if smdominance='40-'>
				<SetVar loseStall='loseStall+1'/>
				<AddText>You eye the women measure her. Whilst she obviously seems more dominant then anyone in your position, you think you may be able to convince her to do a particular thing.</AddText>
				<AskQuestion caption='What act would you like to do?'>
					<Question event=''>Deepthroat</Question>
					<Question event=''>Blowjob</Question>
					<Question event=''>Jerk her off</Question>
				</AskQuestion>
			<else>if</else>
				<AddText>You return her gaze and clear your throat, motioning her to one of the stalls.\n\n</AddText>
				<AskQuestion caption='What act would you like to perform?'>
					<Question event=''>Deepthroat</Question>
					<Question event=''>Blowjob</Question>
					<Question event=''>Jerk her off</Question>
				</AskQuestion>
			</if>
		</RLPalaceToiletNormal>

		<RLPalaceToiletNormal2>
			<SetText>She crooks her fingers with a knowing smile on her face. Subconsciously you instantly recognize the dominance in her pose and demeanor, bending you to her desires. You try to fight conflicting messages in your mind, but she wins out in the end... and the bulge in her pants. You shyly approach her keeping your head down, eyes averted from her figure.</SetText>
			<Choices>
				<Choice>
					<DoEvent now='true'>RLPalaceToiletNormal2op1</DoEvent>
				</Choice>
				<Choice>
					<DoEvent now='true'>RLPalaceToiletNormal2op2</DoEvent>
				</Choice>
				<Choice>
					<DoEvent now='true'>RLPalaceToiletNormal2op3</DoEvent>
				</Choice>
				<Choice>
					<DoEvent now='true'>RLPalaceToiletNormal2op4</DoEvent>
				</Choice>
				<Default>
					<DoEvent now='true'>RLPalaceToiletNormal2op5</DoEvent>
				</Default>
			</Choices>
		</RLPalaceToiletNormal2>
		<RLPalaceToiletNormal2op1>
			<AddText>She hands you extremely lewd and humiliating clothing. Made from several pieces, one covers your forearm, another connects above your chest around a metal ring, proceeding to snake down the side of your body designed to flare and show off your hips. On the bottom it has two connectors that loop on the outside of your vagina connecting the front and back leaving your pussy bare. The long stockings connecting by hooks to the torso section of the outfit.\n\nSeeing that you have changed she clasps a gold leash around the ring. You open your mouth to ask her what she is planning but she quickly backhands you across the back of the head. \"The rules are simple, you\'re my slave. A slave only orgasms when her mistress allows it... or she will be severely punished.\"\n\n The women pulls out a pair of panties with a long vibrating dildo on the end. Whilst it is similar to ones you have seen before it is different, one in its girth, two in the rapid speed at which it vibrates, and three the juice that it seems to secrete. Strapping it onto you, you immediately feel your vagina quiver from the aphrodisiac laced liquid. The women tugs on your collar and forces you to crawl along, all the while the dildo rubs maddeningly against you. You crawl only a few steps before you climax. The women tugs on your leash again, this time you crawl at a fraction of the speed, barely being able to resist letting yourself go. It becomes apparent she is leading around the room.</AddText>
			<if this.bjskill * this.bjskill / 1250 > Math.random()>
				<AddText>Thankfully you manage to not allow yourself to cum again till the end, where she gracefully gives you permission to cum. Finally being free you climax in a long moan and what is very satisfying after holding yourself for so long. As you look up at her you realize she is gone, leaving you to gather yourself.</AddText>
			<else>if</else>
				<AddText>Unfortunately you cum many more times. Eyes full of disappointment she draws her hand back and spanks you for five times the times that you came, ass red and sore she walks off shaking her head. \"What a let down.\"</AddText>
			</if>
			<SMMoney>(Math.round(Math.log(this.bjskill * this.bjskill) * 8) * 3)</SMMoney>
			<DoEvent>9999</DoEvent>
		</RLPalaceToiletNormal2op1>
		<RLPalaceToiletNormal2op2>
			<AddText>The women leads you to the extra large stall at the end of the bathroom, as you enter the stall two well endowed twin red-head sisters stand in front of you dressed in black latex suits, staring at your body. From behind their stares, you can sub-consciously feel them them imagining new and perverse ways to violate you. The other women chuckles seeing there stares and comments before walking off, \"Don\'t get over zealous and break the toy girls!\" The one on the right walks behind you and closes the door, locking the dead bolt with an eerily loud thud.</AddText>
			<AddText>\n\nThey both move in synchronously, one saying, \"Let\'s see that pretty little ass of yours!\", while the other one says, \"Let\'s see those pretty tits of yours.\" Continuing to mirror each other they both undress you at the same time leaving you standing naked in between them. Suddenly the one behind you kicks the back of your legs, causing your knees to collapse, whilst the other one forces your torso down with the palm of her hand to the back of your head. Wasting no time they both slip in their cocks, leaving the heads of each resting just within your ass and mouth. They both say \"First one to cum is the sub tonight!\"\n\n</AddText>
			<AddText>They both begin rocking their hips back and forth at the same speed, their large meat a comfortable fit in your well used holes. Oddly enough their motions exactly mirror each other, their cocks twitch at the same time, they make the same moans, and their motions exactly mirror each other. Finally you feel the tell tale sign as each of their cocks between twitching at the same time. </AddText>
			<if chance='50%'>
				<AddText>As you sit their and ironically ponder their completely mirror like motions, as they both slow their pace as they prepare to cum, you are surprised as the one behind you unleashes her seed into your ass giving it a slimy coating. Not for the fact she came, but that they didn\'t cu... your thoughts are interrupted as the other shoots her load off down your throat emulating the other ones moan as she came.</AddText>
			<else>if</else>
				<AddText>As you sit their and ironically ponder their completely mirror like motions, as they both slow their pace as they prepare to cum, you are surprised as the one in front you unleashes her seed into your throat giving it a slimy coating. Not for the fact she came, but that they didn\'t cu... your thoughts are interrupted as the other shoots her load off in your ass emulating the other ones moan as she came.</AddText>
			</if>
			<AddText>They both withdraw their now flaccid cocks, smiling the winner sticks her tongue out, while the other one looks pouty. The girl behind you undoes the door as the other one walks to join her. Very strangely they seem to walk into each other inexplicably conjoining their bodies into one as they walk out.</AddText>
			<SMMoney>(Math.round(Math.log(this.bjskill * this.bjskill) * 8) * 2.5)</SMMoney>
			<DoEvent>9999</DoEvent>
		</RLPalaceToiletNormal2op2>
		<RLPalaceToiletNormal2op3>
			<AddText> She grabs you by the wrist and leads you to a stall, roughly pushing you in through the door of the stall.</AddText>
			<AddText>As you enter the stall you strip naked, exposing your genitalia to the elements. She, then makes a twirling motion with her fingers for you to spin. As you do she roughly grabs your hips stopping you, your ass exposed to her. Taking her index-fingers she lewdly plunges one into your ass suddenly . You croak at the suddenness of her finger\'s invasion, but are promptly cut off as a second then third finger join the original, creating a firmer fit around each one as she goes. Apparently her task complete, of loosening your anus, she withdraws her fingers. You feel your anal lips slowly part as she begins to delicately slide her cock into anus. Her tenderness, however, does not completely abate the stinging as her head slowly fills more and more of your rectum.\n\n After sliding all the way in she slowly begins violating you, allowing you to acclimate to the foreign member in your ass. Despite her original slowness, she begins to build up speed, her pre-cum acting as lubrication as she goes. She slaps your ass with a smack, at each crescendo of her hips meeting your rear. With your anus firmly wrapped around her dick for a time, her balls finally sputter coating your insides in cum which slowly drips as she withdraws with a popping sound of a seal being broken. Finished with your task you complete your usual ritual of cleaning up, and moving on to the next event on your schedule.</AddText>
			<SMMoney>(Math.round(Math.log(this.bjskill * this.bjskill) * 8) * 1)</SMMoney>
			<DoEvent>9999</DoEvent>
		</RLPalaceToiletNormal2op3>
		<RLPalaceToiletNormal2op4>
			<AddText>As you enter she reveals your cock and crosses her arms waiting for you to get to work. You take the dick in your hands and begin to sensually lick the expanding length up and down. Using your mouth you begin to slowly oscillate along her dick. You lightly bite down your teeth as the very tip comes in and out of your mouth to create more pleasure. When all is said and done she ends up cumming over your body. Satisfied with your work she leaves the gold and exits. </AddText>
			<SMMoney>(Math.round(Math.log(this.bjskill * this.bjskill) * 8) * 0.9)</SMMoney>
			<DoEvent>9999</DoEvent>
		</RLPalaceToiletNormal2op4>
		<RLPalaceToiletNormal2op5>
			<SetText>You take her soft dick in your hand and begin rubbing the tip with your fingers. From your motions pre-cum begins oozing out of the head of her penis, as the shaft begins to slowly harden. With this pre-cum you take your right hand and form an O-shape with your thumb and index finger. With this you start at the top and begin to slowly work your way down the shaft. Her breath shallows and quickens as you continue to pump your hand up and down her dick. With your other hand you cup her balls and begin slowly kneading them. Continuing this routine her dick sputters soon afterward rewarding you with a coat of sticky goo on your chest. She leaves depositing the gold behind herself.</SetText>
			<SMMoney>(Math.round(Math.log(this.bjskill * this.bjskill) * 8) * 0.8)</SMMoney>
			<DoEvent>9999</DoEvent>
		</RLPalaceToiletNormal2op5>

		<RLPalaceToiletNormal3>
			<SetText>As you enter the stall you strip naked, exposing your genitalia to the elements. She, then makes a twirling motion with her fingers for you to spin. As you do she roughly grabs your hips stopping you, your ass exposed to her. Taking her index-fingers she lewdly plunges one into your ass suddenly . You croak at the suddenness of her finger\'s invasion, but are promptly cut off as a second then third finger join the original, creating a firmer fit around each one as she goes. Apparently her task complete, of loosening your anus, she withdraws her fingers. You feel your anal lips slowly part as she begins to delicately slide her cock into anus. Her tenderness, however, does not completely abate the stinging as her head slowly fills more and more of your rectum.\n\n After sliding all the way in she slowly begins violating you, allowing you to acclimate to the foreign member in your ass. Despite her original slowness, she begins to build up speed, her pre-cum acting as lubrication as she goes. She slaps your ass with a smack, at each crescendo of her hips meeting your rear. With your anus firmly wrapped around her dick for a time, her balls finally sputter coating your insides in cum which slowly drips as she withdraws with a popping sound of a seal being broken. Finished with your task you complete your usual ritual of cleaning up, and moving on to the next event on your schedule.</SetText>
			<SMMoney>(Math.round(Math.log(this.bjskill * this.bjskill) * 8) * 1)</SMMoney>
		</RLPalaceToiletNormal3>

		<RLPalaceToiletRoxy>
			<SetText>You quickly enter the restroom As you enter the stall you can almost instantly feel your cunt start to begin to become to wet with eager anticipation. </SetText>
			<if gender='3'><AddText>At the same time blood begins rushing to your head as dick goes from flaccid to rock hard, your balls aching ready for action. </AddText></if>
			<AddText>Seconds after you lock the door, a giant cock begins filling the hole, at first it seems as if the head won't fit through, but after a few grunts of effort from the other side it quickly pops through. The sheer size, the girth it occupies, the sheen...\n</AddText>
			<PersonSpeak person='Roxy'>What's the hold up? Te he! Little Roxy is quite the stunner.</PersonSpeak>
			<AddText>\n\n You give yourself a personal smile surprised by how enraptured you were by it. You open your lips and begin wrapping them around the head, daintily playing the underside of it with your tongue. As you push further you are surprised when the cock itself gets stuck at your teeth. For their part the person across from you pushes against your mouth with little success, instead pushing your own head back. You hear the person across from you pound her fist against the wall obviously unsatisfied. Withdrawing their cock you take a few moments to gather your composure, until the stall door begins shattering against blows from the fist on the other side.\n\n</AddText>
			<PersonSpeak person='Roxy'>Open this door! Please! My balls are aaaaaching!</PersonSpeak>
			<AddText>Only seconds after yelling the wooden door fractures into pieces showering the stall, and by extension you, with shards of wood. Standing in front of you is Roxy, a carefree futa with what may be the thickest member on the block. Her warm smile quickly goes to a worried frown as she sees you littered with wooden shards. After a quick examination she looks satisfied that you aren\'t hurt however. Realizing this her smiles return as she says, \"Okay time to suck silly!\" Now semi-flaccid she takes her hands grabs the back of your head. Despite your struggles she is able to force her smaller, but continually expanding cock down your throat.</AddText>
			<AddText>As her cock reaches full girth you can feel your jaw bones aching, and your throat on fire as your throat spasms in contractions against her tool. Despite this she is able to in combination of her hip thrusts as well as her hands forcing down on your head she is able to establish a brutal pace.\n\n</AddText>
			<PersonSpeak person='Roxy'>Fucking better then my cock sleeve! Um-mm, I can see why you\'re all the bu-AHHHZ!</PersonSpeak>
			<AddText>With a final surge she forces your nose right into her sweaty aromatic sack, and sends a direct injection load straight down into your stomach. Finished she withdraws from your throat, her partially rigid cock coated in white goo. She then smiles, taking her cock she dangles it over your face, splatters of cum drooling down from it falling directly into your eyes. Taking it in her hands she takes it and brushes it in your hair, in effect cleaning off her cock.\n</AddText>
			<PersonSpeak person='Roxy'>Gosh! You make quite the mess! It was soooo much fun dear! I\'d help clean up your mess... but that\'s why I\'m paying you, hehe!</PersonSpeak>
			<AddText>\nGagging trying to catch your breath, while simultaneously trying not to move your incredibly sore throat, you put in little resistance to her cruel game. Giggling she wipes off the very last remaining bit of cum onto a small leather bag. Pinching your nose she deposits the bag into your mouth. Struggling not to break in laughter she says, \"The salty taste of a job well done.\" Taking her cue she heads off laughing, allowing you time to clean up yourself up and make it to your next engagement.\n\nSex skill +1. Now: " + this.bjskill</AddText>
			<SMMoney>50</SMMoney>
			<DoEvent>9999</DoEvent>
		</RLPalaceToiletRoxy>

		<RLContractOfferNo>
		</RLContractOfferNo>
		<RLContractOfferYes>
			<PersonSpeak person='Revy'>So this is how it works, I expect you to be here at least every other day for the obligated two weeks. Failure to do so will allow me, as stipulated, seize assets of yours to what may be deemed fair by me.</PersonSpeak>
			<AddText>\n\nShe quickly gives you directions to the Red Lily, expecting you to be present yourself the next day.</AddText>
		</RLContractOfferYes>

		<RLToiletService loseStall='50+' chance='5%'>
			<SetText>As you wander in you see the same women as normal standing there non-chalantly waiting for you. In a unsurprising sultry voice she addresses you.\n\n</SetText>
			<PersonSpeak person='Women'>I\'m a bit worn out today Miss. Although... if you\'re bored there is a bit of a problem. There working maintenance on the sewer system, tentacle eradication and such. As a result the water pressure has been quite low, making it so the toilets aren\'t quite working as well as they should be. Maybe you\'d be willing to help out on the issue?</PersonSpeak>
			<YesNoQuestion>RLToiletService</YesNoQuestion>
		</RLToiletService>
		<RLToiletServiceYes>
			<if badend='true'>
				<SetText>As you nod your head yes, the women violently comes at you with a piece of cloth and stuffs it up against your mouth and noise. You almost immediately lose consciousness, as your world turns black. As you come to you can feel the stings of the restraints all over your body where your limbs are bound, the soft drool running down your chin from the gag, and finally your vision is impaired by a blind fold. Rubbing against your bare ass you can feel the cool porcelain and open air under your ass that is quite familiar as a toilet.\n</SetText>
				<PersonSpeak person='Women'>I'd like to thank you for your willingness to help out with our toilet situation. We were looking for an upgrade over the standard affair. It really is a symbiotic relationship toy. You get your near-insatiable sluttish needs fulfilled, and the members of our upper-class get easy access to a fuck-toy whilst they are away from home, everyone one wins!</PersonSpeak>
				<AddText>\n\nAn odd feeling sets upon yourself. You originally imagined yourself struggling and detesting the actions of this women, yet an odd sense of relief and calm sets over you. In a way, you can see the reason behind your feelings. Exchanging your will for day after day of pure bliss has its appeal.\n\n...Weeks later you are much more happy with your situation then you once were. A majority of your days are spent tied up in some form or fashion in one of the stalls. You are nearly constantly fucked, a large line usually waiting to use you. In the mornings you are tied in such a way that the public has access to your mouth. During this time you are given your lot of food for the day via warm loads of cum, and on the rare occasion the sweet taste of pussy. During the afternoons your ass is fucked raw, often filled with more than one dick at once. You think your record was five at once, not that the owners of those cocks had anything to brag about. During the evening your vagina is available for a thorough fucking. It's during this time Roxy often comes and fills you up with her massive cock. It's always great when she comes, as you find yourself eagerly anticipating her arrival between visits. Finally at night you are lead around by your still mysterious captor who exercises you, while you wear all sorts of cruel and exciting bondage equipment. Overall life couldn't be better for you. As for your slave, you literally couldn't care less what became of her.</AddText>
				<DoEvent>9800</DoEvent>
			<else>if</else>
				<SetText>As you nod your head in agreement, the women violently attacks you. Luckily you are able to escape from her, and return from the bathroom shaken and bruised, but yourself none the less.</SetText>
				<DoEvent>9999</DoEvent>
			</if>
		</RLToiletServiceYes>
		<RLToiletServiceNo>
			<PersonSpeak person='Women'>Fair enough, see you some other time toy.</PersonSpeak>
			<DoEvent>9999</DoEvent>
		</RLToiletServiceNo>

		<RLSocialiceEasDrink0>

			<SetText>You end up having a pleasant conversation with her, learning her name is Eas and that she is just a tourist. After discussing some of the more interesting locations in the area you end with an awkward silence. You take this as your queue and get up looking for something else to do.</SetText>
		</RLSocialiceEasDrink0>

		<RLSocialiceEasDrink1>

			<SetText>You slowly talk to her finding out her name is Eas. With the edge broken with your current state of sobriety you slowly begin to flirt with her. You try using your charms to see how serious she is by moving your hand onto her thigh, when she returns the favor you begin popping in some dirty talk with her. She moves her hand up your skirt and begins lightly teasing your lips. As you begin to move your hand up she smiles and says, "Too public, meet me in the closet", pointing to the bottom right room.</SetText>
		</RLSocialiceEasDrink1>

		<RLSocialiceEasDrink2>

			<SetText>You walk up to her with a dopey smile on your face, you stumble a bit as you sit. The girl doesn't notice, or more likely decides not to comment. You drop a few corny and rather lewd pick up lines on her. She looks at you with no expression then surprisingly says, "... only thing worse then your pick up lines is sitting here, meet me in the closet and we can do something that could be fun." As she says this she points to the closet off to the side of the room.</SetText>
		</RLSocialiceEasDrink2>

		<RLSocialiceEasDrink3>

			<SetText>You walk up to her and promptly trip over your shoes, you end up landing right in her cleavage. She looks down at you with an angry frown, her cheeks turning red in embarrassment at the scene you caused. You look up at her and giggle, then quickly shake your head back and forth making a loud sound of, "BRRRRRRRRRRRRrrrrrrrrr". She grabs your arm and twists it around your back. She quickly leads you out of the room, supporting you so you don't fall on your face.</SetText>
		</RLSocialiceEasDrink3>
		<RLSocialiceEasDrink3p1Yes>
			<SetText>You begin licking Eas with all the vigor you can muster, only relenting to take gasps of air. After what you estimate to be fifteen minutes she suddenly gets up off of you.\n\n</SetText>
			<PersonSpeak person='Eas'>Pretty good, figures that it must transfer from all the cock you must suck. I'm going to give you easier access, but don't think that if you slack off for a second I won't do something much worse to you!</PersonSpeak>
			<AddText>With that you can hear her adjusting some equipment in back, all of a sudden you fly up and do a somersault so that you are now suspending belly down in the middle of the air. You wait patiently and are rewarded when you feel her fresh folds presented up to your lips. Without her saying anything you begin thrusting your tongue in and out occasionally giving a bit on her clit which causes a moan form her. After a while her pussy juices gush out as she hits her climax. You slurp up as much juice as you can and swallow down the juice which has a slight taste of strawberries.\n\n</AddText>
			<PersonSpeak person='Eas'>Enough, I think you've done enough, additionally I wouldn't like to be you in the morning.</PersonSpeak>
			<AddText>\n\nShe releases the cuffs on your body, then guides you on a brief walk. All of the sudden you feel fresh air hit your face, and no longer feel her presence behind you. You grab at your blindfold and find that you're now outside the Red Lily. Giving a collective shiver you walk away to continue your day.</AddText>
		</RLSocialiceEasDrink3p1Yes>
		<RLSocialiceEasDrink3p1No>
			<SetText>You try letting out a defiant refusal, which ends up just being gagged by the flesh on your lips. After a while it becomes clear to Eas you have no intention of complying. She says, "defiant for such a whore. Unfortunate for you, fun for me." She then shuffles her hips a bit, sitting on your face without a chance for air at long intervals at a time, leaving you gasping when she finally does allow you air. This cycle lasts for a long two hours which feels like a lifetime to you. Finally she gets up allowing you a long gasp of air. Tears running down your face from what equates to torture you beg her to let you go. After rubbing her chin, causing even more pleading from you she shakes her head with a smile.\n\n</SetText>
			<AddText>\n\nIt is at this point she starts playing with your restraints. Quickly you find yourself in the position where your arms are bound together at the wrist, with your hands bound through your thighs by your crotch. While your legs are completely immobilized with your calves tautly tied to your thighs. She then places a leather collar around your nick with a metal ring on the back for what you must presume is a leash. After this she examines your breasts, carefully weighing each in her hand, occasionally giving a soft pinch on your nipples. As a result of her unwanted attention you feel your nipples slowly hardening, until both are prominently sticking out. With malice in her grin she produces a pair of bar-bell nipple rings, with each separate one attached to each other with sturdy string. While on the string resides a metal circlet. She quickly punctures both of your nipples with the sharp ends, with slight discomfort to you. "This is my coup de grace whore.", she says as she holds up knotted rope.</AddText>
			<AddText>\nTaking the cord she first ties it securely around your already bound wrists. She carefully gets it through the ring located on the nipple piercing rope, taking the slack and running it all the way through. Then looping it back, she passes the rope between your thighs and up your back she runs the rope through the ring of the collar on the back of your neck. Finally she very tightly binds your legs together with yet more rope. In effect allowing you to move your arms up and down through your thighs, but not pull them out of your thighs. Planting a boot on your ass with rope in hand, she chuckles, "Ready whore?"</AddText>
		</RLSocialiceEasDrink3p1No>

		<RLBarDrink4>
			<SetText>
			</SetText>
			<DoEvent>RLBarDrink4WellFucked</DoEvent>
		</RLBarDrink4>

		<RLBarDrink4WellFucked>
			<SetText>As you groggily blink upon your cum caked eyes you find yourself in the stockades at the center of town. Shifting your weight around you find the rest of your body equally cum caked as your face, including your now sore ass and pussy.\nYou can\'t quite recall how you ended up here, other than it involved a lot of cocks, and a... well fucked pussy? After hollering a bit you eventually convince a good Samaritan to unlock you from the contraption. Eyeing the sun you figure you should be able to manage to clean yourself off and make the evenings trainings of #slave.</SetText>
			<ChangeTime>20-time</ChangeTime>
		</RLBarDrink4WellFucked>

		<RLNew10225>
			<SetText>I understand your decision, if that is what you think is best.\" She leads you out of the building to a small shack nearby which has a bed in it. She holds up a syringe with pink liquid inside of it. She sticks it into your forearm and presses the plunger watching the liquid go in with a keen eye. Upon injection the immediate spot begins to warm up. This heat quickly becomes searing hot, slowly radiating outward. As it does so, the roof of your begins to dry, whilst a more sharp pain develops in your groin, chest, and scalp. Eventually as the hot pain continues to spread your body goes into mild shock as you feint.</SetText>
			<DoEvent>RLNew10228</DoEvent>
		</RLNew10225>
		<RLNew10228>
			<SetText>As you come around, you find yourself lying nude and sweating in a bed. You recognize yourself residing in the same shack where you were first injected. Giving yourself a physical examination you cup your rather large breasts testing them in your hands. As you fondle your nipples you quickly become flush with arousal finding them overly sensitive. You continue down your body and tease the lips of your quivering vagina. Finding it slick and wet you explore it with your finger, becoming more familiar with yourself you finally stop. Looking on the floor you see a pile of clothing waiting for you. In it you find a set of risque lingerie, heels, and a very low cut purple dress. After finishing dressing the agent walks in with a distressed look on her face.\n\n\"Quickly we must hurry, our opportunity to get you in front of the recruiter is quickly diminishing.\"\n\nShe bustles you off down the city till you arrive near the high class district, she points you to an opulent building at the end of the street. She tells you good luck and to get going.</SetText>
			<DoEvent>RLNew10240</DoEvent>
		</RLNew10228>
		<RLNew10240>
			<SetText>Once inside the house a person meets you who refers to herself as the recruiter. Her skin is a pale alabaster white. Her eyes are a piercing blood red color, which sharply contrast her bob cut lavender hair. She is about 5\'7\" tall with a perky set of c-cup tits which are tightly pressed against her body thanks to a skin tight leotard that clenches against her skin. You notice around her neck is the amulet that the contact described at the bar.\n\n</SetText>
			<PersonSpeak person='Recruiter'>I\'m assuming you are here for the concubine position? Well you certainly look the part with those curves, so I suppose you pass the first check. Hmm well.... I nee... the client needs to make sure that you have the endurance required. You\'ll be expected to be ready to fuck on a moments notice, and be able to for hours straight. Let us begin now.</PersonSpeak>
			<DoEvent>RLNew10243</DoEvent>
		</RLNew10240>
		<RLNew10243>
			<DoEvent>RLNew10246</DoEvent>
		</RLNew10243>

		<RLNew10226>
			<SetText>"Very well then, hold still.\" She leads you out of the building to a small shack nearby which has a bed in it. She holds up a syringe with green liquid inside of it. She sticks it into your forearm and presses the plunger watching the liquid go in with a keen eye. Upon injection the immediate spot begins to warm up. This heat quickly becomes searing hot, slowly radiating outward. As it does so, the roof of your begins to dry, whilst a more sharp pain develops in your groin, chest, and scalp. Eventually as the hot pain continues to spread your body goes into mild shock as you feint.</SetText>
			<DoEvent>RLNew10229</DoEvent>
		</RLNew10226>
		<RLNew10229>
			<SetText>As you come around, you find yourself lying nude and sweating in a bed. You recognize yourself residing in the same shack where you were first injected. Giving yourself a physical examination you cup your breasts testing them in your hands and getting a feel for them. You continue down your body and tease the lips of your quivering vagina. Looking on the floor you see a pile of clothing waiting for you. In it you find plain underwear and a cute dress. After finishing dressing the agent walks in with a distressed look on her face.\n\n\"Quickly we must hurry, our opportunity to get you in front of the recruiter is quickly diminishing.\"\n\nShe bustles you off down the city till you arrive near the high class district, she points you to an opulent building at the end of the street. She tells you good luck and to get going.</SetText>
			<DoEvent>RLNew10241</DoEvent>
		</RLNew10229>

		<RLNew10227>
			<SetText>\"Hmmm, still clinging to your masculinity, perhaps a wise decision.\" She leads you out of the building to a small shack nearby which has a bed in it. She holds up a syringe with blue liquid inside of it. She sticks it into your forearm and presses the plunger watching the liquid go in with a keen eye. Upon injection the immediate spot begins to warm up. This heat quickly becomes searing hot, slowly radiating outward. As it does so, the roof of your begins to dry, whilst a more sharp pain develops in your groin, chest, and scalp. Eventually as the hot pain continues to spread your body goes into mild shock as you feint.</SetText>
			<DoEvent>RLNew10239</DoEvent>
		</RLNew10227>
		<RLNew10239>
			<SetText>You wake up in the same room in the bed. Lying on your back you are surprised to feel the weight of two B-cup tits now rest upon your chest, at the same time your dick now feels.... inverted. It is a strange feeling you can\'t quite reconcile, until you sit up and look, only to find out you now have a pussy. Lying on the wall is shiny set of plate mail, with a large silver sword laying next to it. You quickly dress in the armor. After finishing dressing the agent walks in with a distressed look on her face.\n\n\"Quickly we must hurry, our opportunity to get you in front of the recruiter is quickly diminishing.\"\n\nShe bustles you off down the city till you arrive near the high class district, she points you to an opulent building at the end of the street. She tells you good luck and to get going.</SetText>
			<DoEvent>RLNew10242</DoEvent>
		</RLNew10239>

















	</Events>


	<Visits>
	</Visits>


	<Planning>
		<Acts>
			<DoPlanning>
			</DoPlanning>
		</Acts>
	</Planning>

	<Slaves>
		<Slave>
		</Slave>

		<SpecialParticipants>
			<Participant enable='false'>
			</Participant>
		</SpecialParticipants>
	</Slave>


</Language>